<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2023-04-16T14:05:17.454Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The one about AI]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2023/04/15/ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2023/04/15/ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like everyone, I’ve been thinking about AI. It’s already useful, in a way that the previous big thing, crypto, wasn’t. I don’t think it’ll become generalized AI - I think the AI winter cycle is the base case and human-like intelligence is qualitatively different than LLM, no matter how many terabytes of training data you throw at them. But that isn’t what this article is about.
No, it’s about other stuff, particularly technological change, happiness, and craft.


Optimists and pessimists agree that AI will change the world.
If it goes wrong, AI will continue to do a bad job suggesting sentences for criminals and promise, but fail, to diagnose cancer, and find its way into a lot of other jobs that it’s not qualified for – much like an overconfident young man, which is also its preferred wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Azure Extensions in VSCode.dev!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/new-azure-extensions-in-vscode-dev/ba-p/3795806</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/new-azure-extensions-in-vscode-dev/ba-p/3795806"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T20:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of 3 Azure Extensions to vscode.dev! These extensions are Azure Static Web Apps, Azure Container Apps, and Azure Resource Groups.
 
vscode.dev is a development tool that is a lightweight version of VSCode that runs fully in the browser. You can open a folder on your local machine and start coding immediately or type “.” in a GitHub repository and it takes you directly to vscode.dev without any installation required.
 
So you might be wondering, why vscode.dev? What can I do in the browser? There is quite a bit of functionality that’s available at your grasp and that is fully discussed in this in-depth article. But for now, we will focus on the 3 Azure extensions that just shipped in this tool.
 
vscode.dev - Azure Static Web Apps Extension
 
Azure Sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>meerahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java to the cloud in minutes: JBoss EAP on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-to-the-cloud-in-minutes-jboss-eap-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3745277</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-to-the-cloud-in-minutes-jboss-eap-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3745277"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T18:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Jakarta EE- and Java-based applications offer a number of benefits for developers, taking the time to prepare them for a cloud transition can be cost prohibitive. With Red Hat® JBoss® Enterprise Application Platform (JBoss EAP) on Azure App Service, minimal to no rework is required, enabling companies to seamlessly transition their existing apps to the cloud. In some cases, that transition could be made in as little as 30 minutes! But there’s more to JBoss EAP and App Service than just speed—it can transform your capabilities, too.  
 

 
Benefits of JBoss EAP
JBoss EAP allows you to take everything you already love about your Java or Jakarta EE applications and move to the cloud for improved speed and more advanced capabilities. One key feature is the ability to quickly and easily s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayunk Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote certificate is invalid when calling an external endpoint from web app]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/remote-certificate-is-invalid-when-calling-an-external-endpoint/ba-p/3785758</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/remote-certificate-is-invalid-when-calling-an-external-endpoint/ba-p/3785758"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T00:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using .NET code to resolve “Remote certificate is invalid” when multi-tenant web app is configured as client in client-server model.
 
You can implement the server thumbprint in the .NET application code to resolve “Remote certificate is invalid” when multi-tenant web app is configured as client in client-server model and making HTTS request to a server configured with a private CA.
 
When a web app acts as a client and makes an HTTPS call to an external server secured by a private CA, the web app uses its default installed trusted root CA’s public key to validate the server’s certificate. However, the remote server certificate is signed by a private CA, and since there is no such trusted CA in the web app’s trusted source list, it will not be validated by the web app. You cannot modify th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma_Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshoot Failed External Calls Between App Services Using AppServiceIPSecAuditLogs]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/troubleshoot-failed-external-calls-between-app-services-using/ba-p/3793204</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/troubleshoot-failed-external-calls-between-app-services-using/ba-p/3793204"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service is a cloud-based service that allows developers to deploy and manage web applications. It provides an easy way to host your web applications without worrying about the underlying infrastructure. Sometimes, you may face issues when making external calls between two App Services. In this blog post, we will discuss how to troubleshoot failed external calls between App Services using the App Service IP Sec audit logs.
 
App Service IP Sec audit logs provide detailed information about the traffic that passes through your IPsec tunnel. This information can be used to troubleshoot issues related to failed external calls between App Services. The audit logs provide details such as source IP address, destination IP address, protocol, and port number.
 
Azure Monitor Logs reference…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ronelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic rebases on Dependabot pull requests stop after 30 days of inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-automatic-rebases-on-dependabot-pull-requests-stop-after-30-days-of-inactivity</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-automatic-rebases-on-dependabot-pull-requests-stop-after-30-days-of-inactivity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic rebases on Dependabot pull requests stop after 30 days of inactivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository topics and team filters for enterprise-level Dependabot, secret scanning, and code scanning pages]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-repository-topics-and-team-filters-for-enterprise-level-dependabot-secret-scanning-and-code-scanning-pages"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now filter by repository topic or team on the enterprise-level Dependabot, code scanning, and secret scanning pages in security overview. These improvements have shipped to GitHub.com and will be available in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9. Learn more security overview and send us your feedback Learn more about GitHub Advanced Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Logic Apps plans: Consumption based vs Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-logic-apps-plans-consumption-based-vs-standard/ba-p/3793997</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-logic-apps-plans-consumption-based-vs-standard/ba-p/3793997"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Logic App is an integration service. It provides you the opportunity to create and run automated workflows that integrates with your application, data, services and systems etc. These workflows can be written with little to no code. While creating a logic apps, when we come across the logic apps plan, there are two choices. 

Standard 
Consumption based

This is an attempt to help make a decision by comparing both the plans at a high-level. Hopefully, this will be helpful and help me achieve my goal.
 



 
Consumption based
Standard


Pricing Plan
Pay only for usage
Based on a hosting plan


Hosting Infrastructure
Multi-tenant/Shared
Single tenant


Best suited for
Entry-level, ad-hoc, for limited use
Enterprise level


Number of workflows
1
Multiple


Virtual Network and Private Endpoint Support
No
Yes


VNET Integration 
No
Yes


Network Isolation
No
Yes



Billing

Trigger and action operations

 
 
 

Storage operations




Per execution, after free built-in operations.
Managed connector operations, per call




Unlimited, included in the plan.
Managed connector operations, per call




Charges applies only to data retention related storage consumption.
Any storage operation run by logic app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>umeshpanwar1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now supports fetching release notes and changelogs for Docker images]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-dependabot-now-supports-fetching-release-notes-and-changelogs-for-docker-images</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-dependabot-now-supports-fetching-release-notes-and-changelogs-for-docker-images"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now supports fetching release notes and changelogs for Docker images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Functions with MongoDB Atlas in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-azure-functions-with-mongodb-atlas-in-java/ba-p/3795163</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-azure-functions-with-mongodb-atlas-in-java/ba-p/3795163"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing is one of the most discussed topics in the tech industry. Having the ability to scale your infrastructure up and down instantly is just one of the many benefits associated with serverless apps. In this article, we are going write the function as a service (FaaS) — i.e., a serverless function that will interact with data via a database, to produce meaningful results. FaaS can also be very useful in A/B testing when you want to quickly release an independent function without going into actual implementation or release. In this article, you'll learn how to use MongoDB Atlas, a cloud database, when you're getting started with Azure functions in Java.
 
Prerequisites
 

A Microsoft Azure account that we will be using for running and deploying our serverless function. If you don'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Month in Azure Container Apps: March/April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/this-month-in-azure-container-apps-march-april-2023/ba-p/3794238</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/this-month-in-azure-container-apps-march-april-2023/ba-p/3794238"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T01:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first monthly Azure Container Apps newsletter! We'll share the latest news and community highlights for Container Apps every month here on the Apps on Azure blog.
 
Azure Container Apps monthly community live stream
 
Our next live stream is April 13, 2023 at 11:00AM PDT (18:00 UTC). Join us to discuss our big announcements this month!
 



 
Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
 
Community highlights
 

.NET Azure Container Apps workshop
Deploy Container Apps with Pulumi and Go
Start from zero and scale to zero – Azure Spring Apps consumption plan
Learn Live – Azure Container Options - YouTube
Ask the Expert: Deploying a Python Project with Azure Container Apps - YouTube
Azure Policy for Azure Container Apps? Yes, please - Microsoft Community Hub
Simplifying deploying Azure Container Apps to Arc enabled Kubernetes using az containerapp up - Microsoft Community Hub
Using Azure Container Apps at scale instead of building your own NaaS on top of K8s?

 
Product news
 

Public Preview: New Azure Container Apps Pricing Plan and Enhanced Networking
Generally Available: Azure Monitor integration with Azure Container Apps
Generally Available: Mount Azure Files and ephemeral storage in Azure Container Apps
Public Preview: Session Affinity in Azure Container Apps
Public Preview: Azure Key Vault references in Container Apps secrets
New: Azure Container Apps environment now shows current Dapr and KEDA versions
New: HTTP service discovery via app name

 
For more, check out our product roadmap.
 
Get notified when we publish future newsletters, subscribe to the Apps on Azure blog. Connect with the Azure Container Apps team on GitHub, Twitter, and Discord.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets leaked historically in issues]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-leaked-historically-in-issues</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-leaked-historically-in-issues"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T21:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets leaked historically in issues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Improved scaling model for Azure Functions with Target Based Scaling]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-improved-scaling-model-for-azure-functions-with-target-based-scaling</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-improved-scaling-model-for-azure-functions-with-target-based-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling improvement for Service Bus, Event Hubs, Storage Queue, and Cosmos DB is now available for the Azure Functions Consumption and Premium plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Azure Functions V4 programming model for Node.js]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-azure-functions-v4-programming-model-for-nodejs</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-azure-functions-v4-programming-model-for-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a more intuitive and idiomatic experience for JavaScript and TypeScript developers writing Azure Functions apps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Availability:  App Configuration geo-replication]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-app-configuration-georeplication</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-app-configuration-georeplication/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Replicate your application configuration data across supported regions to create redundancy, reduce latency, and distribute request load.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps Announces New Pricing Plan and Enhanced Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-announces-new-pricing-plan-and-enhanced/ba-p/3790723</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-announces-new-pricing-plan-and-enhanced/ba-p/3790723"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Microsoft announced the public preview of a new plan and pricing structure for Azure Container Apps (ACA). This structure is designed to adapt compute options to individual apps and microservices components for more flexible microservices solutions. Azure Container Apps now supports a Dedicated plan in addition to the existing serverless Consumption plan.
 
The Dedicated plan guarantees single tenancy and specialized compute options including memory-optimized choices. In addition, the new Dedicated plan runs in the same Azure Container Apps environment as the serverless Consumption plan. This allows apps or microservice components that may have different resource requirements depending on component purpose or development stack to run in the same Azure Container Apps environment.  An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Morton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM with the REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-generate-an-sbom-with-the-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-generate-an-sbom-with-the-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T16:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM with the REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook forwarding in the GitHub CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-webhook-forwarding-in-the-github-cli</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-webhook-forwarding-in-the-github-cli"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook forwarding in the GitHub CLI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning default setup is available for Go]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-code-scanning-default-setup-is-available-for-go</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-code-scanning-default-setup-is-available-for-go"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T10:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning default setup is available for Go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost efficiency with Power Platform and Azure APIM]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-apim/ba-p/3793182</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-apim/ba-p/3793182"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T23:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of cloud computing, mobile devices, and the Internet of Things (IoT), APIs have become more important than ever, and their use has increased tremendously in recent years. APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, are the mechanisms that enable different software systems to communicate and interact with each other seamlessly. They allow developers to build flexible, integrated solutions that leverage data and functionality from multiple sources. This, in turn, enables businesses to deliver more personalized, efficient, and innovative services to employees, partners, and customers.
 
With the ability for software systems to communicate with each other comes the need for an efficient platform that can handle the integration of different applications and services. That’s why w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sonjagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost efficiency with Power Platform and Azure API Management]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-api-management/ba-p/3793182</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-api-management/ba-p/3793182"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T23:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of cloud computing, mobile devices, and the Internet of Things (IoT), APIs have become more important than ever, and their use has increased tremendously in recent years. APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, are the mechanisms that enable different software systems to communicate and interact with each other seamlessly. They allow developers to build flexible, integrated solutions that leverage data and functionality from multiple sources. This, in turn, enables businesses to deliver more personalized, efficient, and innovative services to employees, partners, and customers.
 
With the ability for software systems to communicate with each other comes the need for an efficient platform that can handle the integration of different applications and services. That’s why w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sonjagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metadata for active GitHub tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-secret-scanning-now-shows-metadata-for-active-github-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-secret-scanning-now-shows-metadata-for-active-github-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T21:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metadata for active GitHub tokens]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository archive date in GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-repository-archive-date-in-graphql-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-repository-archive-date-in-graphql-api"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T20:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository archive date in GraphQL API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting on files in a pull request is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-commenting-on-files-in-a-pull-request-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-commenting-on-files-in-a-pull-request-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting on files in a pull request is now generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1399-april-10-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1399-april-10-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We rolled out an update fixing a bunch of annoyances.  The main theme for this month is improving search quality and we are working on implementing new search sources.
 

In the upcoming months we will be trying to remove as many "limits" in our existing pricing plans and simplifying them as much as possible.
Family plan roll-out has been successful and we are pleased that many families around the world are enjoying benefits of ad-free and safe search for their loved ones. If you have not yet, check out Family plan features.
 


Kagi Search
"Visit Original URL" should be below the other two options #1295 @Browsing6853 
Summarize Page now follows Kagi interface language #1373 @peterdussaud
Summarize Results does not reappear for new queries #1346 @httpjames 
Unexpected behavior on malformed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage caches in your Actions workflows from Web Interface]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-10-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-10-manage-caches-in-your-actions-workflows-from-web-interface"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caching dependencies and other commonly reused files enables developers to speed up their GitHub Actions workflows and make them more efficient. We have now enabled Cache Management from the web interface to enable developers to get more transparency and control over their cache usage within their GitHub repositories. Actions users who use actions/cache can now: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated and customized dashboards for Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automated-and-customized-dashboards-for-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3786891</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automated-and-customized-dashboards-for-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3786891"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T12:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of you have been leveraging Azure Load Testing (ALT) to evaluate how your applications respond to high scale load and get actionable insights to fix performance bottlenecks. If you haven’t started yet, you can get started and run your first load test in less than 10 minutes.
 
Azure Load Testing (ALT) provides a unified dashboard of test statistics, client-side metrics, and server-side metrics so that the performance bottlenecks can be easily identified. While the out of the box dashboard is helpful in most scenarios, you might want the load test results to be available in a tool of your choice –

You have a dashboard to monitor multiple aspects of service reliability and you want to see load test results in that dashboard.
You want to observe the trend of specific metrics across test…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nagarjuna_V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup Multisite in WordPress on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-setup-multisite-in-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3791071</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-setup-multisite-in-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3791071"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T08:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try WordPress on Azure App Service here:

 
What is WordPress Multisite?
 
WordPress Multisite is a feature of WordPress that enables you to run and manage multiple WordPress websites using the same WordPress installation. You could update multiple websites in a single click by using the parent WordPress dashboard, and even manage individual sites through their individual dashboards. This feature was previously called WordPress Multi-User.
 
For example, a multinational e-commerce store can create multiple country-specific subsites in the same WordPress installation using this feature. The root admin can install plugins and themes required for all the websites at once. They can also assign different admins to each subsite. A lot of our customers use the multisite feature for various scenar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notifications for Team @mentions can now be disabled]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-notifications-for-team-mentions-can-now-be-disabled"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team Maintainers may now disable notifications resulting from a team @mention in GitHub issue and pull request comments through an optional configuration in the team settings page. Notifications resulting from PR review requests are unaffected by this setting. Existing issue and PR subscriptions are also unaffected. This team setting will also be exposed via API. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redirect from the non WWW domain to the WWW domain in the Azure WordPress Market Place offering-]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/redirect-from-the-non-www-domain-to-the-www-domain-in-the-azure/ba-p/3790022</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/redirect-from-the-non-www-domain-to-the-www-domain-in-the-azure/ba-p/3790022"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Navigate to your App Service via the Azure Portal. Under the Development Tools section, select SSH then Go -->.

 
2. Modify the default site config - You would need to make a copy of the existing configuration and place the file inside the /home/site directory by running the below command.
 
 
cp /etc/nginx/conf.d/default.conf /home/site/default
 
 
 

 

Go to https://<app name>.scm.azurewebsites.net/newui/fileManager click on Modify site/default file.


 

in the existing server block update the server name to www domain

 
 
server {

        listen 80;

        ## Your website name goes here.

        server_name www.example.com
 
 
 

In the same default.conf file, you can create a new server block and add the below configurations for non-www to www redirection -

 
 
server {

    listen 80;

    server_name example.com;

    return 301 $scheme://www.example.com$request_uri;

}
 
 
 
// This directive tells Nginx to send any request //for http://example.com to http://www.example.com with HTTP redirect code 301.

Copy the following code snippet to /home/dev/startup.sh.

 
 
cp /home/site/default /etc/nginx/conf.d/default.conf 

/usr/sbin/nginx -s reload
 
 
 

Please restart App Service and verify that the redirect from non www domain to www domain works fine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun_Baliga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running cronjobs in Azure App Service Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/running-cronjobs-in-azure-app-service-linux/ba-p/3789879</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/running-cronjobs-in-azure-app-service-linux/ba-p/3789879"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T08:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To schedule a cronjob on azure app service Linux web application you can follow the steps outlined below,
 

 
Navigate to “SSH” from azure app services portal and click on Go ->
 

 

 
Create a script file in /home with name as start.sh and add the below lines to the script file and save the file.
Command to create a script file - touch /home/start.sh
Open the file using vim editor: vi /home/start.sh and copy the below code
 
# Installing cron 
apt-get update -qq && apt-get install cron -yqq 
# Starting cron 
service cron start 
#cron scheduler 
(crontab -l 2>/dev/null; echo "* * * * * find /home/BackupLogs -type f -size 1k -delete ")|crontab
 
Post that, you can add the created script as a startup command which would install the cron, start the cron and schedule the cron during startup. To add as a startup command, navigate to Azure portal -> Configuration blade -> General settings tab and provide as below,
 
 

 
 
In the above sample code, it checks for all the files with size 1KB in /home/BackupLogs and delete them for every minute.
 
Based on your convenience you can adjust the CRON scheduler time and command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>karthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects – April 6th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-06-github-issues-projects-april-6th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-06-github-issues-projects-april-6th-update"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects - April 6th update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Crypto News Website in C# using the Microsoft Azure App Service and MongoDB Atlas]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-a-crypto-news-website-in-c-using-the-microsoft-azure/ba-p/3789523</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-a-crypto-news-website-in-c-using-the-microsoft-azure/ba-p/3789523"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who said creating a website has to be hard? Writing the code, persisting news, hosting the website. A decade ago this might have been a lot of work. These days, thanks to Microsoft Blazor, Microsoft Azure App Service, and MongoDB Atlas you can get started in minutes. And finish it equally fast!
 
In this tutorial I will walk you through:
 

setting up a new Blazor project,
creating a new page with a simple UI,
creating data in MongoDB Atlas,
showing those news on the website and
making the website available by using Azure App Service to host it.

 
All you need is this tutorial and the following pre-requisites, but if you prefer to just read along for now, check out the GitHub repository for this tutorial where you can find the code and the tutorial.
 
Pre-requisites for this tutorial
 
Be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambitious People Need Each Other]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9540</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/ambitious-people-need-each-other/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ambitious people don’t just need peers. They need mentors. They need people who will encourage them to pursue hard and meaningful projects. 
The post Ambitious People Need Each Other appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use WebP Images on Azure WordPress Managed Offering]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-webp-images-on-azure-wordpress-managed-offering/ba-p/3789326</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-webp-images-on-azure-wordpress-managed-offering/ba-p/3789326"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your WordPress Managed offering, go to webssh of your SCM site -  https://<app name>.scm.azurewebsites.net/webssh/host
Install the GD extension with Webp support using the below command.

apk add --no-cache --virtual .build-deps autoconf pkgconfig gcc g++ gawk make zlib-dev libpng-dev libwebp-dev \
&& docker-php-ext-configure gd --with-webp \
&& docker-php-ext-install gd \
&& apk del .build-deps
Copy the newly installed gd.so file to a persistent file storage. 
mkdir -p /home/dev/extensions
cp /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20200930/gd.so /home/dev/extensions/gd.so
 

Now write a post-startup script to restore the updated copy of gd.so everytime the app starts.

Edit the startup script file in /home/dev directory using the below command: 
vi /home/dev/startup.sh
Then add the following command to the startup.sh file and save it (type :wq to save).
 
cp /home/dev/extensions/gd.so /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20200930/gd.so 
 

Now restart your app from Azure Portal and you can upload a sample .webp image to test the changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun_Baliga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned navigation available in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-05-redesigned-navigation-available-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-05-redesigned-navigation-available-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned navigation available in Public Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Cache Retrieval Failures on Azure App Service - Node-Cache Example]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/addressing-cache-retrieval-failures-on-azure-app-service-node/ba-p/3786901</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/addressing-cache-retrieval-failures-on-azure-app-service-node/ba-p/3786901"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T01:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently encountered an issue when attempting to read cache values using the Node-Cache module on an app service running on multiple instances. However, the module worked fine on my local environment, single virtual machine, or single-instance app service.
 
This behavior occurs because Node-Cache and other private cache solutions are designed to store data in the memory of a single process. The private cache works properly when running on a single instance, as all requests are handled by the same process and have access to the same cache.
 

However, in a multi-instance environment like a multi-instance App Service, using a private cache can lead to inconsistent behavior and data inconsistency.
 
For example, you save a value in one cache in an instance. Then, a request tries to read th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yorkzhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding the Triage role and introducing new options for how content is reported]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-expanding-the-triage-role-and-introducing-new-options-for-how-content-is-reported</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-expanding-the-triage-role-and-introducing-new-options-for-how-content-is-reported"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T19:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding the Triage role and introducing new options for how content is reported]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export your sponsorable dependencies and sponsor many in one checkout]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-export-your-sponsorable-dependencies-and-sponsor-many-in-one-checkout</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-export-your-sponsorable-dependencies-and-sponsor-many-in-one-checkout"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Export your sponsorable dependencies and sponsor many in one checkout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling for Demand: Deploying Python Applications Using MongoDB Atlas on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/scaling-for-demand-deploying-python-applications-using-mongodb/ba-p/3786792</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/scaling-for-demand-deploying-python-applications-using-mongodb/ba-p/3786792"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing large amounts of data locally can prove to be a challenge, especially as the amount of saved data grows. Fortunately, there is an efficient solution available. By utilizing the features of Flask, MongoDB Atlas, and Azure App Service, you can build and host powerful web applications that are capable of storing and managing tons of data in a centralized, secure, and scalable manner. Say goodbye to unreliable local files and hello to a scalable solution.
 
This in-depth tutorial will teach you how to build a functional CRUD (Create, Read, Update, and Delete) Flask application that connects to a MongoDB Atlas database, and is hosted on Azure App Service. Using Azure App Service and MongoDB together can be a great way to build and host web applications. Azure App Service makes it easy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning adds support for C# 11 / .NET 7]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-code-scanning-adds-support-for-c-11-net-7</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-code-scanning-adds-support-for-c-11-net-7"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T08:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning adds support for C# 11 / .NET 7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surrendering to Your Nature]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9525</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/surrendering-to-your-nature/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T19:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mark of maturity is surrendering to the person you actually are instead of the one you wish you were. 
The post Surrendering to Your Nature appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API requests are available via audit log streaming – Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-03-api-requests-are-available-via-audit-log-streaming-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-03-api-requests-are-available-via-audit-log-streaming-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T18:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API requests are available via audit log streaming - Public Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price reduction in Hosting Plans for WordPress on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/price-reduction-in-hosting-plans-for-wordpress-on-azure-app/ba-p/3786290</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/price-reduction-in-hosting-plans-for-wordpress-on-azure-app/ba-p/3786290"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T17:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Database for MySQL – Flexible Server announced a new feature: Autoscale IOPS in October 2022. With this feature enabled, you do not need to pre-provision IOPs. The Flexible server automatically scales IO up and down depending on the workload. You can save on your costs as you do not have to pay for the resources you are not fully using. Read about the announcement here: Announcing Autoscale IOPS (Public Preview) for Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server
 
WordPress on Azure App Service is taking advantage of Autoscale IOPS and Storage auto-grow features of Azure Database for MySQL to provide you with more cost-effective hosting plans. Read more about these features here: Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server service tiers
 
Updated Hosting Plans:
 




Hosting Plan


WebApp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add MIME Types to Nginx - Linux App Service (PHP 8.x blessed image)]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-mime-types-to-nginx-linux-app-service-php-8-x-blessed-image/ba-p/3786096</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-mime-types-to-nginx-linux-app-service-php-8-x-blessed-image/ba-p/3786096"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T15:18:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIME types describe the media type of content, either in email, or served by web servers or web applications. They are intended to help provide a hint as to how the content should be processed and displayed.
Examples of MIME types:

text/html for HTML documents.
text/plain for plain text.
text/css for Cascading Style Sheets.
text/javascript for JavaScript files.
text/markdown for Markdown files.
application/octet-stream for binary files where user action is expected.

Server default configurations vary wildly and set different default MIME-type values for files with no defined content type. As new content types are invented or added to web servers, the users may fail to add the new MIME types to their web server's configuration. This is a major source of problems for users of browsers that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shuanand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository topics and team filters for organization-level Dependabot, secret scanning, and code scanning pages]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-repository-topics-and-team-filters-for-organization-level-dependabot-secret-scanning-and-code-scanning-pages"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T00:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now filter by repository topic or team on the organization-level Dependabot, code scanning, and secret scanning pages in security overview. These improvements have shipped to GitHub.com and will be available in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9. Learn more security overview and send us your feedback Learn more about GitHub Advanced Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2023/04/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2023/04/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weather is starting to get better.
Listening
Gift from the Trees by Mammal Hands

I am still really loving the constellation of bands around
Mammal Hands. They just released
a new album, “Gift from the Trees”, and it’s really excellent.
RETURN by tAKX

Their guitarist, Stephen Mullins, also just released an excellent
album that has more of a Fennesz
direction - guitar-based ambient.
Watching
Of course I watched Succession, and it was good. I also watched
four movies - the best being Nope,
which delivered on all the levels. The rest were more uneven:
The Neon Demon is
a “vibes movie”, Triangle of Sadness
was sort of an overdone, kind of tedious satire, and I disliked
how much I liked This is the End.
It started sometime in the pandemic, but my already-bad taste in movies
has gotten even…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server connector’s V1 actions and triggers will be retired on 31 March 2024 – transition to SQL Server connector’s V2 actions and triggers]]></title>
        <id>sql-server-connector-s-v1-actions-and-triggers-will-be-retired-on-31-march-2024-transition-to-sql-server-connector-s-v2-actio</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/sql-server-connector-s-v1-actions-and-triggers-will-be-retired-on-31-march-2024-transition-to-sql-server-connector-s-v2-actio/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T23:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server connector’s V1 actions and triggers will be retired on 31 March 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 31, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1371-march-31-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1371-march-31-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T22:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Family Plan
We are happy to announce the launch of Kagi Family Plans!
Read everything about it in our blog post Ad-Free Search for Families: Introducing the Kagi Family Plan.
Universal Summarizer
 

Muriel, our best-in-class model, is now available to API users.
Connect Universal Summarizer to 5,000 other apps with the fresh Zapier integration.
Added support for summarizing PowerPoint files (pptx). 
Added cache param to the API to control how are summaries handled (privacy friendly option). 
Added privacy policy for the Universal Summarizer.
Fix: AI Summarizer doesn't work with Thai #1315 @whs 
Fix: Unable to summarize English Wikipedia #1357 @whs 
Fix: Universal Summarizer fails on mp3 with error message 'No summary available at this moment, please try again later.' #1358 @AC2
 


New
Add…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metrics for custom patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-secret-scanning-now-shows-metrics-for-custom-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-secret-scanning-now-shows-metrics-for-custom-patterns"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metrics for custom patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice for npm PGP signatures]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-deprecation-notice-for-npm-pgp-signatures</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-deprecation-notice-for-npm-pgp-signatures"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T14:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice for npm PGP signatures]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Actually Listen]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9507</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/learning-to-actually-listen/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T14:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been listening the wrong way my entire life — with just my ears. True listening is a totalizing, full-body experience.
The post Learning to Actually Listen appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1369-mar-30-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1369-mar-30-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T04:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To everyone waiting for the launch of the Kagi Family plan - we expect it to happen before noon PST on Friday.  Sorry for the delay.
We will be also enabling EUR payments and additional payment methods.
 

Thank you for your patience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository security advisories REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-repository-security-advisories-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-repository-security-advisories-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T20:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository security advisories REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensitivity Isn’t Static]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9501</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/sensitivity-isnt-static/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sensitivity of our senses ebbs and flows. If you’re looking to be more perceptive, start by changing your environment.
The post Sensitivity Isn’t Static appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Organizations with REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-delete-organizations-with-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-delete-organizations-with-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Organizations with REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAMLIdentity GraphQL object now supports `read` scope]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-samlidentity-graphql-object-now-supports-read-scope</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-samlidentity-graphql-object-now-supports-read-scope"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T14:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAMLIdentity GraphQL object now supports `read` scope]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info messages for bypassing branch protections in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-29-info-messages-for-bypassing-branch-protections-in-git</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-29-info-messages-for-bypassing-branch-protections-in-git"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T13:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info messages for bypassing branch protections in Git]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure OpenAI Service, ChatGPT and more: Explore the latest developer resources]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-openai-service-chatgpt-and-more-explore-the-latest/ba-p/3741547</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-openai-service-chatgpt-and-more-explore-the-latest/ba-p/3741547"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T00:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our April highlight includes Azure OpenAI Service, ChatGPT and open source related technologies to help you better understand the impact they have on today’s development landscape. Start learning with free training and documentation, watch demos to explore new tools, and watch on demand sessions from the recent Azure Open Source Day event to dive deeper.  
Here’s some of the most recent resources to help you get started. 
 
Revolutionize your enterprise data with ChatGPT: Next-gen apps with Azure OpenAI Service and cognitive search   Revolutionize your enterprise data with ChatGPT. Pablo Castro explains how to combine Azure Cognitive Search and Azure OpenAI Service to build a solution that uses your organization’s data as the basis for responses.  
 
Microsoft Learn: Introduction to Azure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Medford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to the repository dependency graph view]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-updates-to-the-repository-dependency-graph-view</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-updates-to-the-repository-dependency-graph-view"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to the repository dependency graph view]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM from the dependency graph]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-generate-an-sbom-from-the-dependency-graph</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-generate-an-sbom-from-the-dependency-graph"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T18:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM from the dependency graph]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Visual Studio Code Extension is now in public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-github-actions-visual-studio-code-extension-is-now-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-github-actions-visual-studio-code-extension-is-now-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Visual Studio Code Extension is now in public beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Goes Mainstream In Security With Microsoft Security Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.forrester.com/?p=209436</id>
        <link href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/generative-ai-goes-mainstream-in-security-with-microsoft-security-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T15:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, security is late to the game with technology innovation. Before we get to see innovative technology, we have to wait for it to matter to security. This time, however, is different. In January, we predicted how the announcement of ChatGPT could change cybersecurity, and today, our predictions were validated again with the announcement of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allie Mellen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom plugin creation and integration with JMeter and Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/custom-plugin-creation-and-integration-with-jmeter-and-azure/ba-p/3745773</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/custom-plugin-creation-and-integration-with-jmeter-and-azure/ba-p/3745773"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T12:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JMeter has a lot to offer, though sometimes, you may run into use cases that are unique to your workflows or user scenarios, and not directly implementable using standard JMeter elements. For example, you might want to enable a custom authentication process, create a sampler of your own, or design a testing element that is not yet released in the open source JMeter community. 
Custom plugins extend the core functionality of JMeter and may allow you to implement that custom scenario into your performance tests to fine tune your test scripts and reporting capabilities. Learn how to get more from your performance testing, using custom plugins and Azure Load Testing.  
 
In our blog we will talk about how one can broadly classify planning and execution for performance testing in 3 stages.

Pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivam_Maralay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning shows the health of tools enabled on a repository]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-code-scanning-shows-the-health-of-tools-enabled-on-a-repository</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-code-scanning-shows-the-health-of-tools-enabled-on-a-repository"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T11:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning shows the health of tools enabled on a repository]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Light and dark theme color contrast improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-light-and-dark-theme-color-contrast-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-28-light-and-dark-theme-color-contrast-improvements"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Light and dark theme color contrast improvements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to install Drush on Azure App Service.]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/steps-to-install-drush-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3775011</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/steps-to-install-drush-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3775011"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T08:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing a Drupal website can be time-consuming, especially when it comes to updates, backups, and deployments. This is where Drush comes in. Drush is a command-line interface (CLI) tool for Drupal that makes managing your Drupal website faster and easier.
 
In this blog post, we will take a closer look at how to install Drush along with Drupal in Azure App Service.
 
If you wanted to know how to migrate an existing Drupal site to Azure App Service please refer Easy way to migrate an existing PHP site with MySQL to Azure App Service. - Microsoft Community Hub.
 
Please use following steps in order to install Drush on Azure App Service:
 
Step 1:
Go to your KUDU console http://<yoursitename>.scm.azurewebsites.net/newui (replace "yoursitename" with your actual Web App name) through the brows…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vinku85</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions: Version 4 of the Node.js programming model is in preview]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-version-4-of-the-node-js-programming-model-is-in/ba-p/3773541</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-version-4-of-the-node-js-programming-model-is-in/ba-p/3773541"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T17:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that version 4 of the Node.js programming model is currently in preview! This programming model is part of Azure Function’s larger effort to provide a more flexible and intuitive experience for all supported languages. If you follow news from Functions closely or happen to use Python as well, you may have heard about the release of the new programming model for Python last fall. During that time, we were working on a similar effort for Node.js. The experience we ship today is a culmination of feedback we received from JavaScript and TypeScript developers through GitHub, surveys, and user studies, as well as suggestions from internal Node.js experts working closely with customers.
 
What’s improved in the V4 model?
 
In this section, we highlight several key improv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lily-ma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cutoff deadlines and improved assignment dashboard for GitHub Classroom Educators, better deadline visibility for Students]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-27-cutoff-deadlines-and-improved-assignment-dashboard-for-github-classroom-educators-better-deadline-visibility-for-students</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-27-cutoff-deadlines-and-improved-assignment-dashboard-for-github-classroom-educators-better-deadline-visibility-for-students"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cutoff deadlines and improved assignment dashboard for GitHub Classroom Educators, better deadline visibility for Students]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental improvements to the security coverage enablement slide-out panel]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-incremental-improvements-to-the-security-coverage-enablement-slide-out-panel</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-incremental-improvements-to-the-security-coverage-enablement-slide-out-panel"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T21:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental improvements to the security coverage enablement slide-out panel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency graph GraphQL API preview includes submitted dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-dependency-graph-graphql-api-preview-includes-submitted-dependencies</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-dependency-graph-graphql-api-preview-includes-submitted-dependencies"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency graph GraphQL API preview includes submitted dependencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organization APIs for fine-grained PATs management]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-organization-apis-for-fine-grained-pats-management</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-organization-apis-for-fine-grained-pats-management"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T19:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organization APIs for fine-grained PATs management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: The setup-go Action now enables caching by default]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-github-actions-the-setup-go-action-now-enables-caching-by-default</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-github-actions-the-setup-go-action-now-enables-caching-by-default"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: The setup-go Action now enables caching by default]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 23, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1351-mar-23-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1351-mar-23-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T14:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the official launch of the Universal Summarizer by Kagi.
Universal Summarizer now features better and faster summaries, new input content types, a full API, Zapier integration and even an enterprise-grade summarization engine available.
Read everything about it in our announcement blog post:  https://blog.kagi.com/universal-summarizer
Try it:  https://kagi.com/summarizer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: SBOMs are now attached to hosted runner image releases for macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-github-actions-sboms-are-now-attached-to-hosted-runner-image-releases-for-macos</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-24-github-actions-sboms-are-now-attached-to-hosted-runner-image-releases-for-macos"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T13:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: SBOMs are now attached to hosted runner image releases for macOS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Static Web Apps with database connections: Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-static-web-apps-with-database-connections-best/ba-p/3777155</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-static-web-apps-with-database-connections-best/ba-p/3777155"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T20:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, many web applications depend on custom API backends to have access to databases. This approach allows you to have full flexibility over your database calls but building out such a backend can be tedious and complex, especially when considering the edge cases of a data-access backend such as authorization and relationships. With Static Web Apps’ database connections feature, and its underlying open-source project Data API Builder, you now have more options to build out database-backed web applications. In this blog article, we cover the considerations of choosing between these various options.
 
A quick introduction to the Static Web Apps database connections feature
 
As announced last week, Static Web Apps database connections is a new feature to connect and use databases directly …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thomasgauvinmsft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GitHub Classroom CLI extension for the GitHub CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-introducing-the-github-classroom-cli-extension-for-the-github-cli</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-introducing-the-github-classroom-cli-extension-for-the-github-cli"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T20:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the GitHub Classroom CLI extension for the GitHub CLI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally available: Azure Private Link support in Azure API Management]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-azure-private-link-support-in-azure-api-management</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-azure-private-link-support-in-azure-api-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T20:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Azure Private Link support in Azure API Management, you can now integrate clients in a virtual network privately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Preview: Workspaces in Azure API Management]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-workspaces-in-azure-api-management</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-workspaces-in-azure-api-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T20:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workspaces for Azure API Management is now in public preview. This new capability enables granular access control in multi-team Azure API Management deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed bug that allowed private issues and pull request titles to be shown in search results]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-fixed-bug-that-allowed-private-issues-and-pull-request-titles-to-be-shown-in-search-results</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-fixed-bug-that-allowed-private-issues-and-pull-request-titles-to-be-shown-in-search-results"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed bug that allowed private issues and pull request titles to be shown in search results]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roadmaps in Projects are now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-roadmaps-in-projects-are-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-roadmaps-in-projects-are-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roadmaps in Projects are now generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with MongoDB Atlas, NodeJS, and Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/getting-started-with-mongodb-atlas-nodejs-and-azure-app-service/ba-p/3776109</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/getting-started-with-mongodb-atlas-nodejs-and-azure-app-service/ba-p/3776109"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to easily deploy a MERN Stack application to Azure App Service
MongoDB Atlas and Azure are great friends! In fact, they became even better friends recently with the addition of the MongoDB Atlas Pas-as-You-Go Software as a Service (SaaS) subscription to the Azure Marketplace, allowing you to use your existing Azure credits to enjoy all the benefits of the MongoDB Atlas Developer Data Platform. So there is no better time to learn how you can take advantage of both of these.
 
In this article, we are going to see how you can deploy a MERN stack application to Azure Web Apps, part of Azure App Service, in a few simple steps. By the end of this, you will have your own version of the website that can be found here.
 
Table of Contents

Prerequisites
What’s the MERN Stack?
Create the Azure A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block ambiguous branch and tag names]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-block-ambiguous-branch-and-tag-names</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-23-block-ambiguous-branch-and-tag-names"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T14:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block ambiguous branch and tag names]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capturing a Network Trace on Azure Container Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/capturing-a-network-trace-on-azure-container-apps/ba-p/3776134</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/capturing-a-network-trace-on-azure-container-apps/ba-p/3776134"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T06:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're running an application on Azure Container App, there may come a time when you need to troubleshoot network issues. One of the best ways to do this is by collecting a network trace. In this blog post, we'll walk you through the process of collecting a network trace on Azure Container App using the `tcpdump` tool.
 
Step 1: Accessing the Azure Container App Console
To access the Azure Container App Console, navigate to your container app in the Azure Portal. Once you've selected your container app, click on the "Console" option under the "Monitoring" blade. This will open up a terminal window in your browser that you can use to connect to your container.
 
Step 2: Installing `tcpdump`
In case `tcpdump` is not installed on your container, you can easily install it using the package …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil_Vetteth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 1b – azd-ify an App Template with existing Bicep files]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/part-1b-azd-ify-an-app-template-with-existing-bicep-files/ba-p/3774273</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/part-1b-azd-ify-an-app-template-with-existing-bicep-files/ba-p/3774273"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've followed Part 1 and Part 2 of the azdev-ify or azd-ify series and are wondering whether you need to completely rework your Bicep files to `azd up` your app, you're in luck! The solution may be simpler than you think.
 
In this post, I'll walk you through the steps involved, which include:

creating an "azure.yaml" file via `azd init`
adding a "main.parameters.json" file
properly tagging your resource group and resources with `azd-env-name`
for deployment targets, add the corresponding `azd-service-name` tag as defined in "azure.yaml"

To demonstrate the process, I collaborated with my colleague Farhat Saleem in the Customer Success Team to azd-ify a sample integration app template that guides users through the process of setting up API Management policy for sending data to Azure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pcchan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start from zero and scale to zero – Azure Spring Apps consumption plan]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/start-from-zero-and-scale-to-zero-azure-spring-apps-consumption/ba-p/3774825</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/start-from-zero-and-scale-to-zero-azure-spring-apps-consumption/ba-p/3774825"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are launching a new way to pay for Azure Spring Apps -- the consumption pricing plan. This plan is now in public preview so you can start creating and deploying apps today. This new plan is super-efficient because you can start from zero and scale to zero vCPU.  You get more straightforward pricing across your containerized applications since it costs the same as Azure Container Apps, but with added value for Spring apps.
 
How does this work? With the new plan, you can deploy apps that don’t need to run all the time or apps that have bursts of traffic and only pay for the resources used. This is a “serverless plan”, which means your apps can scale out and in automatically depending on the number of HTTP requests or events they receive or simply run as always-on background jobs.
 
This …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asir_Selvasingh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Downloading Files from Azure Container App to your Local Machine via Azure Blob Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/downloading-files-from-azure-container-app-to-your-local-machine/ba-p/3774872</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/downloading-files-from-azure-container-app-to-your-local-machine/ba-p/3774872"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T10:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps is a powerful tool for running containerized applications in the cloud. However, if you need to transfer files (custom log files, network captures, etc.) from your container app to another destination such as your local machine or Azure Blob Storage, you might find that the process is not as straightforward as you'd like.
In this post, we'll walk you through the steps to transfer files from your Azure Container App to Azure Blob Storage using the `curl` command. Once the file is present on your Blob Storage, you can easily download it to your local machine from the Azure Portal itself in case you need to analyze the logs or network traces with a local tool.
 
Step 1: Accessing the Azure Container App Console
To access the Azure Container App Console, navigate to your c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil_Vetteth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying deploying Azure Container Apps to Arc enabled Kubernetes using az containerapp up]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-deploying-azure-container-apps-to-arc-enabled/ba-p/3773194</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-deploying-azure-container-apps-to-arc-enabled/ba-p/3773194"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since we launched the early public preview of Azure Container Apps on Arc enabled Kubernetes clusters last December, we have been working to continue to bring new features and capabilities to the preview (Container Apps on Azure Arc Overview | Microsoft Learn).  One area we have been keen to improve is the onboarding process and steps required to deploy your first Azure Container App on an Arc enabled Kubernetes cluster.
 
The number of steps and number of CLI extensions required to get to the point of having an app up and running is quite extensive:

Connect a Kubernetes cluster to Azure
Create a Log Analytics Workspace for app logs
Deploy the Azure Container Apps extension to the cluster
Create a new or use an existing Custom Location and bind it to the extension on the cluster
Create a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>apwestgarth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning API to enable default setup with CodeQL on a repository]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-code-scanning-api-to-enable-default-setup-with-codeql-on-a-repository</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-code-scanning-api-to-enable-default-setup-with-codeql-on-a-repository"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T17:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning API to enable default setup with CodeQL on a repository]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of granular access token on npm]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-general-availability-of-granular-access-token-on-npm</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-general-availability-of-granular-access-token-on-npm"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T11:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of granular access token on npm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use the “security extended” query suite in code scanning default setup with CodeQL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-you-can-now-use-the-security-extended-query-suite-in-code-scanning-default-setup-with-codeql</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-21-you-can-now-use-the-security-extended-query-suite-in-code-scanning-default-setup-with-codeql"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T09:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use the "security extended" query suite in code scanning default setup with CodeQL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable code scanning default setup with CodeQL at the organization level (public beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-20-enable-code-scanning-default-setup-with-codeql-at-the-organization-level-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-20-enable-code-scanning-default-setup-with-codeql-at-the-organization-level-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T21:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enable code scanning default setup with CodeQL at the organization level (public beta)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Secure Baseline accelerators for multi-tenant App Service deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-secure-baseline-accelerators-for-multi-tenant-app/ba-p/3745281</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-secure-baseline-accelerators-for-multi-tenant-app/ba-p/3745281"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure is excited to announce a new Secure Baseline scenario in the Landing Zone Accelerator for Azure App Service. This new scenario provides a simple, secure starting point to build new apps in the multi-tenant cloud platform, or to modernize your existing web apps running on-premises or in Virtual Machines with Azure App Service.
 
Landing Zone Accelerators accelerate deployment of Azure App Service at scale
Azure App Service is an easy way to deploy and manage web apps at scale, making it a no-brainer for developers looking to streamline their application deployments in the cloud. be more successful at any skill-level.
 
Landing Zone Accelerators were built to fast-track your production-grade deployments to Azure. These accelerators include a set of best practices, architectur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayunk Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1333-march-19-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1333-march-19-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-19T22:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New
All new AI features available on Lenses (Summarize Results, Summarize Document, Ask Questions about Document)
Result dropdown ("...") now available on grouped results
Custom CSS is now allowed on document chat page #1318 @exsesx
 

Improved
Many improvements to robustness of AI features
Clarifications in "Legacy Plan Renewal Notice" that you will always have access to the Early Adopter Pro plan
In more cases when AI fails to produce an answer, it is no longer counted as an interaction


Fixed
Summarize Results not working when a filter is enabled
Search suggestions working on mobile
Show stripe credits and manage billing portal for users in Trial state, with prior billing history
Fix settings dropdown not working on ipads and touch devices.
Fix summarizing arxiv pages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 19th, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1333-march-19th-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1333-march-19th-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-19T22:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New
All new AI features available on Lenses (Summarize Results, Summarize Document, Ask Questions about Document)
Result dropdown ("...") now available on grouped results
Custom CSS is now allowed on document chat page #1318 @exsesx
 

Improved
Many improvements to robustness of AI features
Clarifications in "Legacy Plan Renewal Notice" that you will always have access to the Early Adopter Pro plan
In more cases when AI fails to produce an answer, it is no longer counted as an interaction


Fixed
Summarize Results not working when a filter is enabled
Search suggestions working on mobile
Show stripe credits and manage billing portal for users in Trial state, with prior billing history
Fix settings dropdown not working on ipads and touch devices.
Fix summarizing arxiv pages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>