<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2024-03-07T14:07:25.152Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Support Portal redesign: Toward a more personalized future]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-github-support-portal-redesign-toward-a-more-personalized-future</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-github-support-portal-redesign-toward-a-more-personalized-future"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T22:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Support Portal redesign: Toward a more personalized future
The post GitHub Support Portal redesign: Toward a more personalized future appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Group Configuration Options for Dependabot Security Updates – Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-group-configuration-options-for-dependabot-security-updates-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-group-configuration-options-for-dependabot-security-updates-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Group Configuration Options for Dependabot Security Updates - Public Beta
The post Group Configuration Options for Dependabot Security Updates – Public Beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sponsor your dependencies for recurring sponsorships in one checkout]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-sponsor-your-dependencies-for-recurring-sponsorships-in-one-checkout</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-sponsor-your-dependencies-for-recurring-sponsorships-in-one-checkout"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sponsor your dependencies for recurring sponsorships in one checkout
The post Sponsor your dependencies for recurring sponsorships in one checkout appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Fine Grained Permissions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-actions-fine-grained-permissions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-06-actions-fine-grained-permissions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T19:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Fine Grained Permissions
The post Actions Fine Grained Permissions appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally available: Azure Functions Support for Node.js 20]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-azure-functions-support-for-nodejs-20</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-azure-functions-support-for-nodejs-20/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Develop functions using Node.js 20 locally and deploy them to all Azure Functions plans on Linux and Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Dark Sky Country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/protecting-dark-sky-country</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/protecting-dark-sky-country"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Protecting Dark Sky Country appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caia Hagel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-05-the-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-05-the-github-enterprise-server-3-12-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T23:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is generally available
The post The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 is generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps Newsletter – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-newsletter-march-2024/ba-p/4076252</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-newsletter-march-2024/ba-p/4076252"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this month's Azure Container Apps newsletter! We'll share the latest news and community highlights for Container Apps every month here on the Apps on Azure blog.
 
Azure Container Apps monthly community live stream
 
Our next live stream is March 5, 2024 at 11:00AM PST (19:00 UTC). Join us and our special guests to learn about Java on Azure Container Apps.
 



 
Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
 
Community highlights
 
Some great content created by our amazing community:

How Azure Container Apps Simplify the Cloud Deployment Process
Resiliency Policies in Azure Container Apps
Proxying Azure Container Apps With Yarp
Path-based routing and hostname-based routing in Azure Container Apps
Continuous deployment to Azure Container Apps with Azure DevOps
Observability on Azure Container Apps
Using Azure Python SDK to manage Azure Container Apps
Tomcat support in Azure Container Apps

 
For more, check out our product roadmap.
 
Get notified when we publish future newsletters, subscribe to the Apps on Azure blog. Connect with the Azure Container Apps team on GitHub, Twitter, and Discord.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 5th, 2024 - Wolfram|Alpha partnership, Claude 3 Opus and Mistral Large in Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3425-march-5th-2024-wolframalpha-partnership-claude-3-opus-and-mistral-large-in-assistant/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3425-march-5th-2024-wolframalpha-partnership-claude-3-opus-and-mistral-large-in-assistant/1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcements
We are launching instant Summary Boxes, together with announcing partnership with Wolfram|Alpha and welcoming Stephen Wolfram to Kagi's board of advisors.
 

Read everything in our blog post.

Features

"Small YouTube" (part of Kagi Small Web) feed has been enhanced with more content, check it out
 (+ RSS feed is available)



We've added Orion+ member count to our stats page.



You can now summarise videos directly from the results page via three dots menu. You can even ask questions about it (as with any other result appearing in Kagi search).  #3269 @Browsing6853



We've added keyboard shortcut for activating Quick Answer. Just press q on your keyboard after the results are loaded to get a quick summary of results. #3161 @Browsing6853
  
We added access to Mistral Large and Claude 3 Opus to Assistant (please note, the Assistant remains in beta and limited to Ultimate subscribers)



Improvements & Bug fixes
Simplified the onboarding process for Duo & Family accounts via universal invitation links
Apple Sign In, then Set Password, Breaks Apple Sign In #3330 @hanji
Handling for Desktop/Mobile Website Versions in Search Results #1727 @Wisely
Wrong results from currency converter #3366 @ioctl 
Search option bar can be vertically scrolled after reloading if the bar contains Quick Answer button #3328 @sefidel 
When you navigate back, the search query in the More Results button doesn't match the results. #3209 @xorgy
Cannot click enter in search box android #3315 @KaraZajac 
Wolfram Alpha math result does not meet expectation #3189 @brotis
Assistant doesn't remember last selected model in some situations #3223 @sefidel
Further improvements to fix $_latex_inline in quick answer #3225 @bert
The response None is returned by FastGPT #3343 @AndreL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions and Larger Runners; Windows 11 Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-04-github-actions58-larger-runners-windows-11-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-04-github-actions58-larger-runners-windows-11-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions&#58 Larger Runners; Windows 11 Beta
The post GitHub Actions and Larger Runners; Windows 11 Beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mkinitcpio hook migration and early microcode]]></title>
        <id>tag:archlinux.org,2024-03-04:/news/mkinitcpio-hook-migration-and-early-microcode/</id>
        <link href="https://archlinux.org/news/mkinitcpio-hook-migration-and-early-microcode/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of mkinitcpio v38, several hooks previously provided by Arch packages have been
moved to the mkinitcpio upstream project. The hooks are: systemd, udev, encrypt,
sd-encrypt, lvm2 and mdadm_udev.
To ensure no breakage of users' setup occurs, temporary
conflicts have been introduced into the respective packages to prevent installing packages
that are no longer compatible.
The following packages needs to be upgraded together:
mkinitcpio 38-3
systemd 255.4-2
lvm2 2.03.23-3
mdadm 4.3-2
cryptsetup 2.7.0-3
Please note that the mkinitcpio flag --microcode, and the microcode option in the preset files,  has been deprecated in favour of
a new microcode hook. This also allows you to drop the microcode initrd
lines from your boot configuration as they are now packed together with the main initramfs image.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Morten Linderud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Tomcat support in Azure Container Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-tomcat-support-in-azure-container-apps/ba-p/4074465</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-tomcat-support-in-azure-container-apps/ba-p/4074465"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T06:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, we introduced the code-to-cloud build process for Java on Azure Container Apps. This process brings simplicity, consistency, and a better mechanism to govern IT policies when deploying Java apps to the cloud. We’re now enhancing the build process with two new features: Tomcat and build environment variable support.
 
Tomcat is one of the most popular and widely used Java web servers, providing a fast and reliable platform for running Java applications on the web. By supporting Tomcat in the cloud build process, we make it easy for developers to migrate their existing Java web applications to Azure Container Apps without changing any code or configuration.
 
Build environment variables are variables that affect how the build process is executed. You can use them to specify the v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean_Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Immortal’ AI Challenges The Mortal Computation Of Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/immortal-ai-challenges-the-mortal-computation-of-humans</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/immortal-ai-challenges-the-mortal-computation-of-humans"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T15:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post ‘Immortal’ AI Challenges The Mortal Computation Of Humans appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.16.3: AI-powered autofixes for Python, updated queries, and security fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-01-codeql-2-16-3-ai-powered-autofixes-for-python-updated-queries-and-security-fixes</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-01-codeql-2-16-3-ai-powered-autofixes-for-python-updated-queries-and-security-fixes"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T10:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.16.3: AI-powered autofixes for Python, updated queries, and security fixes
The post CodeQL 2.16.3: AI-powered autofixes for Python, updated queries, and security fixes appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Path and hostname-based routing in Azure Container Apps with NGINX]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/path-and-hostname-based-routing-in-azure-container-apps-with/ba-p/4068923</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/path-and-hostname-based-routing-in-azure-container-apps-with/ba-p/4068923"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T01:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps is a fully managed serverless container service that enables you to deploy and run containerized applications without having to manage the infrastructure. 
 
By default, HTTP apps in Azure Container Apps are accessible via a public URL that is unique to the app. However, you can create a container app to use a reverse proxy like NGINX to control how traffic is routed to multiple apps based on the path or hostname.
 
In this tutorial, you'll learn how to use Azure Container Apps to configure path and hostname-based routing for a set of containerized applications using NGINX as a reverse proxy. You'll deploy 4 applications: 1 NGINX container which will be publicly exposed and 3 container apps which will only be accessible from within the environment and that traffic will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cary_Chai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/03/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/03/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Busy month! In January, I wrote
about the first four Val Town runtimes, and built a lot of
features in Val Town.
I also hacked around enough to make
Placemark Play available
again, the “free-as-in-beer” Placemark UI. It still
has some warts, but it’s there. Want to improve it?
It’s open source, so you can!
Listening
Put The Shine On by CocoRosie

I’ve been listening to this new-to-me CocoRosie
album. I fear that this is millenial music through
and through - they got popular because of the music blogs,
and their sound is almost an in-joke. But, like the rest of
their albums, this one has a few genuine bangers.
Again by Oneohtrix Point Never

I’m late to the Oneohtrix Point Never fascination. I came to them
like probably others have - their soundtrack score for Good time.
Watching
I’ve been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft and open-source software]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/microsoft-and-open-source-software/ba-p/4072418</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/microsoft-and-open-source-software/ba-p/4072418"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T21:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has embraced open-source software—from offering tools for coding and managing open-source projects to making some of its own technologies open source, such as .NET and TypeScript. Even Visual Studio Code is built on open source. For March, we’re celebrating this culture of open-source software at Microsoft. 
 
Explore some of the open-source projects at Microsoft, such as .NET on GitHub. Learn about tools and best practices to help you start contributing to open-source projects. And check out resources to help you work more productively with open-source tools, like Python in Visual Studio Code.
           
.NET is open sourceDid you know .NET is open source? .NET is open source and cross-platform, and it’s maintained by Microsoft and the .NET community. Check it out on GitHub.  
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mpgraven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push protection is enabled for free users on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-29-push-protection-is-enabled-for-free-users-on-github</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-29-push-protection-is-enabled-for-free-users-on-github"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Push protection is enabled for free users on GitHub
The post Push protection is enabled for free users on GitHub appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Extraordinary Lives Of Coast Redwoods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-extraordinary-lives-of-coast-redwoods</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-extraordinary-lives-of-coast-redwoods"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Extraordinary Lives Of Coast Redwoods appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction and Deployment of Backstage on Azure Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/introduction-and-deployment-of-backstage-on-azure-kubernetes/ba-p/4052492</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/introduction-and-deployment-of-backstage-on-azure-kubernetes/ba-p/4052492"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Backstage
 
Backstage, originally created by a small team during a hack week, is now a CNCF Incubation project. An incubation project means that it is considered stable and successfully being used in production, at scale by enterprises. Backstage is a platform for building developer portals which act as an operational platform between developers and the services they need to deploy. Developer portals can accelerate developer velocity providing push button deployment of production ready services and infrastructure.
 
In this Walkthrough we will learn about what Backstage is as well as how we can build and deploy it on Azure using multiple services including:
 

Azure Kubernetes Service
Azure Container Registry
Azure Database for PostgreSQL 
Microsoft Entra ID

Backstage Feat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>owaino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Azure Functions Support for HTTP Streams in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-azure-functions-support-for-http-streams-in-nodejs</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-azure-functions-support-for-http-streams-in-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use this feature for use cases where real time exchange and interaction between client and server over HTTP connections is needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Testing Azure Service Bus]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/load-testing-azure-service-bus/ba-p/4070521</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/load-testing-azure-service-bus/ba-p/4070521"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Azure Service Bus is a fully managed enterprise message broker that allows you to connect, decouple, and exchange messages between different applications and services. It supports a range of communication patterns, such as queues, topics, and event hubs, and enables reliable and secure message delivery at scale.
However, to ensure that your Azure Service Bus solution can handle the expected load and performance requirements, you need to conduct load testing and measure the throughput, latency, and resource utilization of your system under various scenarios. Load testing can help you identify and resolve any bottlenecks, errors, or failures that might occur when your system is under stress.
In this blog post, we will show you how to use JMeter and Azure Load Testing to load tes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita_Nallamothu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions: Support for HTTP Streams in Node.js is now in Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-support-for-http-streams-in-node-js-is-now-in/ba-p/4066575</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-support-for-http-streams-in-node-js-is-now-in/ba-p/4066575"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions support for HTTP streams in Node.js is now in preview. With this feature, customers can now stream HTTP requests to and responses from their Functions Apps. 





 
Being one of the most requested features for Azure Functions, we’re confident that this release will unblock Node.js Functions customers and make scenarios like processing large data, streaming OpenAI responses, delivering dynamic content etc. possible. Customers can leverage this feature for use cases where real time exchange and interaction between client and server over HTTP connections is needed. We recommend using streams to get the best performance and reliability for your app. 
 
HTTP Streams in Node.js is supported only in the Azure Functions Node.js v4 programming model. Follow these instructions to try…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madhurabharadwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise READMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-28-enterprise-readmes</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-28-enterprise-readmes"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T16:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise READMEs
The post Enterprise READMEs appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot – February 27th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-february-15th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-february-27th-update"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot - February 15th update
The post Copilot – February 27th update appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot – February 15th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-february-15th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-february-15th-update"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot - February 15th update
The post Copilot – February 15th update appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Rules – configure merge queue rule – public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-repository-rules-configure-merge-queue-rule-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-repository-rules-configure-merge-queue-rule-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Rules - configure merge queue rule - public beta
The post Repository Rules – configure merge queue rule – public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices for using Azure Container Registry and Docker Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/best-practices-for-using-azure-container-registry-and-docker-hub/ba-p/4068979</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/best-practices-for-using-azure-container-registry-and-docker-hub/ba-p/4068979"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many developers rely on Docker Hub to consume public content such as container images, Helm charts, and other artifacts, often without authenticating. However, when you have dependencies on public content you can introduce security and reliability risks into your environment. In this blog, we will describe the best practices for mitigating risks when using public content from Docker Hub and other public registries.
 
Import public content locally whenever possible
Importing public content to an internal registry is the first step in a set of best practices for your software supply chain . Doing so raises the availability and reliability of your public content pipeline. If you pull public content without using credentials from any public registry, including Docker Hub, you may be limited in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MSFTPM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untangling Religion From Our AI Debates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/untangling-religion-from-our-ai-debates</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/untangling-religion-from-our-ai-debates"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Untangling Religion From Our AI Debates appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Moynihan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-enterprise-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-27-copilot-enterprise-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Enterprise is now generally available
The post GitHub Copilot Enterprise is now generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Intelligent Apps on App Service with .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/creating-intelligent-apps-on-app-service-with-net/ba-p/4062684</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/creating-intelligent-apps-on-app-service-with-net/ba-p/4062684"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T19:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use Azure App Service to work with popular AI frameworks like LangChain and Semantic Kernel connected to OpenAI for creating intelligent apps. In the following tutorial we will be adding an Azure OpenAI service using Semantic Kernel to a .NET 8 Blazor web application.
 
Prerequisites

An Azure OpenAI resource or an OpenAI account.
A .NET 8 Blazor Web App. Create the application with a template here.

 
Setup Blazor web app

For this Blazor web application, we’ll be building off the Blazor template and creating a new razor page that can send and receive requests to an Azure OpenAI OR OpenAI service using Semantic Kernel.

Right click on the Pages folder found under the Components folder and add a new item named OpenAI.razor
Add the following code to the ****OpenAI.razor file and cli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeffmartinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning supports user namespace repositories for Enterprise Managed Users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-23-secret-scanning-supports-user-namespace-repositories-for-enterprise-managed-users</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-23-secret-scanning-supports-user-namespace-repositories-for-enterprise-managed-users"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning supports user namespace repositories for Enterprise Managed Users
The post Secret scanning supports user namespace repositories for Enterprise Managed Users appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing The Berggruen Prize Essay Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/announcing-the-berggruen-prize-essay-competition</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/announcing-the-berggruen-prize-essay-competition"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T15:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Announcing The Berggruen Prize Essay Competition appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New limits on scoped token creation for GitHub Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-22-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-22-new-limits-on-scoped-token-creation-for-github-apps"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T01:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a proactive measure to protect Github.com availability, GitHub Apps that attempt to create high-complexity scoped installation tokens will receive failures if they would individually reference too many repositories. At the time of release, no GitHub App is above these limits – the limit is approximately 8 times higher than what any app is consuming. […]
The post New limits on scoped token creation for GitHub Apps appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Azure Python SDK to manage Azure Container Apps - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-python-sdk-to-manage-azure-container-apps-part-2/ba-p/4059840</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-python-sdk-to-manage-azure-container-apps-part-2/ba-p/4059840"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T03:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Part 1 of this article, we discussed the implementation of Azure Python SDK for managing Azure Container Apps while using the DefaultAzureCredentials with Azure CLI (Developer Authentication). Here, we will be creating/updating a Container App Job using Azure Python SDK, while using Service Principal for authentication. Also, we will be using an App Service to deploy our project. We will be referring to the job creation sample which is one of the many templates provided in the Azure Python SDK template list.
 
Getting Started
 
Prerequisites
 
It is assumed here that you already have an existing Azure Subscription, Resource Group and a Container App Environment available. Also, we will be using a Linux App Service to run our Python project. Hence please make sure that you have a Pyt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ractando</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Country Shaped By Poetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/a-country-shaped-by-poetry</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/a-country-shaped-by-poetry"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T17:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post A Country Shaped By Poetry appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Strochlic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure API Center: The First Look]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-api-center-the-first-look/ba-p/4060180</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-api-center-the-first-look/ba-p/4060180"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you work for a company that has a lot of APIs. You might have a few questions:
 

How do you manage the lifecycle of those APIs?
What governance would you apply to these APIs?
What is the list of environments needed to manage these APIs?
What are the deployment strategies for those APIs?
How would you integrate those APIs with other services?

 
As your company's number of APIs increases, so does the complexity of managing them. Azure API Center (APIC) is a central repository for your APIs lifecycle management, and it offers the more efficient ways for management. Throughout this post, I will take a first look at what Azure API Center is and what it offers.
 

You can find a sample code from this GitHub repository.

 
Prerequisites
 
There are a few prerequisites to use Azure API…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinyoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.16.2: New Android queries and improved precision]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-21-codeql-2-16-2-new-android-queries-and-improved-precision</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-21-codeql-2-16-2-new-android-queries-and-improved-precision"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T14:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.16.2: New Android queries and improved precision
The post CodeQL 2.16.2: New Android queries and improved precision appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 27, 2024 - Bangs upgrades, user control enhancements, and colour code widget]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3290-feb-27-2024-bangs-upgrades-user-control-enhancements-and-colour-code-widget/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3290-feb-27-2024-bangs-upgrades-user-control-enhancements-and-colour-code-widget/1"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T10:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features
We've made further progress in enhancing Bangs in the UI. And following the release of our open-source bags repository, the community has contributed by adding and fixing dozens of bangs already! Additionally, we upgraded all bangs to use HTTPS where possible.



To further enhance user control, we now indicate when there are blocked results for your search queries  #2698 @Fernandez)



We've introduced a new colour code search widget. It displays the selected colour, allows to pick an alternative, and to convert between HSL and RGB formats   #118 @yokoffing)



Kagi for Safari 2.2.2
If you were having issues with Kagi for Safari, make sure you are running the latest version and that 'Engine to redirect' option in extension settings is set to the one used by Safari. 
[Changed] Adopted monochrome icon for toolbar/menu to match Safari icon styles


Improvements and bug fixes
Kagi Quick Answer now remembers 'Show more" option  #3241 @Dustin
We've introduced a new progress animation for the Assistant's responses (please note, the Assistant remains in beta and limited to Ultimate subscribers)
Include non-US universities in Academic lens #3303 @rainfallwaterfallweb
Automatic Kagi Status Page Updates #2914 @happinessattack 
Quotes cannot be used with assistant? #3276 @cardinal086
Quick answer freezes page #3237 @repelz 
LLM Model Help Chart - Add Cost and Context Window #3049 @CrunchyFritos
Error summarizing Von Neumann PDF #2978 @CrunchyFritos
Universal Summarizer on iOS should not scroll horizontally #3251 @equalidea
Site: search shows fewer results with "personalization" turned off #3040 @Value7609 
Broken search dropdowns #3278 @val
PDFs appear in image search #3289 @matteoscopel
Quick Peek breaks with "[ CDATA" in question #3308 @paszek
Taiwan(tw) bang is missing in region search #3287 @fc
Site: search shows fewer results with "personalization" turned off #3040 @Value7609 
Jisho bang encodes spaces incorrectly #3245 @adamaveray
Changelog formatting broken for lists #3280 @VIEWVIEWVIEW]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning adds validity checks for Mailgun and Mailchimp]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-20-secret-scanning-adds-validity-checks-for-mailgun-and-mailchimp</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-20-secret-scanning-adds-validity-checks-for-mailgun-and-mailchimp"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning adds validity checks for Mailgun and Mailchimp
The post Secret scanning adds validity checks for Mailgun and Mailchimp appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 20, 2024 - Kagi Bangs go open-source, Kagi Sidekick concept plus numerous improvements and bug fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3272-feb-20-2024-kagi-bangs-go-open-source-kagi-sidekick-concept-plus-numerous-improvements-and-bug-fixes/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3272-feb-20-2024-kagi-bangs-go-open-source-kagi-sidekick-concept-plus-numerous-improvements-and-bug-fixes/1"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcements

Kagi Bangs repository is now open source (thanks @Browsing6853 for suggesting this in #481). You can now refine the accuracy of existing bangs or introduce new ones for everyone to enjoy on Kagi Search. Your contributions will enhance the search experience for users worldwide.



Fresh from Kagi Labs: We're shipping an alpha version of Kagi Sidekick, a search and "chat with content" solution for websites.
 

  
Kagi Sidekick will offer instant site search results, and on-demand AI generated summaries, by tapping directly into the website's content. As a bonus, the website content will automatically (after opt-in) surface as a part of Kagi search index.
You can see Sidekick live in action in Kagi's documentation.

We'd love to hear your feedback, and how would you use it on y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to trigger Azure Function from Event Grid over virtual network]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-trigger-azure-function-from-event-grid-over-virtual/ba-p/4049984</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-trigger-azure-function-from-event-grid-over-virtual/ba-p/4049984"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T07:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. BackgroundIn the cloud environment, it's very important to securely protect sensitive APIs from unauthorized access and potential security threats originating from the public internet. Azure Function App provide Access Restriction and Private Endpoint feature to safeguard your Function App from unauthorized inbound requests.
In order to safeguard the Function App, one customer enable the private endpoint in Function App and implement the Event Grid trigger function, sending a message to Event Grid when the blog storage file changes and bring up the Azure Function. However, the Ip Forbidden (403) issue occurred from Azure Function.
 
2. The IP Forbidden (403) issue from Event Grid trigger function

 
Assessment:1.Function App aspectThere is Ip Forbidden (403) issue in Front End. The Even…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James_Yu320</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Automatic Secret rotation by triggering Azure Function from Event Grid over virtual network]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enable-automatic-secret-rotation-by-triggering-azure-function/ba-p/4055618</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enable-automatic-secret-rotation-by-triggering-azure-function/ba-p/4055618"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T09:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background:In most cases, the best authentication method for Azure services is by using a managed identity. However, there are scenarios where this may not be an option, and access keys or passwords are used. In such cases, it is important to rotate access keys and passwords regularly.
 
Automatic Secret rotation solution:Based on the document (https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/secrets/tutorial-rotation-dual?tabs=azure-cli), it proposes a solution to generate new access keys on storage account and update it in the key vault based on the secret expiry time. It uses Azure Event Grid to send the secret expiry event to an Azure Function App (aka the Azure Function App triggered by Azure Event Grid notifications) – which in turn generates the new access key and updates the secre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James_Yu320</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions Newsletter – February 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-february-2024/ba-p/4057533</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-february-2024/ba-p/4057533"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T22:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the February 2024 edition of Azure Functions newsletter! We'll share the latest news for Azure Functions here on the Apps on Azure blog.
 
Azure Functions monthly community live stream
 
Join us for our upcoming live stream on February 20, 2024, at 10:00 AM PST (18:00 UTC). Tune in to hear from Eamon O'Reilly, Lily Ma, and Madhura Bharadwaj as they discuss the latest releases in Azure Functions, provide insights into building intelligent apps with OpenAI, and unveil an exciting new feature in Durable Functions. Mark your calendars for this informative session!
 



 
Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
 
Product News
 
Following is the list of new Azure Functions features released since October 15 2023 
 




Areas


Feature




Languages



GA: Support for local …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madhurabharadwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Live With Elephants In The Backyard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/how-to-live-with-elephants-in-the-backyard</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/how-to-live-with-elephants-in-the-backyard"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T17:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post How To Live With Elephants In The Backyard appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Oriel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At The Climate Threshold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/at-the-climate-threshold</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/at-the-climate-threshold"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T16:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post At The Climate Threshold appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 Release Candidate is available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-15-the-github-enterprise-server-3-12-release-candidate-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-15-the-github-enterprise-server-3-12-release-candidate-is-available"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T14:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 Release Candidate is available
The post The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12 Release Candidate is available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step by Step Practical Guide to Architecting Cloud Native Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/step-by-step-practical-guide-to-architecting-cloud-native/ba-p/4057960</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/step-by-step-practical-guide-to-architecting-cloud-native/ba-p/4057960"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a step by step, no fluff guide to building and architecting cloud native applications.
Cloud application development introduces unique challenges: applications are distributed, scale horizontally, communicate asynchronously, have automated deployments, and are built to handle failures resiliently. This demands a shift in both technical approach and mindset.
So Cloud Native is not about technologies, if you can do all of the above, then you are Cloud Native. You don’t have to use Kubernetes for instance, to become Cloud Native.
 


 


Steps:
Say you want to architect an application in the cloud, and let’s use an E-Commerce Website as an example, how do you go about it and what decisions do you need to make?
Regardless of the type of application, we have to go through six distinct s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AbdullahAbuHassan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning’s push protection will soon be enabled for all free accounts on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-14-secret-scannings-push-protection-will-soon-be-enabled-for-all-free-accounts-on-github</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-14-secret-scannings-push-protection-will-soon-be-enabled-for-all-free-accounts-on-github"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T21:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning's push protection will soon be enabled for all free accounts on GitHub
The post Secret scanning’s push protection will soon be enabled for all free accounts on GitHub appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Custom Properties GA and Ruleset Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-14-repository-custom-properties-ga-and-ruleset-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-14-repository-custom-properties-ga-and-ruleset-improvements"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T19:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Custom Properties GA and Ruleset Improvements
The post Repository Custom Properties GA and Ruleset Improvements appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v1 and v2 of the artifact actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-13-deprecation-notice-v1-and-v2-of-the-artifact-actions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-13-deprecation-notice-v1-and-v2-of-the-artifact-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v1 and v2 of the artifact actions
The post Deprecation notice: v1 and v2 of the artifact actions appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot support for pub private repositories and registries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-13-dependabot-support-for-pub-private-repositories-and-registries</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-13-dependabot-support-for-pub-private-repositories-and-registries"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T21:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot support for pub private repositories and registries
The post Dependabot support for pub private repositories and registries appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating your JBOSS EAP apps to Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/migrating-your-jboss-eap-apps-to-azure-app-service/ba-p/4053972</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/migrating-your-jboss-eap-apps-to-azure-app-service/ba-p/4053972"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating web apps to App Service typically follows a 4-step process: 

Discover
Assess
Upgrade
Migrate

We'll take a look at each of these for a JBOSS EAP application, the cool store from Red Hat, as an example of an app migration using the latest and greatest tooling from Microsoft and Red Hat. 
 
If you prefer video content, check out the video demo, or livestream of this content.
 
Discover
Discovering applications can be a challenge, especially in the case of bulk migrations of large environments potentially containing hundreds or more applications. Azure Migrate makes discovery of web apps, servers, and even databases simpler than ever. Just run the appropriate Azure Migrate tool in your VM or on-prem environment to generate an inventory of applications, servers, and databases. 
 
As…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Azure Static Web Apps site using WordPress on App Service as a headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-an-azure-static-web-apps-site-using-wordpress-on-app/ba-p/4004955</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-an-azure-static-web-apps-site-using-wordpress-on-app/ba-p/4004955"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps is the ideal service to host static content sites on Azure. Many static sites are built using content from content management systems (CMS) into static assets and then deployed to Azure Static Web Apps. In this article, we take a look at using Wordpress on App Service as a headless CMS for a static site hosted on Azure Static Web Apps.
 
Evolution of traditional CMS's to headless CMS's
 
A content website generally involves 2 artifacts: the website code itself, and the articles that make up the website content. To build such websites, content management systems (CMS) are ideal tools to provide purpose-built editing experiences for content editors.
 
Traditional CMS's such as WordPress provide both the ability to edit content and the website code itself. They provide a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thomasgauvinmsft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 13, 2024 - Faster and more accurate instant answers. And we got a Wikipedia page!]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3179-feb-13-2024-faster-and-more-accurate-instant-answers-and-we-got-a-wikipedia-page/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3179-feb-13-2024-faster-and-more-accurate-instant-answers-and-we-got-a-wikipedia-page/1"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features

We added Wolfram|Alpha to enhance our capabilities in calculations, unit conversions, and time queries for better results. This solves a huge number of issues reported for these kind of queries as the results now come from a computational knowledge authorithy.
(Wolfram Alpha integration for fact based queries #1271 @Recast)



In the same spirit of getting answers faster, now simply starting your query with an interrogative word (what, where, who, which, when, how) or just ending it with a question mark (?) will automatically trigger Quick Answer:





Video results will now feature duration, channel name and timestamp  #2970 @blosh)

You can now hear how words are pronounced directly in our dictionary results, #321 @Yuu 

We've introduced a new feature in Research Assistant that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Azure Kubernetes Service Authentication Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-azure-kubernetes-service-authentication-part-2/ba-p/4055332</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-azure-kubernetes-service-authentication-part-2/ba-p/4055332"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the second installment of our multipart series on simplifying Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) authentication. In this article, we delve deeper into the intricacies of AKS setup, focusing on critical aspects such as deploying demo applications, configuring Cert Manager for TLS certificates (enabling HTTPS), establishing a static IP address, creating a DNS label, and initiating the groundwork for robust authentication. First part here Part 1
 
Let’s dive in!
 
Deploy two demo applications
In the previous post we set up our AKS cluster and configured NGINX. Now we will deploy two sample applications and deploy them. You can follow the official documentation here Create an unmanaged ingress controller.
 
First create the following two YAML files that define our two applications:
aks-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emiller635</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning adds webhook support for validity checks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-secret-scanning-adds-webhook-support-for-validity-checks</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-secret-scanning-adds-webhook-support-for-validity-checks"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning adds webhook support for validity checks
The post Secret scanning adds webhook support for validity checks appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Codespaces Connection]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-enhanced-codespaces-connection</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-enhanced-codespaces-connection"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T20:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Codespaces Connection
The post Enhanced Codespaces Connection appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects – Projects without Limits Private Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-github-issues-projects-projects-without-limits-private-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-github-issues-projects-projects-without-limits-private-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T18:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects – Projects without Limits Private Beta
The post GitHub Issues & Projects – Projects without Limits Private Beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Could Actually Help Rebuild The Middle Class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/how-ai-could-help-rebuild-the-middle-class</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/how-ai-could-help-rebuild-the-middle-class"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post AI Could Actually Help Rebuild The Middle Class appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Autor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Copilot Chat January 2024 (version 0.12)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-vs-code-copilot-chat-january-2024-version-0-12</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-12-vs-code-copilot-chat-january-2024-version-0-12"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T17:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Copilot Chat January 2024 (version 0.12)
The post VS Code Copilot Chat January 2024 (version 0.12) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Improvements in Azure Key Vault]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-improvements-in-azure-key-vault</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-improvements-in-azure-key-vault/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements in Azure Key Vault: FIPS 140-2 Level 3, PCI DSS and PCI 3DS certified for all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot in GitHub Support (GA)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-09-copilot-in-github-support-ga</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-02-09-copilot-in-github-support-ga"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T17:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot in GitHub Support (GA)
The post Copilot in GitHub Support (GA) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feb 8, 2024 - Ultimate features available for Family / Duo plans]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3122-feb-8-2024-ultimate-features-available-for-family-duo-plans/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3122-feb-8-2024-ultimate-features-available-for-family-duo-plans/1"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features
We're happy to announce that Family and Duo plan members can now upgrade to Ultimate plan features for just $15 per month. The Ultimate plan includes access to the latest AI models, such as GPT-4/GPT-4-Turbo, Claude 2.1 (100k) and soon Gemini Ultra. To upgrade your account or that of another member, simply visit the "Members" section under Family Settings.

 #2024 @nucleardog

Kagi for Safari 2.2.0 is released, fixing many previous issues reported by the users.



We've improved the mobile experience for Assistant users. Now, Now, when composing your prompt, you can effortlessly access settings for Assistant, including options for Research mode and Chat mode. Additionally, the entire prompt is now fully visible.

Improvements & Bug fixes
Kagi search on Firefox ESR 78 give JS error (previously fixed but happening again) #3055 @kagi-not-working 
Weather Widget Doesn't Display when Asking for Temperature #3046 @bhagwad
/ (slash) keyboard shortcut doesn't scroll to top in safari #2989 @nullable
Quick answer does not always show up on results page #3035 @stoyle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clock In The Forest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/a-clock-in-the-forest</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/a-clock-in-the-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T15:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post A Clock In The Forest appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathon Keats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Azure Python SDK to manage Azure Container Apps - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-python-sdk-to-manage-azure-container-apps-part-1/ba-p/4050894</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-python-sdk-to-manage-azure-container-apps-part-1/ba-p/4050894"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T09:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Python SDK is a set of libraries and packages that allow developers to interact with Microsoft Azure services using the Python programming language. It simplifies the process of integrating Python applications with Azure services by providing a set of high-level abstractions and APIs. With the SDK, developers can programmatically manage and interact with Azure resources, such as virtual machines, storage accounts, databases, and other cloud services.
 
To use the Azure Python SDK, developers typically install the required Python packages using a package manager like pip. They can then import the relevant modules into their Python code and use the classes provided and methods to interact with Azure services.
 
If we talk about Azure Container Apps, Microsoft provides comprehensive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ractando</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Azure Container Apps using Azure Python SDK]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/creating-azure-container-apps-using-azure-python-sdk/ba-p/4050894</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/creating-azure-container-apps-using-azure-python-sdk/ba-p/4050894"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T09:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Python SDK is a set of libraries and packages that allow developers to interact with Microsoft Azure services using the Python programming language. It simplifies the process of integrating Python applications with Azure services by providing a set of high-level abstractions and APIs. With the SDK, developers can programmatically manage and interact with Azure resources, such as virtual machines, storage accounts, databases, and other cloud services.
 
To use the Azure Python SDK, developers typically install the required Python packages using a package manager like pip. They can then import the relevant modules into their Python code and use the classes provided and methods to interact with Azure services.
 
If we talk about Azure Container Apps, Microsoft provides comprehensive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ractando</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Azure Kubernetes Service Authentication Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-azure-kubernetes-service-authentication-part-1/ba-p/4051439</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simplifying-azure-kubernetes-service-authentication-part-1/ba-p/4051439"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T15:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a step-by-step guide on how to enable authentication for your Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) cluster, you may have encountered some challenges. The documentation on this topic is scarce and often outdated or incomplete. Moreover, you may have specific requirements for your use case that are not covered by the existing resources. That is why I have created this comprehensive guide using the latest Azure cloud resources.
 
In this guide, you will learn how to set up an AKS cluster and provide authentication to that cluster using NGINX and the OAuth2 proxy. This guide is intended for educational purposes only and does not guarantee proper authentication as certified by NIST. It is also not a complete solution for securing your AKS cluster, which involves more than just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>emiller635</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>