<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2021-07-17T14:11:32.567Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does the sleeping brain think about?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715124527.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715124527.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T16:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using an artificial intelligence approach capable of decoding brain activity during sleep, scientists were able to glimpse what we think about when we are asleep. By combining fMRI and EEG, they provide unprecedented evidence that the work of sorting out the thousands of pieces of information processed during the day takes place during deep sleep. Indeed, the brain can evaluate all of these memories in order to retain only the most useful ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researcher creates cell lines to help treat mitochondrial diseases in children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715103015.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715103015.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T14:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mitochondrion has garnered quite the reputation for its role as the 'powerhouse of the cell.' These tiny, but mighty organelles play various life-sustaining roles, from powering our own cells and organs to fueling chemical and biological processes. But when they aren't working properly, a number of rare diseases can occur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new avenue for fighting drug-resistant bacteria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715090826.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210715090826.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-15T13:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small regulatory RNA found in many problematic bacteria, including Escherichia coli, appears to be responsible for managing the response of these bacteria to environmental stresses. Researchers see a promising avenue for more effective treatment of antibiotic-resistant bacteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultra-processed food linked to higher risk of IBD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714183430.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714183430.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T22:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A higher intake of ultra-processed food is associated with higher risk of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD), finds a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Think about this: Keeping your brain active may delay Alzheimer's dementia 5 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714170134.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714170134.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T21:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your brain active in old age has always been a smart idea, but a new study suggests that reading, writing letters and playing card games or puzzles in later life may delay the onset of Alzheimer's dementia by up to five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: API Management and Event Grid integration]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-api-management-and-event-grid-integration</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-api-management-and-event-grid-integration/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure API Management has now been updated to publish events to Event Grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signaling molecule may help prevent Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714110528.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210714110528.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-14T15:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main driver of Alzheimer's disease is excessive inflammation in the brain that is triggered by cells called astrocytes and microglia in response to high levels of amyloid beta deposits and tau tangles. New research reveals that a subset of astrocytes releases a molecule called interleukin-3 that instructs microglia to adopt a protective response and clear away amyloid beta deposits and tau tangles. Interleukin-3 may hold promise as a new therapeutic intervention in Alzheimer's disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eating whole grains linked to smaller increases in waist size, blood pressure, blood sugar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713165308.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713165308.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T20:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study finds middle- to older-aged adults who ate more servings of whole grains, compared to those who ate fewer, were more likely to have smaller increases in waist size, blood pressure, and blood sugar levels as they aged. All three are linked with increased risk of heart disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent study identifies 11 candidate genetic variants for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713110842.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713110842.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently published study identifies 11 rare candidate variants for Alzheimer's disease. Researchers found 19 different families in Utah that suffered from Alzheimer's disease more frequently than what is considered normal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining plant-based diet and healthy microbiome may protect against multiple sclerosis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713110811.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210713110811.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T15:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that a diet rich in isoflavone, a phytoestrogen or plant-based compound that resembles estrogen, protects against multiple sclerosis-like symptoms in a mouse model of the disease. Importantly, the isoflavone diet was only protective when the mice had gut microbes capable of breaking down the isoflavones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Azure API Management updates - July 2021]]></title>
        <id>azure-api-management-updates-july-2021</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/azure-api-management-updates-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure API Management service has been updated to provide better support to customers through policy expressions and Power platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Clock' created to predict immunological health and chronic diseases of aging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122159.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122159.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T16:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have created an inflammatory clock of aging (iAge) which measures inflammatory load and predicts multi-morbidity, frailty, immune health, cardiovascular aging and is also associated with exceptional longevity in centenarians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A fermented-food diet increases microbiome diversity and lowers inflammation, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122151.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122151.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T16:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A diet rich in fermented foods enhances the diversity of gut microbes and decreases molecular signs of inflammation, according to researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preferred life expectancy and its association with hypothetical adverse life scenarios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122112.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712122112.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T16:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study sheds light on how the specter of dementia and chronic pain reduce people's desire to live into older ages. Among Norwegians 60 years of age and older the desire to live into advanced ages was significantly reduced by hypothetical adverse life scenarios with the strongest effect caused by dementia and chronic pain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step toward advancing precision hormone therapies to reduce Alzheimer's risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712092238.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210712092238.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to post-menopausal hormone therapy, the type, route and duration all play a role in reducing the risk of neurodegenerative diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to light with less blue before sleep is better for energy metabolism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210709104232.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210709104232.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that exposure to specific types of light before sleep can have variable effects on energy metabolism during sleep. Specifically, participants who went to sleep after exposure to organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs), which emit polychromatic white light that contains less blue light than light-emitting diodes (LEDs), exhibited significantly decreased energy expenditure, core body temperature, and increased fat oxidation, indicating fewer negative health consequences compared with after nighttime exposure to LEDs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to light with less blue before sleep is better for energy metabolism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210709104232.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210709104232.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T14:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that exposure to specific types of light before sleep can have variable effects on energy metabolism during sleep. Specifically, participants who went to sleep after exposure to organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs), which emit polychromatic white light that contains less blue light than light-emitting diodes (LEDs), exhibited significantly decreased energy expenditure, core body temperature, and increased fat oxidation, indicating fewer negative health consequences compared with after nighttime exposure to LEDs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists show how light therapy treats depression in mice model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708143918.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708143918.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Light therapy can help improve the mood of people with seasonal affective disorder (SAD) during short winter days, but exactly how this therapy works is not well understood. A new study finds that light therapy's beneficial effects come from activating the circadian clock gene Period1 in a part of the brain involved in mood and sleep-wake cycles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An antioxidative stress regulator protects muscle tissue in space, mouse study shows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708111457.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708111457.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that nuclear factor E2-related factor 2, a master regulator of the oxidative stress response, affects muscle composition in microgravity. Targeting this protein could help protect against muscle changes during space flight, and could also have implications for muscle wasting in conditions such as cancer and aging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EHR alerts go unread, do not lead to deprescribing of medicines linked to dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708083913.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708083913.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of electronic health record (EHR) alerts attempting to reduce prescribing of high-risk medications linked to dementia in older adults went unread in a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tooth loss associated with increased cognitive impairment, dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708083904.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210708083904.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooth loss is a risk factor for cognitive impairment and dementia -- and with each tooth lost, the risk of cognitive decline grows, according to a new analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could ketogenic diet be helpful with brain cancer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707160516.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707160516.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modified ketogenic diet may be worth exploring for people with brain tumors, according to a new study. The small study found that the diet was safe and feasible for people with brain tumors called astrocytomas. The study was not designed to determine whether the diet could slow down tumor growth or improve survival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When taste and healthfulness compete, taste has a hidden advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707160504.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707160504.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You dash into a convenience store for a quick snack, spot an apple and reach for a candy bar instead. Poor self-control may not be the only factor behind your choice, new research suggests. That's because our brains process taste information first, before factoring in health information, according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Updates to secrets configuration options in App Service and Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-updates-to-secrets-configuration-options-in-app-service-and-azure-functions</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-updates-to-secrets-configuration-options-in-app-service-and-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[App Service and Azure Functions have been updated to better support management of secrets as part of your secure application development process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impulsiveness tied to faster eating in children, can lead to obesity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707140721.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707140721.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The research sought to uncover the relationship between temperament and eating behaviors in early childhood. The findings are critical because faster eating and greater responsiveness to food cues have been linked to obesity risk in children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-androgen therapy can fuel spread of bone tumors in advanced prostate cancer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707112445.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210707112445.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-androgen therapy is commonly used to treat patients with advanced prostate cancer at stages where the disease has spread to the bones. However, new research has found that anti-androgen treatment can actually facilitate prostate cancer cells to adapt and grow in the bone tumor microenvironment model developed by biomedical scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Men's Health News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab analysis finds near-meat and meat not nutritionally equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210706153026.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210706153026.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research team's deeper examination of the nutritional content of plant-based meat alternatives, using metabolomics, shows they're as different as plants and animals. Beef contained 22 metabolites that the plant substitute did not. The plant-based substitute contained 31 metabolites that meat did not. The greatest distinctions occurred in amino acids, dipeptides, vitamins, phenols, and types of saturated and unsaturated fatty acids found in these products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New study uncovers how a series of sleep loss impacts mental and physical wellbeing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210706133113.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210706133113.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T17:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study looked at the consequences of sleeping fewer than six hours for eight consecutive nights -- the minimum duration of sleep that experts say is necessary to support optimal health in average adults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psychedelic spurs growth of neural connections lost in depression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210705113923.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210705113923.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T15:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers show that a single dose of psilocybin given to mice prompted an immediate and long-lasting increase in connections between neurons. The findings are published July 5 in the journal Neuron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spirituality News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More filling? Tastes great? How flies, and maybe people, choose their food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210705094725.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210705094725.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T13:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flies have discriminating taste. Like a gourmet perusing a menu, they spend much of their time seeking sweet nutritious calories and avoiding bitter, potentially toxic food. But what happens in their brains when they make these food choices? Researchers discovered an interesting way to find out. They tricked them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brain circuit for spirituality?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701195245.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701195245.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T23:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using datasets from neurosurgical patients and those with brain lesions, researchers mapped lesion locations associated with spiritual and religious belief to a specific human brain circuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spirituality News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long can a person live? The 21st century may see a record-breaker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701150951.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701150951.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T19:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study calculates the probability of living past age 110, which, though rare, likely will increase this century.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The sense of smell in older adults declines when it comes to meat, but not vanilla, researchers find]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701112621.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/07/210701112621.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T15:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what science once suggested, older people with a declining sense of smell do not have comprehensively dampened olfactory ability for odors in general -- it simply depends upon the type of odor. Researchers reached this conclusion after examining a large group of older Danes' and their intensity perception of common food odors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consuming a diet with more fish fats, less vegetable oils can reduce migraine headaches, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630213035.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630213035.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T01:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A diet higher in fatty fish helped frequent migraine sufferers reduce their monthly number of headaches and intensity of pain compared to participants on a diet higher in vegetable-based fats and oils, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep your friends close, cortisol levels low for life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630173629.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630173629.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T21:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interdisciplinary team has determined that older adult women converse more effectively with strangers than their younger counterparts; additionally, communicating with female friends decreases stress hormone levels for women across the lifespan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5-minute breathing workout lowers blood pressure as much as exercise, drugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630135033.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630135033.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T17:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that a breathing exercise known as Inspiratory Muscle Strength Training can reduce blood pressure in weeks, with benefits on par with daily exercise or medication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers look to human 'social sensors' to better predict elections and other trends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115436.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115436.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers can gather highly accurate information about social trends and groups by asking about a person's social circle rather than interrogating their own individual beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eating disorder behaviors alter reward response in brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115345.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115345.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study found that eating disorder behaviors alter the brain's reward response process and food intake control circuitry, which can reinforce the behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Southern diet - fried foods and sugary drinks - may raise risk of sudden cardiac death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630091407.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630091407.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T13:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participants in a large-scale study who more commonly consumed a Southern-style diet - high in added fats, fried foods, processed meats and sugary drinks - had a higher risk of sudden cardiac death than people who had lower adherence to a Southern-style diet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High physical activity levels may counter serious health harms of poor sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191745.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191745.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T23:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physical activity levels at or above the weekly recommended amounts may counter the serious health harms associated with poor sleep quality, suggests a large long term study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A promising new pathway to treating type 2 diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191737.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191737.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T23:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers believe the liver may hold the key to new, preventative Type 2 diabetes treatments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success in reversing dementia in mice sets the stage for human clinical trials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629120756.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629120756.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a new treatment candidate that appears to not only halt neurodegenerative symptoms in mouse models of dementia and Alzheimer's disease, but also reverse the effects of the disorders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers question prevailing Alzheimer's theory with new discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170605.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170605.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts estimate more than 6 million Americans are living with Alzheimer's dementia. But a recent study sheds new light on the disease and a highly debated new drug therapy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GluN3A knockout mouse: Alternative model for Alzheimer's neurodegeneration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170459.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170459.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GluN3A-deficient mice display all aspects of Alzheimer's neurodegeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love: How the feeling of power determines happy relationships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628132145.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628132145.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T17:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to have a happy relationship? Make sure both partners feel they can decide on issues that are important to them. Objective power measured by income, for example, doesn't seem to play a big role, according to a new study. Instead, how lovers perceive power dynamics in their relationship is most important for relationship satisfaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists develop simple blood test for early detection of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628124947.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628124947.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T16:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An international research team has developed a simple but robust blood test from Chinese patient data for early detection and screening of Alzheimer's disease (AD) with an accuracy level of over 96%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having the same nurse for home health visits may prevent rehospitalization for people with dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210625120428.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210625120428.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T16:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People with dementia receiving home health care visits are less likely to be readmitted to the hospital when there is consistency in nursing staff, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early findings of Alzheimer's study in diverse populations now available to researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624200440.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624200440.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A growing trove of data to help scientists understand the biology of Alzheimer's disease among diverse populations within the context of sociocultural, behavioral and environmental factors is now available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find health benefits of Connecticut-grown sugar kelp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624152650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624152650.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have reported significant findings supporting the nutritional benefits of Connecticut-grown sugar kelp. They found brown sugar kelp (Saccharina latissima) inhibits hepatic inflammation and fibrosis in a mouse model of diet-induced non-alcoholic steatohepatitis, a fatty liver disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serving larger portions of veggies may increase young kids' veggie consumption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624135551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624135551.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be difficult to get young kids to eat enough vegetables, but a new study found that simply adding more veggies to their plates resulted in children consuming more vegetables at the meal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potato and rice protein shakes may be a viable vegan alternative to whey protein shakes, research suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114501.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114501.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study found that plant-based protein shakes may be potential viable alternatives to milk-based whey protein shakes, particularly in people with need of careful monitoring of glucose levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting the day off with chocolate could have unexpected benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study of postmenopausal women has found that eating a concentrated amount of chocolate during a narrow window of time in the morning may help the body burn fat and decrease blood sugar levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting the day off with chocolate could have unexpected benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study of postmenopausal women has found that eating a concentrated amount of chocolate during a narrow window of time in the morning may help the body burn fat and decrease blood sugar levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists may need to rethink which genes control aging, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114334.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114334.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers fed fruit flies antibiotics and monitored the lifetime activity of hundreds of genes that scientists have traditionally thought control aging. To their surprise, the antibiotics not only extended the lives of the flies but also dramatically changed the activity of many of these genes. Their results suggested that only about 30% of the genes traditionally associated with aging set an animal's internal clock while the rest reflect the body's response to bacteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-invasive potential treatment for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114329.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114329.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultrasound can overcome some of the detrimental effects of ageing and dementia without the need to cross the blood-brain barrier, researchers have found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melatonin in mice: there's more to this hormone than sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141703.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141703.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have created a mouse model that allows the study of naturally occurring melatonin. Experiments using the new mice showed that natural melatonin was linked to a pre-hibernation state that allows mice to slow down their metabolism and survive when food is scarce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Multi-kingdom dialogue' between internal, external microbiota]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141700.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141700.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have identified an internal communication network in mammals that may regulate tissue repair and inflammation, providing new insights on how diseases such as obesity and inflammatory skin disorders develop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dieting and its effect on the gut microbiome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141657.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141657.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers were able to show for the first time that a very low calorie diet significantly alters the composition of the microbiota present in the human gut. The researchers report that dieting results in an increase of specific bacteria - notably Clostridioides difficile, which is associated with antibiotic-induced diarrhea and colitis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western high-fat diet can cause chronic pain, according to new study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141644.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141644.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A typical Western high-fat diet can increase the risk of painful disorders common in people with conditions such as diabetes or obesity, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein linked to heart health, disease a potential therapeutic target for dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623095247.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623095247.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that high levels of a normal protein associated with reduced heart disease also protect against Alzheimer's-like damage in mice, opening up new approaches to slowing or stopping brain damage and cognitive decline in people with Alzheimer's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An unexpected discovery: Inflammatory proteins may slow cognitive decline in aging adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091307.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091307.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new study researchers report that elevated levels of two chemical mediators of inflammation, known as cytokines, are associated with slower cognitive decline in aging adults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starchy snacks may increase CVD risk; fruits and veggies at certain meals decreases risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091210.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091210.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eating fruits with lunch, vegetables at dinner and a dairy snack in the evening was associated with a reduced risk of early death by cardiovascular disease (CVD) and all-cause mortality, according to a study of U.S. adults. Eating a Western lunch (typically containing a high quantity of refined grains, cheese and cured meat) was associated with an elevated risk of CVD and all-cause mortalities in the same study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recycling of the eye's light sensors is faulty in progressive blindness of older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091145.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091145.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the National Eye Institute reporting that about 11 million older adults in the U.S. endure a condition that leads to progressive blindness, known as age-related macular degeneration, researchers are starting to understand what goes wrong in the disease, in order to develop new therapies to treat it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subconscious changes in movement may predict Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research team found that FMAR was associated with preclinical AD pathology in women, suggesting that FMAR may be a new biomarker for AD before cognitive symptoms begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subconscious changes in movement may predict Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research team found that FMAR was associated with preclinical AD pathology in women, suggesting that FMAR may be a new biomarker for AD before cognitive symptoms begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rap1 controls the body's sugar levels from the brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a mechanism in a small area of the brain that regulates whole-body glucose balance without affecting body weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rap1 controls the body's sugar levels from the brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a mechanism in a small area of the brain that regulates whole-body glucose balance without affecting body weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from Western diet to a balanced diet may reduce skin, joint inflammation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622161046.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622161046.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diet rich in sugar and fat leads to disruption in the gut's microbial culture and contributes to inflammatory skin diseases such as psoriasis. Research shows that switching to a more balanced diet restores the gut's health and suppresses inflammation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's true: Stress does turn hair gray (and it's reversible)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622154339.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622154339.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T19:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study offers quantitative evidence linking psychological stress to graying hair in people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personality traits relate to being a morning or evening person]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123338.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123338.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The link between the different hierarchies of personality, sleep patterns and even genetics has now been discovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secretin hormone induces satiation by activating brown fat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new mechanism controlling satiation. According to the recently published study, the hormone secretin induces satiation by activating brown adipose tissue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secretin hormone induces satiation by activating brown fat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new mechanism controlling satiation. According to the recently published study, the hormone secretin induces satiation by activating brown adipose tissue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running to music combats mental fatigue, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123235.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123235.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Listening to music while running might be the key to improving people's performance when they feel mentally fatigued a study suggests. The performance of runners who listened to a self-selected playlist after completing a demanding thinking task was at the same level as when they were not mentally fatigued, the research found. The study is the first to investigate the effect of listening to music playlists on endurance running capacity and performance when mentally fatigued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New position statement declares that sleep is essential to health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621174109.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621174109.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:41:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new position statement emphasizes that sleep is a biological necessity, and insufficient sleep and untreated sleep disorders are detrimental for health, well-being, and public safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to pollutants, increased free-radical damage speeds up aging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621160520.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621160520.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T20:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study suggests that unrepaired DNA damage can increase the speed of aging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Managed HSM is generally available]]></title>
        <id>akv-managed-hsm-ga</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/akv-managed-hsm-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Managed HSM (hardware security module) is now generally available. Managed HSM offers a fully managed, highly available, single-tenant, high-throughput, standards-compliant cloud service to safeguard cryptographic keys for your cloud applications, using FIPS 140-2 Level 3 validated HSMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer catch-up programs need to focus on teens' wellbeing, not just academic progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123730.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123730.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer holiday school catch-up programs to address gaps in knowledge after school closures need to support children who are still struggling due to social isolation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study suggests blood test could guide precision treatment in bladder cancer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123721.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123721.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blood test that can detect tiny amounts of circulating cancer DNA may be able to identify risk of cancer recurrence and guide precision treatment in bladder cancer following surgery, according to a clinical study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How childhood exercise could maintain and promote cognitive function in later life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618134038.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618134038.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T17:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who are physically active during childhood have higher cognitive functions in later life. Participants who exercised when they were children did better on cognitive tests regardless of their current age. However, no such relationship was found between task performance and post-childhood exercise -- suggesting that exercise during childhood is particularly important for brain development and long-term cognitive health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tug-of-war receptors for sour taste in fruit flies sheds light on human taste biology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618091654.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618091654.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sour taste does not have the nearly universal appeal that sweet taste does. Slightly sour foods or drinks such as yogurt and lemon juice are yummy to many, but such highly sour foods as spoiled milk are yucky, even dangerous. Like humans, many other animals, including insects, prefer slightly acidic over very acidic foods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>