<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2021-12-04T14:08:07.872Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring Azure Static Web Apps CI/CD Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/refactoring-azure-static-web-apps-ci-cd-pipeline/ba-p/3021090</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/refactoring-azure-static-web-apps-ci-cd-pipeline/ba-p/3021090"/>
        <updated>2021-12-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I wrote a blog post about Azure DevOps Pipelines refactoring technics. GitHub Actions is also suitable for building CI/CD pipelines. But, compared to Azure DevOps, there are many spaces to achieve the same efficiency level as Azure DevOps. GitHub Actions has recently released a new feature called "Reusable Workflows", which you can reduce the refactoring concerns. Throughout this post, I'm going to refactor the existing Azure Static Web Apps CI/CD pipeline workflows, using the "reusable workflows" feature of GitHub Actions.
 
Workflow for Azure Static Web Apps
 
While provisioning an Azure Static Web Apps (ASWA) instance, GitHub Actions workflow is automatically generated by default. Here's a sample workflow. I'm pretty sure it's not that different from yours.
 
### original w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinyoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daytime meals may reduce health risks linked to night shift work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211203151433.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211203151433.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T20:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small clinical trial has found that eating during the nighttime -- like many shift workers do -- can increase glucose levels, while eating only during the daytime might prevent the higher glucose levels now linked with a nocturnal work life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevated heart rate linked to increased risk of dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211203081519.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211203081519.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T13:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having an elevated resting heart rate in old age may be an independent risk factor of dementia, according to a new study. Since resting heart rate is easy to measure and can be lowered through exercise or medical treatment, the researchers believe that it may help to identify people with higher dementia risk for early intervention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typeform is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-tyepform-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-typeform-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T01:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyepform is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Damaged telomeres in the elderly may increase susceptibility to SARS-CoV-2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202191141.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202191141.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T00:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DNA damage signaling induced by aging telomeres increases the expression of ACE2, the human SARS-CoV-2 cell receptor, scientists report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genes associated with hearing loss visualized in new study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202141512.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202141512.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T19:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have been able to document and visualize hearing loss-associated genes in the human inner ear, in a unique collaboration study between otosurgeons and geneticists. The findings illustrate that discrete subcellular structures in the human organ of hearing, the cochlea, are involved in the variation of risk of age-related hearing loss in the population.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the cause of UTI-induced delirium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202141507.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211202141507.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T19:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that blocking the action of a protein called interleukin 6 (IL-6), part of the immune system, could resolve the delirium that often accompanies urinary tract infection (UTI) in elderly patients. Their study could pave the way for clinical trials of IL-6 inhibitors as a treatment for UTI-associated delirium in humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces now have a configurable idle timeout]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-codespaces-now-have-a-configurable-idle-timeout</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-codespaces-now-have-a-configurable-idle-timeout"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces now have a configurable idle timeout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new GitHub Issues – 12/02 update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-the-new-github-issues-12-02-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-02-the-new-github-issues-12-02-update"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new GitHub Issues - 12/02 update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Report: How developers migrate Spring apps to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/2021-report-how-developers-migrate-spring-apps-to-the-cloud/ba-p/3021421</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/2021-report-how-developers-migrate-spring-apps-to-the-cloud/ba-p/3021421"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by The State of Spring 2021 and 2020 reports, we reached out to Spring developers to learn how they are migrating Spring Boot apps to the cloud.
 
In this first report, you will learn about:
 

Platforms targeted for Spring Boot app deployments
Challenges with Spring Boot app migration to the cloud
Top monitoring tools and Spring Cloud components used today.

 
We plan to make this an annual survey that serves as a key source of feedback for Spring teams in Microsoft, VMware, and many other communities. Thank you to everyone who participated!
 
Demographics
 
Our 2021 survey reached a total of 260 qualified individuals attending SpringOne 2021. A wide range of roles, regions, and job levels are represented. Based on the demographics of the event, we estimate 55% of respondents wer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asir_Selvasingh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel immune cell population may trigger inflammation in multiple sclerosis and other brain disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201203919.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201203919.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T01:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of immune cells that normally protect against inflammation in the gastrointestinal tract may have the opposite effect in multiple sclerosis (MS) and other brain inflammation-related conditions, according to a new study. The results suggest that countering the activity of these cells could be a new therapeutic approach for such conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['My robot is a softie': Physical texture influences judgments of robot personality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201203909.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201203909.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T01:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that the physical texture of robots influenced perceptions of robot personality. Furthermore, first impressions of robots, based on physical appearance alone, could influence the relationship between physical texture and robot personality formation. This work could facilitate the development of robots with perceived personalities that match user expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces can install dotfiles from any repo]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-codespaces-can-install-dotfiles-from-any-repo</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-codespaces-can-install-dotfiles-from-any-repo"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T23:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codespaces can install dotfiles from any repo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Targeting the brain’s immune cells may help prevent or treat Alzheimer’s disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201145309.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201145309.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T19:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A gene mutation linked to Alzheimer's disease alters a signaling pathway in certain immune cells of individuals with the disease, according to a new study. The team also found that blocking the pathway -- with a drug that's currently being tested in cancer clinical trials -- protects against many features of the condition in a preclinical model. The results could lead to new strategies to block the development of Alzheimer's disease or slow its progression.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research reveals new evidence that sugary beverage tax impacts are sustainable, effective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201145301.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201145301.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T19:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two new studies based in Seattle provide evidence that public policies to reduce consumption of added sugars through taxes on sugar-sweetened beverages are effective and sustainable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning REST API now surfaces locations]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-secret-scanning-rest-api-now-surfaces-locations</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-secret-scanning-rest-api-now-surfaces-locations"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning REST API now surfaces locations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unorthodox 'exercise in a pill' could offer simple solution for at-risk patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201111956.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201111956.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unique molecular signals in the body sent to our brain and potentially our eyes immediately after we exercise could be key to helping scientists 'bottle up' the benefits of exercise in a pill for at-risk patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unorthodox 'exercise in a pill' could offer simple solution for at-risk patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201111956.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/12/211201111956.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unique molecular signals in the body sent to our brain and potentially our eyes immediately after we exercise could be key to helping scientists 'bottle up' the benefits of exercise in a pill for at-risk patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensure required status checks provided by the intended app]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-ensure-required-status-checks-provided-by-the-intended-app</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-12-01-ensure-required-status-checks-provided-by-the-intended-app"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T14:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensure required status checks provided by the intended app"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2021/12/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2021/12/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from Konstanz!

I’m spending a week in Germany. So far, I’ve visited the one and only Zeppelin Museum and a castle. Technically I’ve been trying to make this an unplugged vacation, so this will be short.
The traditional economic theory of the time suggested that, because the market is “efficient” (that is, those who are best at providing each good or service most cheaply are already doing so), it should always be cheaper to contract out than to hire.
Coase noted, however, that there are a number of transaction costs to using the market; the cost of obtaining a good or service via the market is actually more than just the price of the good. Other costs, including search and information costs, bargaining costs, keeping trade secrets, and policing and enforcement costs, can all potentia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team sync for Okta is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-team-sync-for-okta-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-team-sync-for-okta-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T22:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team sync for Okta is now generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Azure Kubernetes Service with Grafana and Prometheus]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-kubernetes-service-with-grafana-and-prometheus/ba-p/3020459</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-azure-kubernetes-service-with-grafana-and-prometheus/ba-p/3020459"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T21:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Lucas Santos and Aaron Wislang
 
Kubernetes has become a platform of choice for building cloud native applications. Kubernetes is highly scalable, highly available, and easy to use, and has many other advantages that make it an excellent choice for building distributed applications.
 
However, its distributed nature means monitoring everything that is happening within the cluster can be a challenge. Prometheus and Grafana make our experience better.
 
In this article, we will set up a Kubernetes cluster using Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) and deploy Prometheus and Grafana to gather monitoring data and visualize them.
 
Understand the tooling
 
Prometheus is an open source project that was originally created at SoundCloud in 2012, and contributed to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aaron-w</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Workflows triggered by Dependabot receive dependabot secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-github-actions-workflows-triggered-by-dependabot-receive-dependabot-secrets</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-github-actions-workflows-triggered-by-dependabot-receive-dependabot-secrets"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T19:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Workflows triggered by Dependabot receive dependabot secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubiquitous food additive alters human microbiota and intestinal environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130130223.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130130223.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T18:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New clinical research indicates that a widely used food additive, carboxymethylcellulose, alters the intestinal environment of healthy persons, perturbing levels of beneficial bacteria and nutrients. These findings demonstrate the need for further study of the long-term impacts of this food additive on health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignite 2021 - The do not miss list for app developers]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ignite-2021-the-do-not-miss-list-for-app-developers/ba-p/2955457</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ignite-2021-the-do-not-miss-list-for-app-developers/ba-p/2955457"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Ignite 2021 took place online November 2-5. This fall edition was full of dev news, and if you don’t want to miss anything related to App development and innovation, keep reading! 
 
Session Highlights 
 
What does it take to build the next innovative app?
 
During the Digital and App Innovation Into Focus session, Ashmi Chokshi and Developer and IT guests Amanda Silver, Donovan Brown and Rick Claus discussed processes and strategies to help deliver innovative capabilities faster.
 
Developers are driving innovation everywhere, and Ashmi started the conversation strong sharing how she sees the opportunity to drive impact. Then, Donovan presented his definition of cloud native, the benefits of a microservices architecture, and engaged in a discussion with Rick around DevOps and Ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IngridBabel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure email notifications for new deploy keys]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-configure-email-notifications-for-new-deploy-keys</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-30-configure-email-notifications-for-new-deploy-keys"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure email notifications for new deploy keys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduced meat diet has many advantages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101449.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101449.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which diet is better: moderately reduce meat consumption and eat more fruit, vegetables and wholegrain products or eating more fish and seafood? Or even switch completely to a vegan diet? A new study shows that the answer to these questions is not as clear-cut as one might think -- depending on which impacts one closely looks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Courting success: Why the 'head' outsmarts the body in basketball]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101425.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study reveals why coaches believe 'game intelligence,' work ethic and competitiveness are far more important than physical fitness in determining success on the basketball court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential new treatment for Alzheimer’s disease would be relatively cheap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101245.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130101245.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a protein involved in the development of Alzheimer's disease. Studies in mice showed that eliminating this protein entirely or using drugs to block its function reduced physical changes in the brain associated with the disease and improved memory. Drug therapy that aims to block the protein's activity could be a more effective treatment than what is currently available, as well as being cheaper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early interventions could help counteract muscle loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130084334.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130084334.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T13:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weakening muscles are a natural part of the aging process, but for some people with a condition called sarcopenia the decline is abnormally fast. A new study suggests that the early stages of sarcopenia could be counteracted with timely interventions designed to preserve physical and cognitive function and manage chronic conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers model circadian clock neurons in a day-active animal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130084206.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211130084206.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T13:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's no secret that jet lag and night-shift work can wreak havoc on the way our body's internal clock syncs up our daily wake-sleep cycle, known as circadian rhythm, but now researchers say they are a step closer to understanding how the brain creates behavioral rhythms optimized for diurnal, rather than nocturnal, life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rates of type 2 diabetes are higher in people with one of various common psychiatric disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129212806.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129212806.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T02:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds that the prevalence of type 2 diabetes (T2D) is elevated in people with a psychiatric disorder compared with the general population.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rates of type 2 diabetes are higher in people with one of various common psychiatric disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129212806.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129212806.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T02:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds that the prevalence of type 2 diabetes (T2D) is elevated in people with a psychiatric disorder compared with the general population.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth-delivered diet and exercise program eased knee pain and triggered weight loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129172742.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129172742.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combined diet and exercise Telehealth program saw 80 per cent of participants experience reduced knee pain with an average weight loss of approximately 10.2 per cent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telehealth-delivered diet and exercise program eased knee pain and triggered weight loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129172742.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129172742.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Combined diet and exercise Telehealth program saw 80 per cent of participants experience reduced knee pain with an average weight loss of approximately 10.2 per cent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De-cluttering may not help people with dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129155049.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129155049.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T20:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clutter-free environment may not help people with dementia carry out daily tasks -- according to a new study. Researchers studied whether people with dementia were better able to carry out tasks, such as making a cup of tea, at home - surrounded by their usual clutter - or in a clutter-free environment. They were surprised to find that participants with moderate dementia performed better when surrounded by their usual clutter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID long-haulers may experience abnormal breathing patterns, chronic fatigue syndrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129155037.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129155037.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T20:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many long-haul COVID-19 patients have chronic fatigue syndrome and other breathing issues months after their initial COVID-19 diagnosis, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How obesity damages the skeletal muscle metabolism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122835.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122835.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decline in metabolism and endurance of skeletal muscle is commonly observed in obese patients, but the underlying mechanism is not well-understood. A research team uncovers a new mechanism to explain how obesity jeopardizes the functions of skeletal muscle and provides a potential treatment against the disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How obesity damages the skeletal muscle metabolism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122835.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122835.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decline in metabolism and endurance of skeletal muscle is commonly observed in obese patients, but the underlying mechanism is not well-understood. A research team uncovers a new mechanism to explain how obesity jeopardizes the functions of skeletal muscle and provides a potential treatment against the disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sick and tired: Research reveals toll of poor sleep among health care workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122824.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122824.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New studies quantify the effect of the COVID pandemic on health care workers' sleep patterns and the potential damaging consequences of sleep disturbance on their mental health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sick and tired: Research reveals toll of poor sleep among health care workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122824.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129122824.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New studies quantify the effect of the COVID pandemic on health care workers' sleep patterns and the potential damaging consequences of sleep disturbance on their mental health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists discover potential cause of Alzheimer’s Disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105654.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105654.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T15:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In people with brain buildups, a key but difficult-to-detect difference in the form of tau protein allows scientists to distinguish people showing no outward signs of dementia from those who do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spicy breast milk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105546.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105546.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T15:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part of a recent human study led by the Technical University of Munich (TUM), it was found that after eating a curry dish containing pepper, piperine - an alkaloid responsible for the pungency of pepper - was present in the milk of breastfeeding women. The findings help decipher mechanisms that shape our food preferences from infancy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statin use affects prostate cancer screening results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105542.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211129105542.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T15:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prostate cancer screening results differ in men taking cholesterol-lowering statin drugs compared with non-users, a study finds. In statin users, screening did not increase the incidence of prostate cancer as it did in other men.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Men's Health News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web App Down caused by allowSubDirConfig]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/web-app-down-caused-by-allowsubdirconfig/ba-p/2968143</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/web-app-down-caused-by-allowsubdirconfig/ba-p/2968143"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T08:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Symptom:
 
The issue came up after the web app has been running for a while (several days), the response time of the site slowly increased. And in the end, the requests failed with timeout.
After we reviewed the memory dump and found out that the issue caused by the sites has many unique URLs requests, please refer to the section below.
 
Cause:
 

The Asp.net application can have a web.config files in each folder, it can help to set the specific configuration for that directory. You can find more details here. 
IIS caches the web.config into the machine memory, this can automatically optimize our code by avoiding unnecessary file IO and XML parsing.
To process a request, IIS parses the request URL into directory and looks for the file client requested. Such as the request https://gsm.azur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Selina_Sun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API support for managing labels of Actions self-hosted runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-25-api-support-for-managing-labels-of-actions-self-hosted-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-25-api-support-for-managing-labels-of-actions-self-hosted-runners"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T11:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API support for managing labels of Actions self-hosted runners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study finds brain lesions on MRI linked to years of playing football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124172157.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124172157.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certain markers of injury to the brain's white matter, called white matter hyperintensities, can be seen on brain scans. A new study finds that brain scans taken during the lifetimes of athletes in contact sports, compared to changes in their brains at autopsy, showed that white matter hyperintensities were associated with neuropathological changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the hidden cellular logistics of memory storage in neurons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124172155.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124172155.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the mechanisms involved in sleep-dependent memory storage, a team of cellular biologists found that RNAs associated with an understudied cell compartment in hippocampal neurons vary greatly between sleeping and sleep-deprived mice after learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only alcohol -- not caffeine, diet or lack of sleep -- might trigger heart rhythm condition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124154126.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124154126.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research that tested possible triggers of a common heart condition, including caffeine, sleep deprivation and sleeping on the left side, found that only alcohol use was consistently associated with more episodes of the heart arrhythmia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treating insomnia with cognitive behavioral therapy can prevent major depression in older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124153912.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124153912.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has found that cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT-I) prevented major depression, decreasing the likelihood of depression by over 50% as compared to sleep education therapy in adults over the age of 60 with insomnia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treating insomnia with cognitive behavioral therapy can prevent major depression in older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124153912.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211124153912.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has found that cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT-I) prevented major depression, decreasing the likelihood of depression by over 50% as compared to sleep education therapy in adults over the age of 60 with insomnia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Reusable workflows are generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-github-actions-reusable-workflows-are-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-github-actions-reusable-workflows-are-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T19:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Reusable workflows are generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Specify theme context for images in Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-specify-theme-context-for-images-in-markdown</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-specify-theme-context-for-images-in-markdown"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T17:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Specify theme context for images in Markdown]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL code scanning now recognizes more Python libraries and frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-codeql-code-scanning-now-recognizes-more-python-libraries-and-frameworks</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-24-codeql-code-scanning-now-recognizes-more-python-libraries-and-frameworks"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T17:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL code scanning now recognizes more Python libraries and frameworks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: setup-python now supports dependency caching]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-github-actions-setup-python-now-supports-dependency-caching</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-github-actions-setup-python-now-supports-dependency-caching"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T03:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: setup-python now supports dependency caching]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How eating less in early life could help with reproduction later on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123200926.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123200926.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T01:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research shows how switching from a restricted diet to eating as much as you like could be beneficial for reproduction in later life. Researchers studied the eating and mating habits of the small fruit fly Drosophila melanogaster. They found that those that switched from a restricted diet to unlimited food, started mating and reproducing more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Light high contrast theme beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-light-high-contrast-theme-beta"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A light high contrast theme, with greater contrast between foreground and background elements, is now available to all github.com users in a public beta. Navigate to the “Appearance” page in your profile settings to choose the light]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability of custom OpenID providers in App Service and Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-of-custom-openid-providers-in-app-service-and-azure-functions</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-of-custom-openid-providers-in-app-service-and-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T21:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for authenticating clients of App Service and Azure Functions using OpenID Connect is now generally available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research sheds new light on effects of dietary restriction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123162652.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123162652.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T21:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research in the tiny nematode worm, C. elegans, has revealed that muscle may be a protected tissue under conditions of dietary restriction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Secure cloud deployments with OpenID Connect is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-secure-cloud-deployments-with-oidc-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T20:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenID Connect (OIDC) support for secure cloud deployments with GitHub Actions is now generally available.You can configure your workflows to request short-lived access tokens that are automatically rotated for each deployment. Learn more about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becca Crockett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latte lovers rejoice! Study reveals drinking coffee could lower the risk of Alzheimer’s disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123131427.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123131427.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T18:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news for those of us who can't face the day without their morning flat white: a long-term study has revealed drinking higher amounts of coffee may make you less likely to develop Alzheimer's disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the relationship between diet, intestinal bacteria and cells key to preventing systemic inflammation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123131409.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211123131409.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T18:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mice fed a diet high in fat, cholesterol and calories, akin to the Western diet, had higher measures of blood lipids associated with elevated levels of inflammation, a new study finds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions - Fall update]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-fall-update/ba-p/2978096</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-fall-update/ba-p/2978096"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions – Fall 2021 update
With Ignite and .NET Conf completed, the team wanted to give an update on the latest releases in Azure Functions to enable customers to build event driven serverless applications. The team has been extremely busy working with customers over the last few months to invest in the developer's experience in Functions as well as platform improvements.
The following capabilities are now generally available for all Functions customers.
 
General availability announcements
 
Azure Functions runtime 4.0
Azure Functions runtime 4.0 is now generally available, supporting the following language/runtime versions: 

.NET 6.0 (in-process and isolated process) 
Node.js 14, 16 (preview)
Python 3.7, 3.8, 3.9 
Java 8, 11 
PowerShell 7.0 
Custom handlers 

You can learn more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamon O'Reilly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom footers on GitHub Enterprise Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-custom-footers-on-github-enterprise-cloud"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers on GitHub Enterprise Cloud can now add custom footers to show additional links to enterprise members and collaborators. For more info, see our docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push notifications for pull request review activities on GitHub Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-push-notifications-for-pull-request-review-activities-on-github-mobile"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Mobile now supports push notifications for pull request review activities – you will get notified when someone approves, comments, or requests changes on your pull requests. GitHub Mobile also support push notifications when you’re]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements to the @mention suggester]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-improvements-to-the-mention-suggester"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The @mention suggester now ranks participants in Issues, Pull Requests, and Discussions higher so that it’s more likely the person you are looking for will be listed first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Display help text for your custom CodeQL queries in code scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-display-help-text-for-your-custom-codeql-queries-in-code-scanning"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release of the CodeQL CLI supports including markdown-rendered query help in SARIF files so that the help text can be viewed in the code scanning UI. This functionality is now available for code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Cache size is now increased to 10GB per repository]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-23-github-actions-cache-size-is-now-increased-to-10gb-per-repository"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now enjoy a higher per-repository cache size. The cache storage for each repository has doubled to 10GB. This enables Actions users on github.com to run workflows faster by caching even bigger dependencies and other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking it easy as you get older? Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122172720.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122172720.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T22:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of evolutionary biologists and biomedical researchers lay out evolutionary and biomedical evidence showing that humans, who evolved to live many decades after they stopped reproducing, also evolved to be relatively active in their later years. The researchers say that physical activity later in life shifts energy away from processes that can compromise health and toward mechanisms in the body that extend it. They hypothesize that humans evolved to remain physically active as they age -- and in doing so to allocate energy to physiological processes that slow the body's gradual deterioration over the years. This guards against chronic illnesses such as cardiovascular disease, type 2 diabetes, and even some cancers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking it easy as you get older? Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122172720.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122172720.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T22:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of evolutionary biologists and biomedical researchers lay out evolutionary and biomedical evidence showing that humans, who evolved to live many decades after they stopped reproducing, also evolved to be relatively active in their later years. The researchers say that physical activity later in life shifts energy away from processes that can compromise health and toward mechanisms in the body that extend it. They hypothesize that humans evolved to remain physically active as they age -- and in doing so to allocate energy to physiological processes that slow the body's gradual deterioration over the years. This guards against chronic illnesses such as cardiovascular disease, type 2 diabetes, and even some cancers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep linked to feeling older and worse outlook on aging, which can impact health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep in the over 50s is linked to more negative perceptions of aging, which in turn can impact physical, mental and cognitive health, new research has revealed. A study found that people who rated their sleep the worst also felt older, and perceived their own physical and mental aging more negatively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep linked to feeling older and worse outlook on aging, which can impact health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep in the over 50s is linked to more negative perceptions of aging, which in turn can impact physical, mental and cognitive health, new research has revealed. A study found that people who rated their sleep the worst also felt older, and perceived their own physical and mental aging more negatively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep linked to feeling older and worse outlook on aging, which can impact health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135512.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poor sleep in the over 50s is linked to more negative perceptions of aging, which in turn can impact physical, mental and cognitive health, new research has revealed. A study found that people who rated their sleep the worst also felt older, and perceived their own physical and mental aging more negatively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthier UK diets linked to lower greenhouse gas emissions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135410.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135410.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new analysis adds to evidence that nutritious diets are often more environmentally sustainable, while also demonstrating the feasibility of evaluating diet sustainability at the scale of specific foods -- rather than broader food-group categories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giving social support to others may boost your health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135407.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135407.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to your health, being willing to give social support to your spouse, friends and family may be just as important as receiving assistance, a new study suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting dysfunctional cells alleviates diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating old, dysfunctional cells in human fat also alleviates signs of diabetes, researchers report. The discovery could lead to new treatments for Type 2 diabetes and other metabolic diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting dysfunctional cells alleviates diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating old, dysfunctional cells in human fat also alleviates signs of diabetes, researchers report. The discovery could lead to new treatments for Type 2 diabetes and other metabolic diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting dysfunctional cells alleviates diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211122135329.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating old, dysfunctional cells in human fat also alleviates signs of diabetes, researchers report. The discovery could lead to new treatments for Type 2 diabetes and other metabolic diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Node.js 16 in Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-nodejs-16-in-azure-functions</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-nodejs-16-in-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js 16.x is the latest Long Term Support (LTS) release of the Node.js runtime and includes features such as a new version of the V8 JavaScript engine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A genetic change for achieving a long and healthy life?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155607.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155607.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T20:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presented new insights for improving the health span by just regulating the activity of a protein. A research group has identified a single amino acid change in the tumor suppressor protein phosphatase and tensin homolog (PTEN) that dramatically extends healthy periods while maintaining longevity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New link between diet, intestinal stem cells and disease discovered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155604.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155604.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T20:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obesity, diabetes and gastrointestinal cancer are frequently linked to an unhealthy diet. However, the molecular mechanisms responsible for this are not fully understood. Researchers have gained some new insights that help to better understand this connection. These findings provide an important basis for the development of non-invasive therapies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urbanization not always bad for food and land use diversity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155512.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119155512.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T20:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Widely accepted myths that urbanization negatively impacts food and land use biodiversity are incorrect, according to a team of researchers who developed a framework for evaluating this intersection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allow bypassing required pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-19-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-19-allow-bypassing-required-pull-requests"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T18:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Administrators can now allow specific users and teams to bypass pull request requirements. For context, this image shows how administrators can use branch protections to require pull requests for all changes to a branch: This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becca Crockett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service Automatic Scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-app-service-automatic-scaling/ba-p/2983300</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-app-service-automatic-scaling/ba-p/2983300"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Services currently provides two workflows for scaling: scale up and scale out.

Scale up: Get more CPU, memory, disk space, and extra features. You scale up by changing the pricing tier of the App Service plan that your app belongs to.
Scale out: Increase the number of VM instances that run your app. You can scale out to as many as 30 instances, depending on your pricing tier. App Service Environments in Isolated tier further increases your scale-out count to 100 instances. You can scale manually or automatically based on predefined rules and schedules.

 
These existing scaling workflows work well, but you may want to instead have the App Service platform automatically scale your web app without the hassle of defining auto-scaling rules & schedules.
 
We are introducing a new pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gauravseth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers use model of hypothalamus to implicate genes associated with sleep, BMI, puberty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119085122.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119085122.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T13:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has implicated several genes involved in a variety of bodily functions associated with the hypothalamus, a notoriously difficult-to-study region of the brain. The findings could help clinicians identify potential causes of dysfunction for many important traits regulated by the hypothalamus, such as sleep, stress, and reproduction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers use model of hypothalamus to implicate genes associated with sleep, BMI, puberty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119085122.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211119085122.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T13:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has implicated several genes involved in a variety of bodily functions associated with the hypothalamus, a notoriously difficult-to-study region of the brain. The findings could help clinicians identify potential causes of dysfunction for many important traits regulated by the hypothalamus, such as sleep, stress, and reproduction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chemotherapy may affect muscle cells at lower doses than previously thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211118203721.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211118203721.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T01:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previous research has found that chemotherapy can trigger muscle loss in people living with cancer, but a new study out of found it may also affect the way the body builds new muscle -- and at lower doses than previously known, having potential implications for treatments and rehab programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do we know we're tired?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211118203657.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211118203657.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T01:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do we need sleep? New research takes a step towards solving this mystery by discovering a mechanism of sleep in zebrafish, with some supporting evidence in mice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In defense of verification]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2021/11/19/verification.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2021/11/19/verification.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In lieu of a follow-up to my last IPFS post, here’s why I’m not writing that post.
When I tested out IPFS and Arweave, what I was doing was partly for fun, partly as exploration, and partly to “kick the tires.” After all, IPFS and Arweave make their own bold claims - Arweave that it “stores documents and applications forever” and IPFS that it can “help here and now” and that it can “speed up performance” and “slash bandwidth costs.”
You don’t have to be cynical to ask “does this thing do what it says it does?” To want to actually install the software and confirm whether it’s a competitive market, an uncompetitive market, or not a market at all. Whether the software actually works out of the box, or if it’s fragile and unfinished.
It’s tempting to do the same for other stuff. In a discussio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new GitHub Issues – 11/18 update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-18-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-18-the-new-github-issues-11-18-update"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T19:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After our GitHub Issues public beta announcement at GitHub Universe, we’ve seen teams start to engage with and adopt project tables, boards and all of our recently released features. Now that we’re in the public beta, we’re]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sidi Merzouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Newrelic monitor Linux PHP App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/use-newrelic-monitor-linux-php-app-service/ba-p/2919269</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/use-newrelic-monitor-linux-php-app-service/ba-p/2919269"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When running your PHP application in Azure Linux App Service, you may encounter availability or performance related issues.PHP New Relic agent is one of the APM tools that can help to provide a better understanding of what may be causing these issues.
This article shows a demonstration of how to use New Relic agent to monitor your PHP application running in Linux App Service.
 
Prerequisites

A New Relic account.
Azure App Service for Linux with built-in PHP docker image.

 
Setup and Enable PHP New Relic agent
 
Create Newrelic API keys
We can get the Newrelic API keys by navigating directly to https://one.newrelic.com/launcher/api-keys-ui.api-keys-launcherCreate "Ingest-License" key:


Copy the new create API key, save it in your local notepad. We will use this key later.
 
Install the P…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hanli_Ren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the brain’s cerebellum, a new target for suppressing hunger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117211610.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117211610.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T02:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have identified an entirely new way the brain signals fullness after eating. The findings offer a novel target for therapies that could dramatically curb overeating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brief 5:2 diet advice is as effective as traditional GP advice, but people like it better, according to new study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161441.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161441.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clinical trial has found people prefer receiving information on the 5:2 diet than standard GP weight management advice despite both interventions achieving similar modest weight loss results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brief 5:2 diet advice is as effective as traditional GP advice, but people like it better, according to new study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161441.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161441.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clinical trial has found people prefer receiving information on the 5:2 diet than standard GP weight management advice despite both interventions achieving similar modest weight loss results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food scientists create zinc index for human body]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161416.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117161416.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zinc deficiency is prevalent around the world, and among children, these mineral shortfalls can lead to stunting, embryonic malformations and neurobehavioral abnormalities. Over several decades, science has improved understanding of zinc metabolism, but an accurate, comprehensive assessment tool for its physiological status within a human body has remained elusive. Until now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Azure SQL bindings for Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-azure-sql-bindings-for-azure-functions</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-azure-sql-bindings-for-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can connect Azure SQL to Azure Functions more easily with input and output bindings, now available in public preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging CodeQL code scanning made easier by retaining diagnostic artifacts in Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-17-debugging-codeql-code-scanning-made-easier-by-retaining-diagnostic-artifacts-in-actions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-17-debugging-codeql-code-scanning-made-easier-by-retaining-diagnostic-artifacts-in-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging CodeQL code scanning made easier by retaining diagnostic artifacts in Actions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arterial stiffness in adolescence may potentially cause hypertension and obesity in young adulthood]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117100058.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117100058.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arterial stiffness is a novel risk factor to be targeted for preventing and treating hypertension and obesity from a young age, a new study suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exercise increases the body’s own ‘cannabis-like' substance which reduces chronic inflammation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117100053.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211117100053.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exercise increases the body's own cannabis-like substances, which in turn helps reduce inflammation and could potentially help treat certain conditions such as arthritis, cancer and heart disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview the Markdown rendering of gists]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-17-preview-the-markdown-rendering-of-gists</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-17-preview-the-markdown-rendering-of-gists"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T11:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preview the Markdown rendering of gists]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Cloud self-service compliance reports for 2021 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-github-enterprise-cloud-self-service-compliance-reports-for-2021-are-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-github-enterprise-cloud-self-service-compliance-reports-for-2021-are-now-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Cloud self-service compliance reports for 2021 are now available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating non-audit-related advisory fetch endpoints for the npmjs.com registry API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-deprecating-non-audit-related-advisory-fetch-endpoints-for-the-npmjs-com-registry-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-deprecating-non-audit-related-advisory-fetch-endpoints-for-the-npmjs-com-registry-api"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T19:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecating non-audit-related advisory fetch endpoints for the npmjs.com registry API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sponsorship Transaction Metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-sponsorship-transaction-metadata</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-sponsorship-transaction-metadata"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sponsorship Transaction Metadata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Azure API Management updates- October 2021]]></title>
        <id>azure-api-management-updates-october-2021</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/azure-api-management-updates-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T17:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure API Management is now available with new updates such as support for managed identity authentication for communication with Application Insights, ability to import Container App as an API and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The newest Docker VS Code extension feature you’re not using]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/the-newest-docker-vs-code-extension-feature-you-re-not-using/ba-p/2941119</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/the-newest-docker-vs-code-extension-feature-you-re-not-using/ba-p/2941119"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Docker usage has grown, Docker Compose has become the leader in running multi-service applications locally. Unfortunately, as your application expands and more services must communicate, we’ve found authoring these Compose files can become arduous, time consuming, and mistake prone. We want to make writing Compose files with volumes, ports, and multiple services much easier. 
 
Today, we’d like to announce the Docker Compose Language Service in the Docker Extension for VS Code. That’s right, the Docker Extension will now provide Docker Compose files with IntelliSense, Tooltips, and syntax validation. Here are a few of the incoming features in our 1.18 release: 
 

IntelliSense tab completions (i.e. volumes, ports)


 

Tooltips for Compose keywords (i.e. services, image) 



Right-click to format a Compose file (Shift + Alt + F) 
YAML Syntax Validation 
Hyperlinks for Docker Images 

In our 1.18 release, this feature will be on by default, so we hope you enjoy it!
 
There are more improvements to come! Stay tuned for these features:

More tab completions
Docker Compose schema validation 
… and much more! 

We love your feedback! If you have any comments or ideas on our Compose language support, feel free to submit an issue to the Compose Language Service Repo or the VS Code Docker Repo for general feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uche_Nkadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The prostate cancer cell that got away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211116111315.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211116111315.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have pioneered a new method to track the progression of prostate cancer in mice, from its birth to its spread into other tissues. This approach allows researchers to study the origins of prostate cancer in a more realistic context than traditional methods allow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Men's Health News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet trumps drugs for anti-aging and good metabolic health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211116103107.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211116103107.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study comparing the impact of diet versus drugs on the inner workings of our cells has found nutrition has a much stronger impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing keyboard shortcuts using accessibility settings]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-managing-keyboard-shortcuts-using-accessibility-settings</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-managing-keyboard-shortcuts-using-accessibility-settings"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing keyboard shortcuts using accessibility settings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Windows Server 2022 with Visual Studio 2022 is now generally available on GitHub-hosted runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-github-actions-windows-server-2022-with-visual-studio-2022-is-now-generally-available-on-github-hosted-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-github-actions-windows-server-2022-with-visual-studio-2022-is-now-generally-available-on-github-hosted-runners"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Windows Server 2022 with Visual Studio 2022 is now generally available on GitHub-hosted runners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right-to-left language support]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-right-to-left-language-support</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-16-right-to-left-language-support"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T13:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-to-left language support]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Service to Storage Account Connection Condition Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-to-storage-account-connection-condition-summary/ba-p/2968642</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-to-storage-account-connection-condition-summary/ba-p/2968642"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T07:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, there are 4 main conditions the Azure App Service can connect to Azure Storage Account. 

Condition 1: App Service (Public ) --> Storage Account (Public, Same region)
Condition 2: App Service (Public ) --> Storage Account (Public, Different region)
Condition 3: App Service (Regional Vnet Integration) --> Storage Account (Private, Service Endpoint )
Condition 4: App Service (Regional Vnet Integration) --> Storage Account (Private, Private Endpoint)

 
Before going deeper, here is a brief summary for your to choose the suitable design for your system.
Requirements:

If your security require the Firewall on the Storage Account. And the Storage Account and Azure App Service are in the same region.

          --> Use the above Condition 3 for 4 for your design.

If your security requ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boqian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can we tell someone’s cultural group from the way they laugh?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115165434.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115165434.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can we infer someone's cultural group from their laugher, even when we do not know what they are laughing at? And what kind of laughter do we find most positive? A new study shows that our laughter gives us away. The study included Dutch and Japanese producers of laughter and listeners. Listeners could detect whether a laughing person is from their own or another cultural group by only hearing a brief laughter segment. Spontaneous laughter was rated as most positive by both groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neurobiologists identify a new gene important for healthy daily rhythms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115151002.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115151002.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team neurobiologists has identified a new gene, called Tango10, that is critical for daily behavioral rhythms. This gene is involved in a molecular pathway by which the core circadian clock (the 'gears') controls the cellular output of the clock (the 'hands') to control daily sleep-wake cycles. While the study was done using the fruit fly Drosophila melanogaster, the findings have implications for humans and clock-related problems and disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neurobiologists identify a new gene important for healthy daily rhythms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115151002.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115151002.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team neurobiologists has identified a new gene, called Tango10, that is critical for daily behavioral rhythms. This gene is involved in a molecular pathway by which the core circadian clock (the 'gears') controls the cellular output of the clock (the 'hands') to control daily sleep-wake cycles. While the study was done using the fruit fly Drosophila melanogaster, the findings have implications for humans and clock-related problems and disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysteries of the aging Down syndrome brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115150719.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115150719.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular changes within the aging brains of individuals with Down syndrome could help explain why these individuals tend to develop Alzheimer's later in life, says new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers discover new insights about tau proteins in people living with ALS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123558.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123558.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investigators found elevated levels of tau and a phosphorylated form of the tau protein in brain tissue from deceased people who had amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) and carried a mutation in the C9orf72 gene. The team also identified new genetic mutations in the tau gene that may exacerbate ALS onset or progression. Tau in the cerebrospinal fluid may be a viable biomarker for ALS because levels correlate with disease progression.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common blood pressure drug does not slow down the progression of more advanced Alzheimer’s, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123531.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123531.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research has shown the drug losartan, normally used to treat high blood pressure (hypertension), is not effective in slowing down the progression of Alzheimer's disease (AD) in people with mild-to-moderate disease after 12 months of treatment. However, the drug could still be of benefit if prescribed for longer and if given to people with very early disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping chocolate milk smooth, stable without carrageenan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123515.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123515.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fat-free chocolate milk processed for the first time with high-pressure jet technology exhibits enhanced viscosity, stabilizing cocoa particles in the fluid and eliminating the need for adding a controversial emulsifier. That's the conclusion of a team of researchers, whose study suggests that the new technology can preclude the use of carrageenan in chocolate milk. The widely used food additive -- which helps keep the liquid smooth and well-mixed even after days sitting on a store shelf -- is not desired by many consumers, especially in organic chocolate milk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreaming of being an investment shark? Better figure out if you’re an ‘owl’ or a ‘lark,’ study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123435.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211115123435.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a night owl looking to invest in the next big startup, making that decision first thing in the morning might not be the best idea, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How surviving cancer as a child affects lifelong health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211114201801.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211114201801.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T01:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The researchers are now calling for these long-term health effects to be considered when young people and their families discuss treatment options with their healthcare team initially. The study found that people who survived cancer had five times as many GP or hospital visits relating to cardiovascular disease by age 45, as a matched control group of people who had not had cancer early in life. They also had much higher numbers of healthcare visits relating to infections, disorders of the immune system, and subsequent cancers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For stem cells, bigger doesn’t mean better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211113072504.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211113072504.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T12:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study suggests that enlargement of stem cells contributes to age-related decline in function. The researchers found that blood stem cells, which are among the smallest cells in the body, lose their ability to perform their normal function -- replenishing the body's blood cells -- as they grow larger. When the cells were restored to their usual size, they behaved normally again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled billing maintenance]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-12-scheduled-billing-maintenance</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-12-scheduled-billing-maintenance"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduled billing maintenance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obesity raises the risk of gum disease by inflating growth of bone-destroying cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211112083106.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211112083106.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T13:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chronic inflammation caused by obesity may trigger the development of cells that break down bone tissue, including the bone that holds teeth in place, according to new research that sought to improve understanding of the connection between obesity and gum disease. The study, completed in an animal model and published in October in the Journal of Dental Research, found that excessive inflammation resulting from obesity raises the number of myeloid-derived suppressor cells (MDSC), a group of immune cells that increase during illness to regulate immune function. MDSCs, which originate in the bone marrow, develop into a range of different cell types, including osteoclasts (a cell that breaks down bone tissue).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moderate amounts of caffeine not linked to maternal health risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111171118.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111171118.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T22:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consuming a low amount of caffeine during pregnancy could help to reduce gestational diabetes risk, according to researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PFAS exposure, high-fat diet drive prostate cells’ metabolism into pro-cancer state]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111154311.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111154311.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A high-fat diet synergizes with exposure to PFAS to change the metabolism of benign and malignant prostate cells, according to a new study in mice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gut microbiota differences seen in people with autism may be due to dietary preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130332.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130332.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T18:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research suggested that autism spectrum disorder (ASD) may be at least partly caused by differences in the composition of the gut microbiota, based on the observation that certain types of microbes are more common in people with autism. But a new study suggests that the link may actually work the other way around: the diversity in species found in the guts of children with autism may be due to their restricted dietary preferences associated with autism, rather than the cause of their symptoms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plant-based alternative food consumption may have doubled in UK over ten years suggests first analysis of its kind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130256.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130256.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T18:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proportion of UK people reporting eating and drinking plant-based alternative foods such as plant-based milk, vegan sausages and vegetable burgers nearly doubled between 2008 -- 2011 and 2017 -- 2019, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supportive strategies help 'picky eaters' deal with food aversions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130246.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211111130246.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T18:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a large national survey, adults who struggled with picky eating habits as children overwhelmingly said they benefitted more from positive and encouraging strategies their parents used than forceful or coercive approaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export GitHub Advanced Security license usage data]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-11-export-github-advanced-security-license-usage-data</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-11-export-github-advanced-security-license-usage-data"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T10:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Export GitHub Advanced Security license usage data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable WEBSSH for RedHat based Custom Docker image]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enable-webssh-for-redhat-based-custom-docker-image/ba-p/2947028</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enable-webssh-for-redhat-based-custom-docker-image/ba-p/2947028"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T02:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In App Service platform, the WEBSSH feature is backed by openssh-server. For Azure App Service built-in docker images, the platform by default has OpenSSH server configured. But for custom docker image, you will have to setup the OpenSSH server by yourself.
 
We used to notice the following RedHat issue that may cause your custom docker container failed to install openssh-server.Not Finding openssh-server-8.0p1-3.el8.x86_64.rpm in REDHAT ubi 8 docker image - Red Hat Customer PortalAt that time, you only have two options: either you register the RedHat system running within the container and attach it to a RedHat subscription, or you can download the openssh-server package and manually install it inside your docker container.
 
The good news is that RedHat openssh-server package now became …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hanli_Ren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linkify selected text on URL paste]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-linkify-selected-text-on-url-paste</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-linkify-selected-text-on-url-paste"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T20:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linkify selected text on URL paste]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered genetic link to non-alcoholic inflammatory liver disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110145455.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110145455.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T19:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have shown that albino mice of the C57BL/6 line are highly susceptible to developing the inflammatory liver condition non-alcoholic steatohepatitis (NASH) when fed a high cholesterol diet. The albino mice carry a mutation in the tyrosinase gene leading to a deficiency of melanin synthesis. NASH is a serious illness in humans, and the identification of the involvement of tyrosinase in NASH development will guide future research into this condition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team member pull request review notifications can be configured independently of auto assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-team-member-pull-request-review-notifications-can-be-configured-independently-of-auto-assignment</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-team-member-pull-request-review-notifications-can-be-configured-independently-of-auto-assignment"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T19:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team member pull request review notifications can be configured independently of auto assignment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleep disorders linked with more severe outcomes from COVID-19, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110131628.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110131628.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research shows a 31 percent increased risk for hospitalization and mortality in patients with sleep-disordered breathing and sleep-related hypoxia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleep disorders linked with more severe outcomes from COVID-19, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110131628.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110131628.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research shows a 31 percent increased risk for hospitalization and mortality in patients with sleep-disordered breathing and sleep-related hypoxia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Input types for manual workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-github-actions-input-types-for-manual-workflows</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-github-actions-input-types-for-manual-workflows"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Input types for manual workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Cloud self-service organization upgrade to an Enterprise Account]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-github-enterprise-cloud-self-service-organization-upgrade-to-an-enterprise-account</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-github-enterprise-cloud-self-service-organization-upgrade-to-an-enterprise-account"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T16:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Cloud self-service organization upgrade to an Enterprise Account]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET 6 now available on App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/net-6-now-available-on-app-service/ba-p/2945364</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/net-6-now-available-on-app-service/ba-p/2945364"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week at .NET Conf we announced the availability of Day 0 support for .NET 6 GA on App Service so you can take advantage of the latest .NET Long-term Support (LTS) version.
 
Day 0 support is enabled by our Early Access feature, which allows you to use the latest .NET version immediately for both Windows and Linux applications.  To learn more about Early Access, visit here.
 
Get started with .NET 6 by trying out our Quickstart today.
 
To learn more about .NET 6, visit the .NET blog and tune into our @9:30am session November 10th during .NET Conf to see how you can get started with .NET 6 on App Service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeffmartinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plant-based gummy candy helps vegans and vegetarians get their vitamins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110104636.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211110104636.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldwide, millions of people follow vegan and vegetarian diets for religious, ethical, environmental or economic reasons. While these diets have purported health benefits, they can also lack essential nutrients, such as vitamins B12 and D3, if not well-planned or supplemented correctly. Now, researchers have packed a strawberry-flavored gummy with these vitamins, formulating it without any animal products so vegans and vegetarians can reach their recommended daily allowances (RDA).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL code scanning now recognizes more Java and JavaScript libraries and frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-codeql-code-scanning-now-recognizes-more-java-and-javascript-libraries-and-frameworks</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-codeql-code-scanning-now-recognizes-more-java-and-javascript-libraries-and-frameworks"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T12:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL code scanning now recognizes more Java and JavaScript libraries and frameworks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL now supports Apple Silicon (M1)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-codeql-now-supports-apple-silicon-m1</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-codeql-now-supports-apple-silicon-m1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T12:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL now supports Apple Silicon (M1)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Require pull requests without requiring reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-require-pull-requests-without-requiring-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-require-pull-requests-without-requiring-reviews"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T12:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Require pull requests without requiring reviews]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Track code scanning alerts in GitHub issues using task lists]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-track-code-scanning-alerts-in-github-issues-using-task-lists</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-track-code-scanning-alerts-in-github-issues-using-task-lists"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T11:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Track code scanning alerts in GitHub issues using task lists]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository invites are now more accessible on GitHub.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-repository-invites-are-now-more-accessible-on-github-com</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-10-repository-invites-are-now-more-accessible-on-github-com"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T08:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository invites are now more accessible on GitHub.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-meta-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-meta-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.3 Release Candidate is available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-the-github-enterprise-server-3-3-release-candidate-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-the-github-enterprise-server-3-3-release-candidate-is-available"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.3 Release Candidate is available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landmark study points to source of rapid aging, chronic inflammation in people living with HIV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109155142.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109155142.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T20:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking study of people living with HIV, researchers found that elusive white blood cells called neutrophils play a role in impaired T cell functions and counts, as well as the associated chronic inflammation that is common with the virus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Conditional execution of steps in actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-github-actions-conditional-execution-of-steps-in-actions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-github-actions-conditional-execution-of-steps-in-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T17:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Conditional execution of steps in actions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A potential role for ibuprofen in older adults’ immunity to RSV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109120349.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109120349.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T17:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research suggests there may someday be a role for ibuprofen in providing older adults with lasting immunity against RSV, a virus commonly associated with infants and young kids that also rivals the flu as a dangerous wintertime infection for the elderly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listening to favorite music improves brain plasticity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109120324.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109120324.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T17:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have demonstrated that repeated listening to personally meaningful music induces beneficial brain plasticity in patients with mild cognitive impairment or early Alzheimer's disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fat-secreted molecule lowers response to common cancer treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095351.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095351.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leptin, a molecule produced by fat cells, appears to cancel out the effects of the estrogen-blocking therapy tamoxifen, a drug commonly used to treat and prevent breast cancers, suggests a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anxiety effectively treated with exercise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095348.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095348.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both moderate and strenuous exercise alleviate symptoms of anxiety, even when the disorder is chronic, a new study shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diagnosis of Alzheimer’s and related dementias reduces social activity, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095336.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095336.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the belief that early diagnosis of Alzheimer's disease and other dementias is crucial, a new study found that the diagnosis may unintentionally impact social relationships and activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diagnosis of Alzheimer’s and related dementias reduces social activity, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095336.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095336.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the belief that early diagnosis of Alzheimer's disease and other dementias is crucial, a new study found that the diagnosis may unintentionally impact social relationships and activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cellular aging: A basic paradox elucidated]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095334.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109095334.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cancer researchers show for the first time that cellular senescence, which occurs when aging cells stop dividing, is caused by irreversible damage to the genome rather than simply by telomere erosion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code of conduct highlighted on repository overview]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-code-of-conduct-highlighted-on-repository-overview</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-code-of-conduct-highlighted-on-repository-overview"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T14:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code of conduct highlighted on repository overview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrospective study finds that cancer drug also lowers blood glucose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109080904.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211109080904.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dasatinib, a drug that often is used to treat certain types of leukemia, may have antidiabetic effects comparable to medications used to treat diabetes, and with more research may become a novel therapy for diabetic patients, according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expiration dates of SAML-authorized PATs available via API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-expiration-dates-of-saml-authorized-pats-available-via-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2021-11-09-expiration-dates-of-saml-authorized-pats-available-via-api"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T12:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expiration dates of SAML-authorized PATs available via API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phanatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bedtime linked with heart health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108193627.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108193627.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T00:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going to sleep between 10:00 and 11:00 pm is associated with a lower risk of developing heart disease compared to earlier or later bedtimes, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sleep Disorders News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stem cells do not (only) play dice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108130842.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108130842.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T18:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In just a few weeks a completely new organism develops from a fertilized egg cell. The real miracle is that a bunch of identical stem cells turns into completely different, specialized cell types. A team has now been able to show that the specialization of individual cells during embryonic development is not, as previously assumed, exclusively left to chance but is rather determined by cell communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PowerShell on Linux SKU in Azure Functions is now available in public preview]]></title>
        <id>powershell-on-linux-sku-in-azure-functions-is-now-available-in-public-preview</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/powershell-on-linux-sku-in-azure-functions-is-now-available-in-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now develop Azure Functions PowerShell apps locally and deploy them to Azure Functions on Linux OS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally available: Azure Functions runtime 4.0]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-azure-functions-runtime-40</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-azure-functions-runtime-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.0 of the Azure Functions runtime supports .NET 6. It also supports Node.js, Python, Java, PowerShell, and other languages using custom handlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET 6.0 in Azure Functions is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>net-60-in-azure-functions-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/net-60-in-azure-functions-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both the in-process and isolated models are supported in .NET 6.0 Azure Functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Build and deploy full-stack .NET 6.0 apps with Azure Static Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-build-and-deploy-fullstack-net-60-apps-with-azure-static-web-apps</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-build-and-deploy-fullstack-net-60-apps-with-azure-static-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps now supports building and deploying .NET 6 Blazor WebAssembly and Azure Functions apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Availability of Azure Functions OpenAPI Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-of-azure-functions-openapi-extension/ba-p/2931231</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-of-azure-functions-openapi-extension/ba-p/2931231"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly a year ago, the first public preview version of Azure Functions OpenAPI Extension was released, which had been a long-waited feature from the dev communities for a long time. Today, we cannot be more excited to announce the general availability of Azure Functions OpenAPI Extension. It was originally a community-driven project, and then it's now become the "official" extension. This extension supports .NET Core 2.1 (LTS), 3.1 (LTS), .NET 5 and .NET 6 (LTS). It also supports both in-process worker and out-of-process worker of Azure Functions runtime. Throughout this post, let's take a look at how to create a function app with the OpenAPI extension in .NET 6, in Visual Studio 2022.
 

NOTE: The updated Visual Studio project template for this extension supporting both in-process and ou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinyoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack .NET 6 Apps with Blazor WebAssembly and Azure Static Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/full-stack-net-6-apps-with-blazor-webassembly-and-azure-static/ba-p/2933428</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/full-stack-net-6-apps-with-blazor-webassembly-and-azure-static/ba-p/2933428"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET 6 is the latest version of .NET and it’s generally available today. The Azure Static Web Apps team is excited to announce that you can now run full-stack .NET 6 apps on Static Web Apps!
 
What is Azure Static Web Apps?
 
Azure Static Web Apps is a service that automatically builds and deploys full-stack web apps to Azure from a code repository. It supports popular frontend frameworks, including Blazor WebAssembly.
 
If you need a backend API, you can add Azure Functions to your project’s repository.
 
Each time you push changes to your repository, Azure Static Web Apps automatically builds and deploys both your frontend app and backend API.
 
Azure Static Web Apps has everything you need to run a modern web app, including global distribution, built-in authentication, routing rules, st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite understanding the concept of mindfulness, people are applying it incorrectly, research finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108081645.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211108081645.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T13:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mindful awareness is about both accepting and engaging with life's challenges, and that's what popularized concepts of mindfulness tend to miss, new research has found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spirituality News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers investigate role of gene associated with Alzheimer’s disease in brain’s immune cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211106125841.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211106125841.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T16:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When immune cells move throughout the brain, they act as the first line of defense against viruses, toxic materials and damaged neurons, rushing over to clear out them. Researchers have been investigating how these immune cells in the brain -- microglia -- relate to a gene mutation recently found in Alzheimer's disease patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple sclerosis drug improves memory in mice modeling Alzheimer’s disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105150501.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105150501.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T19:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers found that glatiramer acetate, a prescription drug currently used to treat patients with multiple sclerosis, improved memory in a mouse model of Alzheimer's disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New strategy against treatment-resistant prostate cancer identified]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105134626.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105134626.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T17:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has identified an RNA molecule that suppresses prostate tumors. The scientists found that prostate cancers develop ways to shut down this RNA molecule to allow themselves to grow. According to the new research -- conducted in mice implanted with human prostate tumor samples -- restoring this so-called long noncoding RNA could be a new strategy to treat prostate cancer that has developed resistance to hormonal therapies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Men's Health News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save the planet (and your health) by steering clear of sweets and pastries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105103801.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105103801.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need another reason to cut back on sugary foods and drinks, apart from an expanding waistline? They're not helping the environment, contributing to a higher cropland, water scarcity and ecological footprint, according to a new review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study of 18000+ US and Australian older people reveals moderate drinking protective against heart disease, more than for tea totalers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105103740.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/11/211105103740.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A landmark study of more than 18,000 Americans and Australians over 70 years of age reveals that 3.5 to 7 average drinks of alcohol a week is more protective against heart disease and in fact all-cause mortality - compared to those who drank no alcohol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>