<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2024-04-20T21:06:04.567Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Is Assuming A Pre-War Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-world-is-assuming-a-pre-war-posture</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-world-is-assuming-a-pre-war-posture"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T14:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The World Is Assuming A Pre-War Posture appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push rules public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-push-rules-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-push-rules-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Push rules public beta
The post Push rules public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Kernel Updates: A Closer Look at Our Redesigned Plugin and Function Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2462</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/python-kernel-updates-a-closer-look-at-our-redesigned-plugin-and-function-integration/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T15:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we approach a stable v1.0 version of the Python Semantic Kernel SDK, we analysed the methods used to add plugins and functions to the kernel. We realised that the variety of available methods might confuse developers. For instance, when should one use import_plugin_from_object() versus import_native_plugin_from_directory()?
The post Python Kernel Updates: A Closer Look at Our Redesigned Plugin and Function Integration appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Mattson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Azure Load Testing on Azure App Service web apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/run-azure-load-testing-on-azure-app-service-web-apps/ba-p/4117175</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/run-azure-load-testing-on-azure-app-service-web-apps/ba-p/4117175"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now create and run load tests directly from App Service web apps in Azure portal. This functionality, powered by Azure Load Testing, enables you to get started with your performance testing journey in a few clicks.
 
Using the Load Testing functionality in App Service web apps you can do the following:

Get started without any knowledge of performance testing tools by configuring your HTTP request details in the Azure portal.
Run tests with up to 100,000 concurrent virtual users and up to 24-hour duration to simulate load testing scenarios like stress testing, spike testing, endurance testing etc.
Automatically gain access to client-side and server-side metrics, which will help in identifying performance bottlenecks.
View the test run history to continuously monitor their web app performance.

 
Navigate to your App Service web app in Azure portal to find the Load Testing feature in the Performance section as shown below.Screenshot of Load Testing feature in Azure App service portal
 
To learn more about this feature and how to use it, check out the documentation. We would love to hear your feedback and suggestions on how to improve it. Please share your thoughts and questions in the comments below or on the feedback forum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita_Nallamothu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-codeql-for-visual-studio-code-documentation-is-now-on-docs-github-com</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-codeql-for-visual-studio-code-documentation-is-now-on-docs-github-com"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T09:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com
The post CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Space Of Possible Minds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/ai-could-be-a-bridge-toward-diverse-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/ai-could-be-a-bridge-toward-diverse-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T18:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Space Of Possible Minds appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-updates-to-github-importer-and-the-deprecation-of-the-source-import-rest-api-endpoint</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-updates-to-github-importer-and-the-deprecation-of-the-source-import-rest-api-endpoint"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T17:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint
The post Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in the Reliable Web App Pattern for .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/what-s-new-in-the-reliable-web-app-pattern-for-net/ba-p/4116085</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/what-s-new-in-the-reliable-web-app-pattern-for-net/ba-p/4116085"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of The Reliable Web App (RWA) Pattern for .NET enhances its original objective of helping existing .NET web apps transition to Azure by now emphasizing improvements to production infrastructure. These enhancements are a direct response to user feedback, focusing especially on the importance of Infrastructure as Code (IaC) using Bicep best practices and network security. While the update maintains its foundational developer patterns, it also boosts network security for production deployments and streamlines the initial setup process. 
 
In this blog post, we will explain what the reliable web app pattern entails, highlight the new features, and guide you on how to begin using it today. 
 
What is the reliable web app pattern (RWA)? 
The reliable web app pattern is one of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mattsoucoup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-configure-organization-level-codeql-model-packs-for-github-code-scanning</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-configure-organization-level-codeql-model-packs-for-github-code-scanning"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning
The post Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock AI Collaboration at Microsoft BUILD 2024 with Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2467</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/unlock-ai-collaboration-at-microsoft-build-2024-with-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T21:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The moment we’ve all been waiting for is nearly here. Microsoft BUILD 2024, happening from May 21 – 23rd, is poised to be a groundbreaking event, especially for our community working at the intersection of AI and application development.
The post Unlock AI Collaboration at Microsoft BUILD 2024 with Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Chaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Importer’s new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-github-enterprise-importers-new-git-source-migrator-improves-reliability-of-large-repo-migrations</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-github-enterprise-importers-new-git-source-migrator-improves-reliability-of-large-repo-migrations"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T20:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Importer's new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations
The post GitHub Enterprise Importer’s new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-secret-scanning-for-historically-existing-secrets-found-in-github-discussions-and-pull-requests</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-secret-scanning-for-historically-existing-secrets-found-in-github-discussions-and-pull-requests"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T19:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests
The post Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of multi-label larger runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-of-multi-label-larger-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-of-multi-label-larger-runners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T19:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of multi-label larger runners
The post Deprecation of multi-label larger runners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-notice-v3-of-the-artifact-actions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-notice-v3-of-the-artifact-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T17:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions
The post Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need To Rewild The Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post We Need To Rewild The Internet  appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 20th, 2024 - Introducing QR code sign-in and final sales taxes update]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3841-april-20th-2024-introducing-qr-code-sign-in-and-final-sales-taxes-update/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3841-april-20th-2024-introducing-qr-code-sign-in-and-final-sales-taxes-update/1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features and announcements
QR code sign-in
Now you can simply scan a QR code on Kagi's login page with an authenticated device to log into a new device. For more details, visit our help page. #2417 @FrederickZh


Sales tax rollout
Starting this Sunday, April 21st, sales taxes will apply to all subscriptions. We have notified subscribers of this change via email. This marks the completion of the sales tax rollout. For further details, please visit our FAQ page.
Improvements and bug fixes
Add keyboard shortcuts shift-J/K to skip to next domain's results #2465 @Deebster
[Apperance][New UI] Plans do not show their differences anymore #3796 @igak_rekcartgub
Lens settings has a incorrect input label or maybe an incorrect input field? Not sure... #3845 @gunslingerfry
Provide feedback for copying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sourceRepositoryUrl is now a required input to the StartRepositoryMigration GraphQL Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-15-sourcerepositoryurl-is-now-a-required-input-to-the-startrepositorymigration-graphql-endpoint</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-15-sourcerepositoryurl-is-now-a-required-input-to-the-startrepositorymigration-graphql-endpoint"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T22:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sourceRepositoryUrl is now a required input to the StartRepositoryMigration GraphQL Endpoint
The post sourceRepositoryUrl is now a required input to the StartRepositoryMigration GraphQL Endpoint appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic Kernel Office Hours Recordings]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2453</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-office-hours-recordings/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T20:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Semantic Kernel Office Hour Recordings
The post Semantic Kernel Office Hours Recordings appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Availability: Free hosting plan for WordPress on App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-free-hosting-plan-for-wordpress-on-app/ba-p/4114613</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-free-hosting-plan-for-wordpress-on-app/ba-p/4114613"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to share with you that WordPress on App Service free hosting plan is now generally available.
 
A quick look at our hosting plans:




Hosting Plan


WebApp Server


Database Server




Free


F1 Free Tier
(60 CPU minutes per day, 1 GB RAM, 1 GB Storage)


Burstable, B1ms Free trial
(1 vCores, 2 GB RAM, 32 GB storage, 396 IOPS)




Basic


B1
(1 vCores, 1.75 GB RAM, 10 GB Storage)


Burstable, B1s
(1 vCores, 1 GB RAM, 20 GB storage, Auto IOPS)




Standard


P1V2
(1 vCores, 3.5 GB RAM, 250 GB Storage)


Burstable, B2s
(2 vCores, 4 GB RAM, 128 GB storage, Auto IOPS)




Premium


P1V3
(2 vCores, 8 GB RAM, 250 GB Storage)


General Purpose, D2ds_v4
(2 vCores, 16 GB RAM, 256 GB storage, Auto IOPS)




 
The free hosting plan provides you with a playground to explore and experi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Load Testing generally available on Fairfax]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-load-testing-generally-available-on-fairfax/ba-p/4114448</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-load-testing-generally-available-on-fairfax/ba-p/4114448"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T12:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Load Testing is now generally available in Fairfax cloud - USGov Virginia. US Government customers on the Fairfax cloud can now use Azure Load Testing, a fully managed load-testing service that simplifies the end-to-end process of performance testing.
 
US Government customers can leverage Azure Load Testing to easily generate high-scale load and quickly identify performance bottlenecks using a rich dashboard of client-side and server-side metrics. Customers can also ensure continuous performance validation by integrating load tests into CI/CD workflows. Being a service built for Azure; Azure Load Testing builds on the existing Azure conventions to streamline billing and test management, and it integrates seamlessly with other Azure services.
 
With Azure Load Testing, customers can

Get started without any knowledge of performance testing tools by configuring the test scenarios in the Azure portal itself or by uploading their existing Apache JMeter scripts. Azure Load Testing provides high fidelity support for Apache JMeter.
Run tests with up to 100,000 concurrent virtual users and up to 24-hour duration to simulate load testing scenarios like stress testing, spike testing, endurance testing etc.
Run load tests against private endpoints, that are not publicly accessible, by leveraging virtual network injection.
Easily identify root causes using a combined dashboard of client-side and server-side metrics; identify performance regressions using analysis capabilities like comparing results, viewing trends in metrics across test runs and comparing metrics with baseline.
Automate the process of performance testing using a first class support for Azure Pipelines and GitHub actions or by using Az CLI, REST APIs and SDKs.

Please do try out Azure Load Testing in Fairfax and let us know your feedback through the feedback forum.
Additional resources about Azure Load Testing at https://aka.ms/malt-resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nagarjuna_V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a React+Node App with Nginx as Reverse Proxy on Azure Container App: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploying-a-react-node-app-with-nginx-as-reverse-proxy-on-azure/ba-p/4114304</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploying-a-react-node-app-with-nginx-as-reverse-proxy-on-azure/ba-p/4114304"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T10:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog demystifies the process of deploying a React+Node application using Nginx as a reverse proxy on Azure Container App. This blog will serve as a hands-on guide to help you navigate the complexities of deploying your React+Node application on Azure. We’ll cover everything from setting up your environment to configuring Nginx and Azure Container App.
 
Prerequisites
As stated in our official documentation for Azure Container Apps, there are two types of ingress that can be enabled: External and Internal. In addition, it supports both HTTP and TCP for ingress protocols. For this demo we will require Ingress-enabled Container App and Azure Container Registry to build and publish Docker containers.
 
Architecture
The architecture features an Nginx container that will be accessible over …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yash_gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belgium Leads The Way On Democratic Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/belgium-leads-the-way-on-democratic-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/belgium-leads-the-way-on-democratic-innovation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Belgium Leads The Way On Democratic Innovation appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning changes to detection and validation for Google Cloud Platform, Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-secret-scanning-changes-to-detection-and-validation-for-google-cloud-platform-slack</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-secret-scanning-changes-to-detection-and-validation-for-google-cloud-platform-slack"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T21:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning changes to detection and validation for Google Cloud Platform, Slack
The post Secret scanning changes to detection and validation for Google Cloud Platform, Slack appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Handlebars Planner in Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2441</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/using-handlebars-planner-in-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T20:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to dive into the Handlebars Planner, a powerful tool for creating customized plans.
The post Using Handlebars Planner in Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Native IP Allow List expands to EMU User Namespaces – Private Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-github-native-ip-allow-list-expands-to-emu-user-namespaces-private-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-github-native-ip-allow-list-expands-to-emu-user-namespaces-private-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T19:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Native IP Allow List expands to EMU User Namespaces - Private Beta
The post GitHub Native IP Allow List expands to EMU User Namespaces – Private Beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.17.0: Support for Java 22, Swift 5.10, TS 5.4, C# 12]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-codeql-2-17-0-support-for-java-22-swift-5-10-ts-5-4-c-12</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-11-codeql-2-17-0-support-for-java-22-swift-5-10-ts-5-4-c-12"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.17.0: Support for Java 22, Swift 5.10, TS 5.4, C# 12
The post CodeQL 2.17.0: Support for Java 22, Swift 5.10, TS 5.4, C# 12 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hostfile entry on Windows and Linux machine]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/hostfile-entry-on-windows-and-linux-machine/ba-p/4111820</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/hostfile-entry-on-windows-and-linux-machine/ba-p/4111820"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T10:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hosts file, commonly known as etc\hosts, functions as a text-based tool employed by operating systems like Windows and Linux, to establish associations between IP addresses and host names or domain names. Serving as a localized DNS service, it supersedes mappings provided by external DNS servers, enhancing efficiency in local domain resolution. Its location varies according to the operating system utilized. Failure to retrieve IP addresses from a locally installed server or resolve them through DNS can result in application startup issues, underscoring the critical role of the hosts file in network connectivity.
Steps to create hostfile entry on Windows Virtual Machine:1. Open your text editor in Administrator mode. To do this, right-click on your text editor application (such as Notep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ShrutiDave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring Apps feature updates in Q1 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-spring-apps-feature-updates-in-q1-2024/ba-p/4110086</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-spring-apps-feature-updates-in-q1-2024/ba-p/4110086"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following updates are now available in the Enterprise plan:
 
Save up to 47%: Azure Spring Apps Enterprise is now eligible for Azure Savings plan:
All Azure Spring Apps regions under the Enterprise plan are eligible for substantial cost savings – 20% for one year and 47% for three years – when you commit to Azure savings Plan, read more.
 
Azure CLI supports to stream log of Spring Cloud Gateway:
This feature allows you to fetch the log of Spring Cloud Gateway in real-time for diagnosis purposes, read more.
 
Azure CLI supports to stream log of Application Configuration Service:
The feature allows you to retrieve the log of the Application Configuration Service using Azure CLI, making it possible to detect any configuration updates, read more.
 
Showing version of buildpacks:
The lates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hang_Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub-hosted runner images deprecation notice: Docker Compose v1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-10-github-hosted-runner-images-deprecation-notice-docker-compose-v1</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-10-github-hosted-runner-images-deprecation-notice-docker-compose-v1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T17:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub-hosted runner images deprecation notice: Docker Compose v1
The post GitHub-hosted runner images deprecation notice: Docker Compose v1 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traveling At The Speed Of The Soul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/traveling-at-the-speed-of-the-soul</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/traveling-at-the-speed-of-the-soul"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T16:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Traveling At The Speed Of The Soul appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Hunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a serverless AI chat with RAG using LangChain.js]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-a-serverless-ai-chat-with-rag-using-langchain-js/ba-p/4111041</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-a-serverless-ai-chat-with-rag-using-langchain-js/ba-p/4111041"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're still at the beginning of exploring what we can do with generative AI, and the field is moving fast, very fast!
 
And when things move fast, you need to be able to experiment and iterate quickly. First to validate your ideas with a prototype, then to scale up to production if it works.
 
In this article, we'll show you how LangChain.js, Ollama with Mistral 7B model and Azure can be used together to build a serverless chatbot that can answer questions using a RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) pipeline. We'll see first how you can work fully locally to develop and test your chatbot, and then deploy it to the cloud with state-of-the-art OpenAI models.
 
Here's a preview of the final project:

 
Grab your favorite beverage, and let's dive in!
TL;DR key takeaways

 LangChain.js provide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sinedied</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a serverless ChatGPT with RAG using LangChain.js]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-a-serverless-chatgpt-with-rag-using-langchain-js/ba-p/4111041</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-a-serverless-chatgpt-with-rag-using-langchain-js/ba-p/4111041"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're still at the beginning of exploring what we can do with generative AI, and the field is moving fast, very fast!
 
And when things move fast, you need to be able to experiment and iterate quickly. First to validate your ideas with a prototype, then to scale up to production if it works.
 
In this article, we'll show you how LangChain.js, Ollama with Mistral 7B model and Azure can be used together to build a serverless chatbot that can answer questions using a RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) pipeline. We'll see first how you can work fully locally to develop and test your chatbot, and then deploy it to the cloud with state-of-the-art OpenAI models.
 
Here's a preview of the final project:

 
Grab your favorite beverage, and let's dive in!
TL;DR key takeaways

 LangChain.js provide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sinedied</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL threat model settings are now available for C# (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-10-codeql-threat-model-settings-are-now-available-for-c-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-10-codeql-threat-model-settings-are-now-available-for-c-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL threat model settings are now available for C# (beta)
The post CodeQL threat model settings are now available for C# (beta) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Case Study: Cognizant & Microsoft Collaborate to Power Healthcare with Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2435</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/cognizant-microsoft-collaborate-to-power-healthcare-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cognizant and Microsoft Collaborate to Power the Future of Healthcare Administration with Generative AI
The post Customer Case Study: Cognizant & Microsoft Collaborate to Power Healthcare with Generative AI appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Enhanced Code Review on GitHub Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-09-introducing-enhanced-code-review-on-github-mobile</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-09-introducing-enhanced-code-review-on-github-mobile"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T17:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Enhanced Code Review on GitHub Mobile
The post Introducing Enhanced Code Review on GitHub Mobile appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What just happened, what is happening next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/what-just-happened-what-is-happening</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/what-just-happened-what-is-happening"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T14:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tasks AI can do well are expanding rapidly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 10th, 2024 - Introducing Kagi's new design]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3750-april-10th-2024-introducing-kagis-new-design/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3750-april-10th-2024-introducing-kagis-new-design/1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T12:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Features and Updates
Refreshed UI design
We're delighted to unveil our updated design of key search pages and a completely revamped settings experience, now featuring a fresh, new look!  Here's a sneak peek:
Homepage


Settings


Onboarding


Assistant highlights
New model available: added Google's latest LLM, Gemini 1.5 Pro
Privacy scores: we introduced an LLM privacy score (details on how it's calculated)
Enhanced citations: they now reference the segment of text used to generate the cited content

Sales tax rollout
An update on our sales tax rollout plan. Effective today, sales tax will apply to all new customer accounts. For our existing customers, the implementation date is now set for April 16th. We will provide further details via email soon. In the meantime, if you have any questions, please don't hesitate to contact our team via email at support@kagi.com or Discord.
Improvements and bug fixes
Improved discussions lens results #3424 @raphael
Some requests seem to take too much time to load #3752 @ak42
Github repos from different orgs should not fold as subresults #149 @xvello
Search suggestion details break input field #3727 @b-kaiser
The search term variable, %s, is only evaluated once per bang #3698 @ph
Small Web Lens does not honor blocked sites #3725 @markkrueg
Kagi Knowledge wraps in middle of words #3702 @yeri
Claude 3 Opus failing with "Sorry, a problem occurred while processing your request. Please try again later." #3721 @ak42 
URL highlighting in assistant #3716 @cardinal086
API/FastGPT keep failing on one particular query #3713 @frin 
Summarizer fails with a YouTube link #3704 @frin 
Research AI provides sources not in native language #3658 @bebowilson]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Third Great Decentering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-third-great-decentering</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-third-great-decentering"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Third Great Decentering appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced filtering capabilities for the security overview dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-04-advanced-filtering-capabilities-for-the-security-overview-dashboard</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-04-advanced-filtering-capabilities-for-the-security-overview-dashboard"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T21:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced filtering capabilities for the security overview dashboard
The post Advanced filtering capabilities for the security overview dashboard appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Case Study: DataStax and Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2418</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-datastax-and-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T20:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’ll dive into a customer case study from Datastax and their recent press release and announcement on the DataStax and Microsoft collaboration on RAG capabilities on DataStax Astra DB Thanks again to the DataStax team for their amazing partnership!
The post Customer Case Study: DataStax and Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Java 21 and Tomcat 10.1 on Azure App Service Windows and Linux!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-java-21-and-tomcat-10-1-on-azure-app-service-windows/ba-p/4105714</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-java-21-and-tomcat-10-1-on-azure-app-service-windows/ba-p/4105714"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use Java 21 and Tomcat 10.1 on Azure App Service Windows and Linux! 
 

 
Also be sure to check out the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK 21. For more information about Java Stacks and Support on App Service, check out the Java Statement of Support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Java 21 and Tomcat 10.1 on Azure App Service!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-java-21-and-tomcat-10-1-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4105714</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-java-21-and-tomcat-10-1-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4105714"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use Java 21 and Tomcat 10.1 on Azure App Service! 
 

 
For more information about Java Stacks and Support on App Service, check out the Java Statement of Support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actions: Jobs executing on self hosted runners will now timeout in 5 days]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-04-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-04-actions-jobs-executing-on-self-hosted-runners-will-now-timeout-in-5-days"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To ensure that the Actions runners are truly ephemeral and more secure, we are now limiting execution timeouts on self hosted jobs to 5 days. If a job reaches this limit, the job is terminated and fails to complete. Learn more about using self-hosted runners with GitHub Actions
The post Actions: Jobs executing on self hosted runners will now timeout in 5 days appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total Eclipse Of The Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/total-eclipse-of-the-mind</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/total-eclipse-of-the-mind"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T11:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Total Eclipse Of The Mind appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurence Pevsner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets in GitHub wikis]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-03-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-in-github-wikis</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-03-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-in-github-wikis"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets in GitHub wikis
The post Secret scanning now detects secrets in GitHub wikis appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Plans with Semantic Kernel: Setting Up & Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2395</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/making-plans-with-semantic-kernel-setting-up-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello all, today we’re featuring a guest author on our Semantic Kernel blog, José Luis Latorre Millás, an MVP for Microsoft focused on AI.
The post Making Plans with Semantic Kernel: Setting Up & Authentication appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Hardware accelerated Android virtualization now available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-github-actions-hardware-accelerated-android-virtualization-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-github-actions-hardware-accelerated-android-virtualization-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Hardware accelerated Android virtualization now available
The post GitHub Actions: Hardware accelerated Android virtualization now available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new for GitHub Actions hosted runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-whats-new-for-github-actions-hosted-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-whats-new-for-github-actions-hosted-runners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's new for GitHub Actions hosted runners
The post What’s new for GitHub Actions hosted runners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of The Bee Bandits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-rise-of-the-bee-bandits</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-rise-of-the-bee-bandits"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Rise Of The Bee Bandits appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Milman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code security configurations let organizations easily roll out GitHub security products at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-code-security-configurations-let-organizations-easily-roll-out-github-security-products-at-scale</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-02-code-security-configurations-let-organizations-easily-roll-out-github-security-products-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code security configurations let organizations easily roll out GitHub security products at scale
The post Code security configurations let organizations easily roll out GitHub security products at scale appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 2nd, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3696-april-2nd-2024/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3696-april-2nd-2024/1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements and bug fixes
Allow previous 2FA code to work along with current 30sec one #3540 @frin 
Custom bangs accessible from Search Settings tab #3616 @mhitza
Asking !chat to modify a <script>...</script> tag causes the script tag in the response to be not escaped/not visible #3694 @heavyg
We've resolved capacity issues with our recent models upgrade
Bottom of image search results is cluttered with low quality Second Life screenshots #3632 @yellow 
Show summary of question in fastgpt in tab title #3203 @fictorial 
Image Description Completely Wrong #3600 @CrunchyFritos
Assistant Expert "<SEARCH REQUIRED" and then switches to spanish #3661 @tschoesi
Mistral "Sorry, a problem occurred while processing your request. Please try again later." #3684 @abb128 
Custom assistant ignoring custom instructions #3685 @Wanja 
Latext support in quick answer #3455 @Grooty
AI Model selection should be sticky #3503 @JamesT
Assistant code overflows #3428 @cardinal086]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/04/02/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/04/02/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading
I don’t think you should focus on the failure of others, or even the success of others. What you do need to do—and what is surprisingly hard—is to define success for your own part of the world, and work towards that. Non-monetary success, because again, money lags.
I’ve always loved Paul Ford’s writing, and recently
learned that he’s been writing short, punchy posts for the blog
of his startup, Aboard. His cofounder, Rich Ziade, is also writing great stuff, with
good humor - introducing himself as the other founder of Aboard.
This rally is so different because no one is beating around the bush anymore. It’s not about technology. It’s not about use cases or improving the world. It’s just, “More people buy, number go up.” The veil has been lifted and we all know it. It’s a momentum t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS 14 (Sonoma) is generally available and the `latest` macOS runner image]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-01-macos-14-sonoma-is-generally-available-and-the-latest-macos-runner-image</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-01-macos-14-sonoma-is-generally-available-and-the-latest-macos-runner-image"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[macOS 14 (Sonoma) is generally available and the `latest` macOS runner image
The post macOS 14 (Sonoma) is generally available and the `latest` macOS runner image appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for Microsoft Build: Explore cloud-native, AI, GitHub Copilot, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/get-ready-for-microsoft-build-explore-cloud-native-ai-github/ba-p/4102491</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/get-ready-for-microsoft-build-explore-cloud-native-ai-github/ba-p/4102491"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Build is next month! To get ready for the big event, we're exploring resources from Microsoft Learn so developers can get a head start on key topics by building new skills with the latest developer tools and techniques. We have a curated selection of resources to help you learn more about cloud-native development, adding AI to your apps, working productively with GitHub Copilot, and more. Plus, we have other timely news and announcements for developers from around Microsoft.
 
Get started with GitHub and Visual Studio CodeLearn how to use GitHub Copilot to increase your productivity when developing apps with Visual Studio Code.
Deploy cloud-native apps using Azure Container AppsLearn how to build, deploy, scale, and manage containerized cloud-native apps using Azure Container App…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mpgraven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Education Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-01-github-education-redesign</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-01-github-education-redesign"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“GitHub Education Redesign"
The post GitHub Education Redesign appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced templating in Semantic Kernel for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2123</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/enhanced-templating-in-semantic-kernel-for-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T15:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello to all Python enthusiasts working with Semantic Kernel! We are very happy to share some of the latest work we have been doing, namely we introduced not one but two new options for templates: Handlebars and Jinja2. And we also made some updates to the ‘semantic-kernel’
The post Enhanced templating in Semantic Kernel for Python appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard van Valkenburg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring App Service Certificate in Application Gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/configuring-app-service-certificate-in-application-gateway/ba-p/4083933</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/configuring-app-service-certificate-in-application-gateway/ba-p/4083933"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T11:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application gateway allows you to have an App Service app as a backend pool member with a custom domain.
 
You can use App Service Certificate or a Third Party Certificate to configure the custom domain. The next steps in the blog will guide you on how to download and export App Service Certificate with private key and upload in Application Gateway. Below are the steps:
 
Note: Downloading the App Service Certificate and uploading to App Gateway manually would require you to manually upload the renewed certificate in future.
 

Download the certificate:


Once the App Service Certificate is created and verified , follow the below steps to export the certificate:
Go to App Service Certificate > KeyVault where the certificate is stored.
Key Vault > Objects > Secrets > Select the secret where…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AmritpalSinghNaroo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the necessity of a sin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-the-necessity-of-a-sin</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-the-necessity-of-a-sin"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T14:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why treating AI like a person is the future]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated GitHub App visibility for Enterprise Managed Users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-updated-github-app-visibility-for-enterprise-managed-users</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-updated-github-app-visibility-for-enterprise-managed-users"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T20:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updated GitHub App visibility for Enterprise Managed Users
The post Updated GitHub App visibility for Enterprise Managed Users appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH CA support for enterprise-owned user accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-ssh-ca-support-for-enterprise-owned-user-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-ssh-ca-support-for-enterprise-owned-user-accounts"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T20:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SSH CA support for enterprise-owned user accounts
The post SSH CA support for enterprise-owned user accounts appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise – March 2024 update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-github-copilot-enterprise-march-2024-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-29-github-copilot-enterprise-march-2024-update"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T19:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise - March 2024 update
The post GitHub Copilot Enterprise – March 2024 update appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figma Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/03/29/figma-plugins.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/03/29/figma-plugins.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2023, I released a Figma plugin called Placemark, which lets you create
vector maps in Figma, the graphic design tool.
Since then I’ve been maintaining that plugin for fun, and introduced
another one, Placemark Globe.
They’ve been somewhat successful! The Placemark plugin has 11.3k users,
according to Figma’s community site, and Placemark Globe has 1.5k users.
The feedback loop for plugins is okay - you can see how many likes
your plugin has received, and how many “users” there are, but no
change-over-time statistics, so I built my own dashboard for the plugins using Observable.


But even with that, I don’t really know whether many people are
actually using them. Maybe “users” means unique installations - it
certainly doesn’t mean active users because the charts I’ve g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CircleCI is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-circleci-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-circleci-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T23:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CircleCI is now a GitHub secret scanning partner
The post CircleCI is now a GitHub secret scanning partner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Paths for Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2360</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/learning-paths-for-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T20:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to highlight new learning content released focused on Semantic Kernel.
APL-2005 Develop AI agents using Azure OpenAI and the Semantic Kernel SDK – Training | Microsoft Learn
.NET Conf Student Zone –
The post Learning Paths for Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Usage Metrics public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-actions-usage-metrics-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-actions-usage-metrics-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T19:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Usage Metrics public beta
The post Actions Usage Metrics public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot grouped security updates generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-dependabot-grouped-security-updates-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-28-dependabot-grouped-security-updates-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot grouped security updates generally available
The post Dependabot grouped security updates generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Artists Digitally Liberating Colonial Plunder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-artists-digitally-liberating-colonial-plunder</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-artists-digitally-liberating-colonial-plunder"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T15:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Artists Digitally Liberating Colonial Plunder appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alizeh Kohari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mergify is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-27-mergify-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-27-mergify-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T19:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergify is now a GitHub secret scanning partner
The post Mergify is now a GitHub secret scanning partner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volcengine is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-27-volcengine-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-27-volcengine-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T16:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volcengine is now a GitHub secret scanning partner
The post Volcengine is now a GitHub secret scanning partner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying React SPA and Python Backend Together on the Same Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploying-react-spa-and-python-backend-together-on-the-same/ba-p/4095567</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploying-react-spa-and-python-backend-together-on-the-same/ba-p/4095567"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T05:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction:
 
Integrating a React Single Page Application (SPA) with a Python backend on Azure App Service offers a powerful combination for building dynamic web applications. By leveraging React for the frontend and Python for the backend, developers can create modern, responsive web applications with a seamless user experience.
 

 
Azure App Service provides a convenient platform for hosting both frontend and backend components of your application in a single environment, simplifying deployment and management tasks. With this setup, the React frontend can communicate with the Python backend through HTTP requests, enabling data exchange and interaction between the two layers.
 
Overall, integrating React SPA with a Python backend on Azure App Service offers a flexible and efficient sol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanuja_Palakurthy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET on Azure Functions – March 2024 roadmap update]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/net-on-azure-functions-march-2024-roadmap-update/ba-p/4097744</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/net-on-azure-functions-march-2024-roadmap-update/ba-p/4097744"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our last roadmap update was in August 2023, in which we discussed the parity milestone for the isolated worker model and our overall plans for .NET 8. In that post, we outlined a plan to stagger the .NET 8 releases, with support first coming to the isolated worker model, and the in-process model option coming a bit later. This is still the plan, and in this post, we wanted to discuss a bit more about how things will work once the option is available.
 
How the in-process model option for .NET 8 will work
One key difference between this and previous .NET version changes for the in-process model is that it will be an update solely focused on enabling .NET 8 support. There will be no additional Functions-specific breaking changes from the latest host version for .NET 6 that your project would…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Henderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Case Study: Accenture and Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2350</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-accenture-and-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T22:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below we’ve provided a brief overview of the Customer Story of Accenture. Check out the entire Accenture Customer Story featured here: Accenture evolves its data analytics with Microsoft Fabric to calibrate the new “experience office”
The post Customer Case Study: Accenture and Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightspeed is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-lightspeed-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-lightspeed-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T21:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightspeed is now a GitHub secret scanning partner
The post Lightspeed is now a GitHub secret scanning partner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WorkOS is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-workos-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-workos-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T21:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WorkOS is now a GitHub secret scanning partner
The post WorkOS is now a GitHub secret scanning partner appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL can scan Java projects without a build]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-codeql-can-scan-java-projects-without-a-build</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-26-codeql-can-scan-java-projects-without-a-build"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T17:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL can scan Java projects without a build
The post CodeQL can scan Java projects without a build appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a context-grounded AI chatbot to your Azure Static Web Apps with streaming responses]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-a-context-grounded-ai-chatbot-to-your-azure-static-web-apps/ba-p/4097223</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-a-context-grounded-ai-chatbot-to-your-azure-static-web-apps/ba-p/4097223"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T16:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Static Web Apps is the best service to host websites with a lot of static content, such as documentation, marketing, or educational material. But sometimes, these websites are quite large, and with recent developments in large-language models, we can provide our users AI-generated answers to their questions within seconds, grounded in the content of our website.
 

 
In this article, we demonstrate how we can add a chatbot to allow our users to browse the content of our website quickly and easily with the use of a chatbot grounded in the content of our website. We’ll follow the RAG pattern (retrieval augmented generation), to ground our responses in the static content of our website, and use OpenAI’s APIs to provide responses. We’ll also feature Azure Functions’ Node.js v4 programmin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thomasgauvinmsft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 26th, 2024 - Widget Triggers Open to Community Translations and Model Upgrades for FastGPT and Research Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3654-march-26th-2024-widget-triggers-open-to-community-translations-and-model-upgrades-for-fastgpt-and-research-assistant/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3654-march-26th-2024-widget-triggers-open-to-community-translations-and-model-upgrades-for-fastgpt-and-research-assistant/1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T12:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features

We continue enhancing our search experience with bangs. Check the shield menu to see if a website has a corresponding bang. #3410 @frereit

We've upgraded the FastGPT, and Research Assistant (Fast+Expert) with the latest models to enhance performance:
FastGPT -> Claude 3 Haiku
Research Assistant, Fast -> Claude 3 Haiku
Research Assistant, Expert -> Claude 3 Sonnet

These are also available in Chat mode which allows full access to a range of models like Claude 3 Opus, GPT-4 and Mistral Large [Please note, Kagi Assistant is currently in closed beta and is exclusively accessible to subscribers of the Ultimate plan]

We now allow the community to see and translate the trigger phrases for widgets that utilize them, such as the weather and calculator widgets. Learn more about how to co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Case Study: Visma Spcs Improves Customer Experience with Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2335</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-study-visma-improves-customer-experience-with-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T20:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will dive into a customer case study. Thanks to the Visma team on their amazing partnership!
The post Customer Case Study: Visma Spcs Improves Customer Experience with Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the Feminist Revolution in Northern Syria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/inside-the-feminist-revolution-in-northern-syria</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/inside-the-feminist-revolution-in-northern-syria"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T20:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Inside the Feminist Revolution in Northern Syria appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Flock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Pages with Custom GitHub Actions Workflows are now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-25-github-pages-with-custom-github-actions-workflows-are-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-03-25-github-pages-with-custom-github-actions-workflows-are-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T17:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Pages with Custom GitHub Actions Workflows are now generally available
The post GitHub Pages with Custom GitHub Actions Workflows are now generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing General Availability of Azure App Service Automatic Scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-general-availability-of-azure-app-service-automatic/ba-p/4066251</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-general-availability-of-azure-app-service-automatic/ba-p/4066251"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service is pleased to announce general availability of the "Automatic Scaling" feature. We received important feedback about the Automatic Scaling feature during the preview phase and have made following enhancements to the Automatic Scaling feature.  
 

Automatic scaling is available for Premium V2 (P1V2, P2V2, P3V2) and Premium V3 (P0V3, P1V3, P2V3, P3V3, P1MV3, P2MV3, P3MV3, P4MV3, P5MV3) pricing tiers, and supported for all app types: Windows, Linux, and Windows container. 
A new metric viz. "Automatic Scaling Instance Count" is now available for web apps where Automatic Scaling is enabled. "Automatic Scaling Instance Count" will report the number of virtual machines on which the app is running including the pre-warmed instance if it is deployed.

In addition to these enhanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gauravseth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Service *.azurewebsites.net TLS Cert Renewal for Web Apps, Functions, and Logic Apps (Standard)]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-azurewebsites-net-tls-cert-renewal-for-web-apps/ba-p/4094627</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-azurewebsites-net-tls-cert-renewal-for-web-apps/ba-p/4094627"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T20:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog contains information about *.azurewebsites.net TLS certificate changes for Web Apps, Functions, and Logic Apps (Standard). Customers should not be impacted by this change. The scope of services affected includes Web Apps, Functions, and Logic Apps (Standard); Logic Apps (Consumption) and resources hosted on an ASE are not impacted. This change is limited to public Azure cloud; government clouds are not affected.
 
Every Web Apps, Functions, and Logic Apps (Standard) has its own default hostname that goes by “<resource-name>.azurewebsites.net” where App Service secures it with a wildcard *.azurewebsites.net TLS certificate. The current intermediate Microsoft PKI Subordinate CA certificates were set to expire on June 27th, 2024. App Service used these intermediate certificates in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YutangLin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy hybrid rendering frameworks on Azure Static Web Apps for optimized frontend hosting]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploy-hybrid-rendering-frameworks-on-azure-static-web-apps-for/ba-p/4094514</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploy-hybrid-rendering-frameworks-on-azure-static-web-apps-for/ba-p/4094514"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T19:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid rendering frontend frameworks on Azure Static Web Apps
Frontend frameworks have evolved to make use of the server to provide optimal hosting for frontend applications. From hybrid rendering modes to API routes and backend-for-frontend patterns, frontend frameworks such as Next.js, Nuxt.js, SvelteKit, and others have become capable of building full-stack applications. With Azure Static Web Apps, you can host these frontend frameworks on our distributed static asset host and serverless managed functions, providing you with the best experience for hosting frontend web applications on Azure.
 
In this article, we’ll dive into hybrid rendering frameworks and how these are hosted on Azure Static Web Apps, as well as give an insight into the ongoing work to bring more frameworks to Azure S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thomasgauvinmsft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Semantic Kernel with Dependency Injection]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2310</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/using-semantic-kernel-with-dependency-injection/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T17:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic Kernel fully supports dependency injection. After receiving many questions from the community as to how to best use dependency injection with Semantic Kernel, the team created an app to illustrate some effective patterns. 
The post Using Semantic Kernel with Dependency Injection appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Planetary Risks Of Nationalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-planetary-risks-of-nationalism</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-planetary-risks-of-nationalism"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T15:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Planetary Risks Of Nationalism appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>