<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2023-04-28T14:06:36.081Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To List All VNET Subnets Used for Private Endpoints of App service using PowerShell Script]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-list-all-vnet-subnets-used-for-private-endpoints-of-app/ba-p/3806513</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-list-all-vnet-subnets-used-for-private-endpoints-of-app/ba-p/3806513"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T02:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App service can enable Private Endpoints for inbound traffic. 
Customers may want to list all VNET subnets used for Private Endpoints, and enable Network Security Group for the Private Endpoints.
There is no way to do it from Azure portal. But the below Power shell script can help customers list all the subnets used for Private Endpoints.
 

List all VNET subnets used for Private Endpoint using PowerShell script

$privateEndpoints = Get-AzPrivateEndpoint
$subnetIds = $privateEndpoints | ForEach-Object { $_.Subnet.Id }
$uniqueSubnetIds = $subnetIds | Sort-Object -Unique
 
foreach ($subnetId in $uniqueSubnetIds) {
    Get-AzResource -ResourceId $subnetId
}
 
The output is like this 

 

Regarding more parameters for Get-AzPrivateEndpoint

         Check Get-AzPrivateEndpoint (Az.Network) | Microsoft Learn
 

How To Enable Network Security Group for Private Endpoints 
By default, network policies are disabled for a subnet in a virtual network.
You need to assign the NSG name first in this subnet, then enable NSG in “Network Policy for Private Endpoint”, then the PE will be applied the NSG rule. 
Manage network policies for private endpoints - Azure Private Link | Microsoft Learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Weizhen_Sun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try our new expandable event payload view in your audit log – Private Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-try-our-new-expandable-event-payload-view-in-your-audit-log-private-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-try-our-new-expandable-event-payload-view-in-your-audit-log-private-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T21:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try our new expandable event payload view in your audit log - Private Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects – April 27th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-github-issues-projects-april-27th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-github-issues-projects-april-27th-update"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T18:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects - April 27th update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL improvements for fine-grained PATs and GitHub Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-graphql-improvements-for-fine-grained-pats-and-github-apps</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-graphql-improvements-for-fine-grained-pats-and-github-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T18:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL improvements for fine-grained PATs and GitHub Apps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-fill form fields when creating a new repo]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-pre-fill-form-fields-when-creating-a-new-repo</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-27-pre-fill-form-fields-when-creating-a-new-repo"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-fill form fields when creating a new repo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Spring Boot, MongoDB Atlas App on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-spring-boot-mongodb-atlas-app-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3804121</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-spring-boot-mongodb-atlas-app-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3804121"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we’re going to build a resilient Java Spring Boot application that scales automatically and also provides high availability with built-in monitoring and diagnostics.
 
For this, we will be using Microsoft Azure App Service, a PaaS (platform as a service) offering by Microsoft Azure, because it's quite suitable for long running applications and web workloads.
 
As we want our application to be fully-managed and scaling automatically in the cloud, MongoDB Atlas is a great choice for our data store since it’s a fully-managed, cloud-native database as a service that can also scale up and down automatically in a cost-effective way to meet the needs of any application.
 
For this particular tutorial, we’ll be using the Spring Initializr plugin for IntelliJ,  connect it to a Mon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Custom DNS for Azure Spring App in a Private Network]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/configuring-custom-dns-for-azure-spring-app-in-a-private-network/ba-p/3805406</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/configuring-custom-dns-for-azure-spring-app-in-a-private-network/ba-p/3805406"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T05:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Spring App is a cloud-based platform for building and deploying enterprise-grade Java applications. By default, Azure Spring App uses Azure DNS for name resolution. However, in some cases, you may want to use custom DNS servers for name resolution. This article explains how to configure custom DNS for Azure Spring App in a private network.
 
Suggestions for Using Custom DNS.


Set up less than 3 custom DNS servers. 


         Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) uses the CoreDNS project for cluster DNS management and resolution. Based on observation, it only takes the first three custom DNS server settings. If you specify more than three custom DNS servers, AKS will only use the first three. 
         


Make sure that all custom DNS servers have same records that all of them could resolv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wanjing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A month of cloud native: Explore resources for cloud native app development]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/a-month-of-cloud-native-explore-resources-for-cloud-native-app/ba-p/3741548</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/a-month-of-cloud-native-explore-resources-for-cloud-native-app/ba-p/3741548"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T20:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the month of May, we’re focusing on cloud native—a modern approach to development that leverages cloud technologies, like containers and microservices. By design, cloud-native applications offer many advantages, including easier scalability, improved resiliency, and simpler management. While it might sound like a major shift, adopting a cloud native strategy is easier and quicker than you might think.
 
To help you get started, we’ve gathered essential learning to help you embrace a cloud native approach. Learn the fundamentals, explore tools, work through guided samples, and join a live webinar to learn more about cloud native apps.
 
Cloud native fundamentals Start your cloud native journey. Find out what makes an app "cloud native" and learn about the core pillars of cloud native so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Medford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web App Performance Root Cause Analysis with Application Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/web-app-performance-root-cause-analysis-with-application/ba-p/3805931</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/web-app-performance-root-cause-analysis-with-application/ba-p/3805931"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T17:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview
Having the ability to identify clear root cause for incidents in production workloads is valuable, the best way to prevent future incidents is to understand what caused past ones. Of course you can have a good set of load tests but still, incidents in production environments can happen and it's crucial to have available data that can help to understand what happened so application can be improved and prevent replications.
In this article we will learn how to use Application Insights and automatic profiler to find root cause for past incidents and prepare logging platform to ensure meaningful data for analysis.
 
Check configuration
This guide relies in the Application Insights Profiler, the list of supported platforms is listed here:
https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LuisLopes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Preview: Azure API Management and Microsoft Defender for APIs integration]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-azure-api-management-and-microsoft-defender-for-apis-integration</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-azure-api-management-and-microsoft-defender-for-apis-integration/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T17:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take your API security coverage to the next level with Azure API Management and Microsoft Defender for APIs integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally available: Synthetic GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-synthetic-graphql-2</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-synthetic-graphql-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Synthetic GraphQL, customers can create GraphQL APIs using their existing REST and SOAP APIs, allowing them to modernize their application API stack with minimal effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally available: API Management Authorizations]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-api-management-authorizations</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-api-management-authorizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API Management Authorizations are now generally available, providing a simple and reliable way to unbundle and abstract authorizations from web APIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Load Testing Pricing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-load-testing-pricing/ba-p/3805812</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-load-testing-pricing/ba-p/3805812"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T15:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Load Testing is a fully managed load testing service that enables you to easily generate high-scale load without worrying about test infrastructure set up. As a Product Manager, I get many questions about the pricing for the product. In this article, I will explain how pricing for Azure Load Testing works. The currency mentioned here is US dollar. These are the prices at the time of publishing this post. Over time, prices might change and there could be a mismatch with what customers see. For all pricing calculation and estimates, use the pricing calculator.
 
Cost factors when using Azure Load Testing
In this section I’ll talk about the different steps involved in using Azure Load Testing and the cost implications for each. As a developer or tester to use Azure Load Testing you need…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita_Nallamothu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give us your thoughts on running Kubernetes anywhere for a chance to win a $300 USD gift card!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/give-us-your-thoughts-on-running-kubernetes-anywhere-for-a/ba-p/3797779</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/give-us-your-thoughts-on-running-kubernetes-anywhere-for-a/ba-p/3797779"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you work with Kubernetes? Are you interested in improving Kubernetes experience across hybrid and multicloud environments?  
 
Azure Arc allows teams to manage servers and apps across data centers, at the edge, and in multicloud environments. The Azure Arc team would love to hear your thoughts on running Kubernetes anywhere. Your feedback will influence the future of Azure Arc and supported Kubernetes solutions. 
 
Take the survey below for a chance to win a $300 USD virtual gift card! Must be 18 or older. Survey ends on May 10, 2023.
 
Rules: https://aka.ms/K8sHybridSurveySweepstakes 
 
Take the survey → https://aka.ms/K8sHybridSurveyTC  
 
Thank you for your time! 
- The Azure Arc Team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SparshAgrawat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bring Your Own Storage (BYOS) to Azure App Service Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/bring-your-own-storage-byos-to-azure-app-service-web-app/ba-p/3753649</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/bring-your-own-storage-byos-to-azure-app-service-web-app/ba-p/3753649"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T09:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service Web Apps has been around for many years now and has for a long time been  a very reliable and performant product for running highly utilized workloads.  One of the benefits of Azure App Service Web Apps is the scaling capability which lets you add additional compute resources like CPU and Memory (aka another VM to the web farm) on-demand.  You can add additional compute power to your web site manually or using auto-scaling, as described here.  How this works from an architecture is explained at the location linked in the following bullet point.  The focus of this article however is concentrated on the File Server role which stores your code and static files.

Inside the Azure App Service Architecture

When your website needs to add an additional Web Worker to handle addit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csharpguitar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Service does not support Server Push in Http2]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-does-not-support-server-push-in-http2/ba-p/3803424</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/app-service-does-not-support-server-push-in-http2/ba-p/3803424"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T06:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, the Internet became so entrenched in our daily lives, with the increasing use of mobile, cloud, websites, we're always looking for a faster and more efficient method of communicating data. It finally came to the new protocol HTTP/2 announced by IETF in 2015, which is a more modernized, faster and more secure version, almost all major web browsers are on board so far.
As one of the powerful app platform providers, App service team also announced the support for the HTTP/2 protocol  for all apps hosted on App Service in March 2018.
 
What are the key differences from HTTP/1.x on app service?
 

HTTP/2 is binary
Fully multiplexed, instead of ordered and blocking
Ability to use one connection for parallelism
Has one TCP/IP connection per origin
Uses header compression to reduce overh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>XinyuShan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Min TLS Cipher Suite (Preview) Now Available on Azure Portal and Info on Upcoming Changes Before GA]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/min-tls-cipher-suite-preview-now-available-on-azure-portal-and/ba-p/3804134</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/min-tls-cipher-suite-preview-now-available-on-azure-portal-and/ba-p/3804134"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T20:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a previous announcement on the Minimum TLS Cipher Suite (preview), the feature only supported the configuration through the API. The good news is that now users can configure the minimum TLS cipher suite for incoming requests through the Azure portal! This feature is currently only supported on Premium SKUs and above. This article will go through what cipher suites are and how they work on App Service, the minimum TLS cipher suite experience on Azure portal, and more information about an upcoming change that will happen before General Availability (GA).
 
What are cipher suites and how do they work on App Service? 
A cipher suite is a set of instructions that contains algorithms and protocols to help secure network connections between clients and servers. By default, the front-end's O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YutangL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Your Cloud Journey with Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/start-your-cloud-journey-with-azure-app-service/ba-p/3804037</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/start-your-cloud-journey-with-azure-app-service/ba-p/3804037"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T19:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s face it, moving a line-of-business application that’s been designed to run on-prem, or even on a virtual machine, to the cloud can be intimidating. The good news is that you don’t need to go full-on cloud native all at once. Azure App Service offers a comprehensive platform for hosting .NET applications in the cloud with minimal code changes needed to the existing web app.
In this article I want to talk about how Azure App Service makes an excellent first step for a .NET application’s cloud journey. By the end of this article, I want you to have enough information to have a foundation for taking your taking your app to the cloud – and honestly to decide whether it’s the right decision at all.
 
While we think about the first step of the cloud journey, we need to be thoughtful about m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mattsoucoup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions Importer Feature Flags]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-importer-feature-flags</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-importer-feature-flags"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T18:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions Importer Feature Flags]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Faster macOS runners are now available in open public beta!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-faster-macos-runners-are-now-available-in-open-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-faster-macos-runners-are-now-available-in-open-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Faster macOS runners are now available in open public beta!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: macOS 13 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-macos-13-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-github-actions-macos-13-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: macOS 13 is now available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Click Into GitHub Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-one-click-into-github-codespaces</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-24-one-click-into-github-codespaces"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T15:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Click Into GitHub Codespaces]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service Logging: How to Monitor Your Web Apps in Real-Time]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-app-service-logging-how-to-monitor-your-web-apps-in-real/ba-p/3800390</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-app-service-logging-how-to-monitor-your-web-apps-in-real/ba-p/3800390"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T07:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing and running web applications, things don't always go as planned. You might encounter errors, underperforming response times, or unexpected behavior. The Azure App Service Diagnostics Logging capabilities come to the rescue in such situations. By enabling the application logging features, you can quickly and easily view your application logs to diagnose and fix issues.
 
Here are a few examples of the types of problems you can solve by consulting your application logs:
 

Errors: When an error occurs in your application, it's important to understand what went wrong and where. By consulting your application logs, you can see the error message and any relevant details, such as the stack trace. This can help you pinpoint the issue and fix it more quickly.
Performance iss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PedroGuerraPT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements for admins bypassing branch protections on github.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-enhancements-for-admins-bypassing-branch-protections-on-github-com</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-enhancements-for-admins-bypassing-branch-protections-on-github-com"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T17:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements for admins bypassing branch protections on github.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team Sync no longer invites or removes organization members by default]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-team-sync-no-longer-invites-or-removes-organization-members-by-default</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-team-sync-no-longer-invites-or-removes-organization-members-by-default"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T17:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team Sync no longer invites or removes organization members by default]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Create and share your own deployment protection rules for safe and controlled deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-github-actions-create-and-share-your-own-deployment-protection-rules-for-safe-and-controlled-deployments</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-20-github-actions-create-and-share-your-own-deployment-protection-rules-for-safe-and-controlled-deployments"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: Create and share your own deployment protection rules for safe and controlled deployments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Storing App Service application logs in Blob]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/storing-app-service-application-logs-in-blob/ba-p/3800963</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/storing-app-service-application-logs-in-blob/ba-p/3800963"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T09:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure provides built-in diagnostics to assist with debugging an App Service web app. The primary aim of this blog is to guide one step-by-step to add instrumentation to your application, as well as how to access the information logged.
 
Step 1:
Go to >App Service Logs> Enable Application Logging (Blob) and select the desired Blob Storage and the Container and select the Level of logging.
 

 
For more information on different types of logs you can refer this document.
 
Step 2:
Below is the code we have deployed a .Net Core MVC web application in a Windows App Service.
 
 
 public IActionResult Index()
        {
            _logger.LogInformation("This is a test to send logs to : Blob ");

            return View();
        }

        public IActionResult Privacy()
        {
            return View();
        }
 
 
Below are different level of logs details which you can log:
 

 




Note: If you write logs to blobs, the retention policy no longer applies if you delete the app but keep the logs in the blobs. For more information, see Costs that might accrue after resource deletion.




 
Step 3:
Go to Storage Account> Container and select the folder with your app service name and download the ( .txt ) file to check the logs.
 

 
The Blob option also includes additional information in the log messages, such as the ID of the origin VM instance of the log message (InstanceId), thread ID (Tid), and a more granular timestamp (EventTickCount) in a ( .csv ) file.
 
More information:

Enable diagnostics logging - Azure App Service | Microsoft Learn
azure-content/web-sites-enable-diagnostic-log.md at master · Huachao/azure-content · GitHub

 
If you have any other questions, feel free to comment below!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AmritpalSinghNaroo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pull request merge queue (public beta): API support and recent fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-19-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-19-pull-request-merge-queue-public-beta-api-support-and-recent-fixes"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T16:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we work towards general availability of pull request merge queue, we want to thank everyone that has provided feedback ❤ (keep it coming!) and let you know about some recent fixes and new API support. See the public beta announcement to learn more about merge queue and how it can help increase velocity by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[npm provenance public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-19-npm-provenance-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-19-npm-provenance-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T16:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[npm provenance public beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Istio-based service mesh add-on for Azure Kubernetes Service - Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/istio-based-service-mesh-add-on-for-azure-kubernetes-service/ba-p/3800229</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/istio-based-service-mesh-add-on-for-azure-kubernetes-service/ba-p/3800229"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern applications are typically architected as distributed collections of microservices, with each collection of microservices performing some discrete business function. This distributed microservices architecture allows multiple teams within large organizations to operate independently of each other and release new versions of their microservices at their own cadence. However, this requires an additional level of supervision to address observability, traffic management, and security use cases for service-to-service communication across these distributed workloads. This can be done by embedding logic directly within the application code of each microservice. Or it can be done in a transparent way using service mesh which deploys sidecars to application pods to achieve the same use cases…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shashankbarsin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Divine Intuition]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9572</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/a-divine-intuition/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T13:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under a secular mindset, intuition is all about you — your wants, needs, passions, and desires. A heavenly, God-inspired intuition is different.
The post A Divine Intuition appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open a private vulnerability report with REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-18-open-a-private-vulnerability-report-with-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-18-open-a-private-vulnerability-report-with-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T22:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open a private vulnerability report with REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where the Liberal Arts Went Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9564</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/where-the-liberal-arts-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve lost touch with the ultimate purpose of education: to transform our being and improve our character. The liberal arts are the ends, not the means.  
The post Where the Liberal Arts Went Wrong appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Hate Writing (and So Will You)]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9559</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/i-hate-writing/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T20:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I hate writing, it’s because I love it so much. An experienced writer is somebody who knows when the hatred is temporary.
The post I Hate Writing (and So Will You) appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Kubernetes upgrades and Long Term Support]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-kubernetes-upgrades-and-long-term-support/ba-p/3782789</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-kubernetes-upgrades-and-long-term-support/ba-p/3782789"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T07:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has long invested in the upstream Kubernetes community, and as our Azure team members have led and participated in the Kubernetes release process, we’ve listened to what our customers say about the pace of Kubernetes development. Today we are excited to announce the introduction of Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) Long Term Support (LTS).
 
We’re hearing from customers across a variety of organizations, from healthcare to manufacturing and beyond, who need a longer window of stability.  We’ve heard from ISVs that having to be on a constant treadmill to keep their environments in sync with community releases adds a significant burden to delivering value to their customers.
 
For organizations with multiple teams or complex environments, staying on top of upgrades can pose a signific…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Resource Graph Explorer for Microsoft.Web resources]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-resource-graph-explorer-for-microsoft-web-resources/ba-p/3798295</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-resource-graph-explorer-for-microsoft-web-resources/ba-p/3798295"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T06:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Resource Graph
 
Azure Resource Graph is an Azure service designed to extend Azure Resource Management by providing efficient and performant resource exploration with the ability to query at scale across a given set of subscriptions so that you can effectively govern your environment.
These queries provide the following abilities:

Query resources with complex filtering, grouping, and sorting by resource properties.
Explore resources iteratively based on governance requirements.
Assess the impact of applying policies in a vast cloud environment.
Query changes made to resource properties (preview).

Below are few resource types supported by Azure Resource Graph:
 

Microsoft.web/apimanagementaccounts
Microsoft.web/apimanagementaccounts/apis
Microsoft.web/certificates
Microsoft.Web/con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kalvp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Availability for Azure Active Directory (AD) Workload Identity on AKS]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-for-azure-active-directory-ad-workload/ba-p/3798292</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/general-availability-for-azure-active-directory-ad-workload/ba-p/3798292"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T06:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workload Identity is an open-source project that enables Federated Identity in Kubernetes clusters. It is the next evolution of a public preview feature in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), that is built on the now deprecated pod identity project. Azure AD Workload Identity, is simpler to use and replaces pod identity. Azure AD Workload Identity on AKS is now generally available so customers can run production workloads using Workload Identity on both Windows and Linux and migrate applications using Pod Identity over to Workload Identity. 
 
Azure AD Workload Identity leverages Service Account Token Volume Projection giving pods the ability to use a Kubernetes identity (service account), to which a Kubernetes token is issued and OIDC federation which enables Kubernetes applications to access Azure cloud resources securely with Azure Active Directory based on annotated service accounts.
 
Since the open-source pod identity project is now deprecated, AKS will continue to support the AKS pod identity through 2023. To ease the transition, customers can run Pod Identity and Workload Identity in parallel on an existing AKS cluster.  Please note that during the Public Preview we enabled the sidecar to give customers time to update their SDKs, but this is not a supported configuration for General Availability. We recommend that customers update applications to a list of supported SDKs that will allow applications to talk to the AAD endpoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MichaelWithrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage OpenCost on Azure Kubernetes Service to understand and monitor your infrastructure spend]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/leverage-opencost-on-azure-kubernetes-service-to-understand-and/ba-p/3796813</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/leverage-opencost-on-azure-kubernetes-service-to-understand-and/ba-p/3796813"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adopting Kubernetes, organizations can unlock a range of cost benefits. With workloads configured to consume only the necessary resources and dynamically scale to meet demand, businesses can optimize resource usage while reducing downtime. Additionally, Kubernetes allows organizations to deploy multiple applications from various teams or business units to a single cluster, resulting in significantly reduced infrastructure costs. However, this multitenancy approach poses a new challenge.
 
Consider this scenario: your cluster generates $100/day in infrastructure spend with a shared set of resources split across 10 developer teams. If 1 team consumes 80% of the cluster’s resources, it does not make sense to split infrastructure costs evenly across all teams at $10/day. Instead, your organ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kaysieyu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and bind the custom domain contains special Unicode character in App Service Using Azure CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/create-and-bind-the-custom-domain-contains-special-unicode/ba-p/3797564</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/create-and-bind-the-custom-domain-contains-special-unicode/ba-p/3797564"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T05:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview :
 
Azure App Service is an HTTP-based service for hosting web applications, REST APIs, and mobile back ends. 
 
Azure App Service provides a highly scalable, self-patching web hosting service. This blog shows you how to create and map the custom Domain Name System (DNS) name contains a special unicode character to App Service using Azure CLI.
 
Problem:
 
If you try to create and bind the custom domain containing special Unicode character in Azure App Service using Azure CLI with the below command it will throw the following error:
 
Azure CLI Command:
 
az appservice domain create --contact-info
                            --hostname
                            --resource-group
                            [--accept-terms]
                            [--auto-renew]
              …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guptatushar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed bug that allowed a hovercard URL to be used to display the name, description, and star count of any repository]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-fixed-bug-that-allowed-a-hovercard-url-to-be-used-to-display-the-name-description-and-star-count-of-any-repository</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-fixed-bug-that-allowed-a-hovercard-url-to-be-used-to-display-the-name-description-and-star-count-of-any-repository"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T20:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed bug that allowed a hovercard URL to be used to display the name, description, and star count of any repository]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organize Discussions Categories into Sections]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-organize-discussions-categories-into-sections</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-organize-discussions-categories-into-sections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T19:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organize Discussions Categories into Sections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable security features for multiple repositories from your organization-level security coverage page]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-enable-security-features-for-multiple-repositories-from-your-organization-level-security-coverage-page</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-enable-security-features-for-multiple-repositories-from-your-organization-level-security-coverage-page"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T17:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enable security features for multiple repositories from your organization-level security coverage page]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Repository Rules Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-introducing-repository-rules-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-introducing-repository-rules-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Repository Rules Public Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marking a threaded comment as the answer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-marking-a-threaded-comment-as-the-answer</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-marking-a-threaded-comment-as-the-answer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marking a threaded comment as the answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling AppServiceAppLogs & AppServiceHTTPLogs diagnostic settings in app services]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enabling-appserviceapplogs-amp-appservicehttplogs-diagnostic/ba-p/3793845</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enabling-appserviceapplogs-amp-appservicehttplogs-diagnostic/ba-p/3793845"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T13:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure provides built-in diagnostics to assist with debugging an App Service app. You can send your logs from your App Service to Storage Accounts, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics.
 
This blog will guide you step-by-step to enable AppServiceHTTPLogs , AppServiceAppLogs and view them in Log Analytics.
 
Step 1:
Go to Azure Portal > App Service > Diagnostic Settings and enable the required settings you would like to send to the destination . In this blog I have taken an example of HTTP Logs and App Service Application Logs in a Windows App Service ( .Net Core ).
 

 
You can refer this doc for more details on supported log types.
 
Step 2:
In your application code you can use the usual logging options and send log messages to application logs. By default, ASP.NET Core uses the Microsoft.Extensions.Logging.AzureAppServices logging provider. For more information, see ASP.NET Core logging in Azure.
 
Below is the code snippet of the logging I am doing in my .Net Core MVC webapp.
 

 
 
Step 3:
Go to Azure Portal > Log Analytics workspace > Logs and query the AppServiceAppLogs table and you can see the logs being sent. You can use different levels of logging such as Error, Information, Verbose and etc. in your application and this will show up in your logs in Log Analytics under the “Level” field. You can filter out logs based on the level:
 

 
Similarly, you can also query AppServiceHTTPLogs:
 

 
Sample Queries in Log Analytics:
 




AppServiceAppLogs
| where TimeGenerated >ago(10m)
 
AppServiceHTTPLogs
| where TimeGenerated >ago(10m)




 
 
More information:

AppServiceAppLogs is now available for ASP .NET apps on Windows - Azure App Service
App Service Integration with Azure Monitor (Preview) - Azure App Service
Enable diagnostics logging - Azure App Service | Microsoft Learn
Logging in .NET Core and ASP.NET Core | Microsoft Learn

 
If you have any other questions, feel free to comment below!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AmritpalSinghNaroo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation: Importing non-Git repositories with GitHub Importer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-deprecation-importing-non-git-repositories-with-github-importer</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-17-deprecation-importing-non-git-repositories-with-github-importer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T12:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation: Importing non-Git repositories with GitHub Importer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy app service with private endpoint enabled via Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploy-app-service-with-private-endpoint-enabled-via-azure/ba-p/3789370</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/deploy-app-service-with-private-endpoint-enabled-via-azure/ba-p/3789370"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T05:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a common scenario that customers want their app service being allocated inside private network and cannot be accessed by public network. Therefore, they usually enable private endpoint as well as configure Access Restriction to deny all the public traffic.
 
When the private endpoint is enabled and public traffic is denied to the web app, all the public traffic to this app is cut off. Since there is a range of IP addresses where agents are deployed, they have a public IP. Obviously, these agents are unable to reach web app.

 
As a solution, we can either allow the IP ranges list in the firewall or use self-hosted agents to deploy.
You may check below document for more information Microsoft-hosted-agents for Azure Pipelines
 
In below lab, we will demo 2 tests. One is what if we d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma_Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The one about AI]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2023/04/15/ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2023/04/15/ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like everyone, I’ve been thinking about AI. It’s already useful, in a way that the previous big thing, crypto, wasn’t. I don’t think it’ll become generalized AI - I think the AI winter cycle is the base case and human-like intelligence is qualitatively different than LLM, no matter how many terabytes of training data you throw at them. But that isn’t what this article is about.
No, it’s about other stuff, particularly technological change, happiness, and craft.


Optimists and pessimists agree that AI will change the world.
If it goes wrong, AI will continue to do a bad job suggesting sentences for criminals and promise, but fail, to diagnose cancer, and find its way into a lot of other jobs that it’s not qualified for – much like an overconfident young man, which is also its preferred wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Azure Extensions in VSCode.dev!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/new-azure-extensions-in-vscode-dev/ba-p/3795806</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/new-azure-extensions-in-vscode-dev/ba-p/3795806"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T20:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the release of 3 Azure Extensions to vscode.dev! These extensions are Azure Static Web Apps, Azure Container Apps, and Azure Resource Groups.
 
vscode.dev is a development tool that is a lightweight version of VSCode that runs fully in the browser. You can open a folder on your local machine and start coding immediately or type “.” in a GitHub repository and it takes you directly to vscode.dev without any installation required.
 
So you might be wondering, why vscode.dev? What can I do in the browser? There is quite a bit of functionality that’s available at your grasp and that is fully discussed in this in-depth article. But for now, we will focus on the 3 Azure extensions that just shipped in this tool.
 
vscode.dev - Azure Static Web Apps Extension
 
Azure Sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>meerahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java to the cloud in minutes: JBoss EAP on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-to-the-cloud-in-minutes-jboss-eap-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3745277</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/java-to-the-cloud-in-minutes-jboss-eap-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3745277"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T18:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Jakarta EE- and Java-based applications offer a number of benefits for developers, taking the time to prepare them for a cloud transition can be cost prohibitive. With Red Hat® JBoss® Enterprise Application Platform (JBoss EAP) on Azure App Service, minimal to no rework is required, enabling companies to seamlessly transition their existing apps to the cloud. In some cases, that transition could be made in as little as 30 minutes! But there’s more to JBoss EAP and App Service than just speed—it can transform your capabilities, too.  
 

 
Benefits of JBoss EAP
JBoss EAP allows you to take everything you already love about your Java or Jakarta EE applications and move to the cloud for improved speed and more advanced capabilities. One key feature is the ability to quickly and easily s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayunk Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote certificate is invalid when calling an external endpoint from web app]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/remote-certificate-is-invalid-when-calling-an-external-endpoint/ba-p/3785758</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/remote-certificate-is-invalid-when-calling-an-external-endpoint/ba-p/3785758"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T00:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using .NET code to resolve “Remote certificate is invalid” when multi-tenant web app is configured as client in client-server model.
 
You can implement the server thumbprint in the .NET application code to resolve “Remote certificate is invalid” when multi-tenant web app is configured as client in client-server model and making HTTS request to a server configured with a private CA.
 
When a web app acts as a client and makes an HTTPS call to an external server secured by a private CA, the web app uses its default installed trusted root CA’s public key to validate the server’s certificate. However, the remote server certificate is signed by a private CA, and since there is no such trusted CA in the web app’s trusted source list, it will not be validated by the web app. You cannot modify th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma_Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshoot Failed External Calls Between App Services Using AppServiceIPSecAuditLogs]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/troubleshoot-failed-external-calls-between-app-services-using/ba-p/3793204</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/troubleshoot-failed-external-calls-between-app-services-using/ba-p/3793204"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service is a cloud-based service that allows developers to deploy and manage web applications. It provides an easy way to host your web applications without worrying about the underlying infrastructure. Sometimes, you may face issues when making external calls between two App Services. In this blog post, we will discuss how to troubleshoot failed external calls between App Services using the App Service IP Sec audit logs.
 
App Service IP Sec audit logs provide detailed information about the traffic that passes through your IPsec tunnel. This information can be used to troubleshoot issues related to failed external calls between App Services. The audit logs provide details such as source IP address, destination IP address, protocol, and port number.
 
Azure Monitor Logs reference…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ronelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic rebases on Dependabot pull requests stop after 30 days of inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-automatic-rebases-on-dependabot-pull-requests-stop-after-30-days-of-inactivity</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-automatic-rebases-on-dependabot-pull-requests-stop-after-30-days-of-inactivity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T19:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic rebases on Dependabot pull requests stop after 30 days of inactivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository topics and team filters for enterprise-level Dependabot, secret scanning, and code scanning pages]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-repository-topics-and-team-filters-for-enterprise-level-dependabot-secret-scanning-and-code-scanning-pages"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now filter by repository topic or team on the enterprise-level Dependabot, code scanning, and secret scanning pages in security overview. These improvements have shipped to GitHub.com and will be available in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9. Learn more security overview and send us your feedback Learn more about GitHub Advanced Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Logic Apps plans: Consumption based vs Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-logic-apps-plans-consumption-based-vs-standard/ba-p/3793997</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-logic-apps-plans-consumption-based-vs-standard/ba-p/3793997"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T17:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Logic App is an integration service. It provides you the opportunity to create and run automated workflows that integrates with your application, data, services and systems etc. These workflows can be written with little to no code. While creating a logic apps, when we come across the logic apps plan, there are two choices. 

Standard 
Consumption based

This is an attempt to help make a decision by comparing both the plans at a high-level. Hopefully, this will be helpful and help me achieve my goal.
 



 
Consumption based
Standard


Pricing Plan
Pay only for usage
Based on a hosting plan


Hosting Infrastructure
Multi-tenant/Shared
Single tenant


Best suited for
Entry-level, ad-hoc, for limited use
Enterprise level


Number of workflows
1
Multiple


Virtual Network and Private Endpoint Support
No
Yes


VNET Integration 
No
Yes


Network Isolation
No
Yes



Billing

Trigger and action operations

 
 
 

Storage operations




Per execution, after free built-in operations.
Managed connector operations, per call




Unlimited, included in the plan.
Managed connector operations, per call




Charges applies only to data retention related storage consumption.
Any storage operation run by logic app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>umeshpanwar1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now supports fetching release notes and changelogs for Docker images]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-dependabot-now-supports-fetching-release-notes-and-changelogs-for-docker-images</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-13-dependabot-now-supports-fetching-release-notes-and-changelogs-for-docker-images"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now supports fetching release notes and changelogs for Docker images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Functions with MongoDB Atlas in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-azure-functions-with-mongodb-atlas-in-java/ba-p/3795163</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-azure-functions-with-mongodb-atlas-in-java/ba-p/3795163"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing is one of the most discussed topics in the tech industry. Having the ability to scale your infrastructure up and down instantly is just one of the many benefits associated with serverless apps. In this article, we are going write the function as a service (FaaS) — i.e., a serverless function that will interact with data via a database, to produce meaningful results. FaaS can also be very useful in A/B testing when you want to quickly release an independent function without going into actual implementation or release. In this article, you'll learn how to use MongoDB Atlas, a cloud database, when you're getting started with Azure functions in Java.
 
Prerequisites
 

A Microsoft Azure account that we will be using for running and deploying our serverless function. If you don'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Month in Azure Container Apps: March/April 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/this-month-in-azure-container-apps-march-april-2023/ba-p/3794238</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/this-month-in-azure-container-apps-march-april-2023/ba-p/3794238"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T01:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first monthly Azure Container Apps newsletter! We'll share the latest news and community highlights for Container Apps every month here on the Apps on Azure blog.
 
Azure Container Apps monthly community live stream
 
Our next live stream is April 13, 2023 at 11:00AM PDT (18:00 UTC). Join us to discuss our big announcements this month!
 



 
Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
 
Community highlights
 

.NET Azure Container Apps workshop
Deploy Container Apps with Pulumi and Go
Start from zero and scale to zero – Azure Spring Apps consumption plan
Learn Live – Azure Container Options - YouTube
Ask the Expert: Deploying a Python Project with Azure Container Apps - YouTube
Azure Policy for Azure Container Apps? Yes, please - Microsoft Community Hub
Simplifying deploying Azure Container Apps to Arc enabled Kubernetes using az containerapp up - Microsoft Community Hub
Using Azure Container Apps at scale instead of building your own NaaS on top of K8s?

 
Product news
 

Public Preview: New Azure Container Apps Pricing Plan and Enhanced Networking
Generally Available: Azure Monitor integration with Azure Container Apps
Generally Available: Mount Azure Files and ephemeral storage in Azure Container Apps
Public Preview: Session Affinity in Azure Container Apps
Public Preview: Azure Key Vault references in Container Apps secrets
New: Azure Container Apps environment now shows current Dapr and KEDA versions
New: HTTP service discovery via app name

 
For more, check out our product roadmap.
 
Get notified when we publish future newsletters, subscribe to the Apps on Azure blog. Connect with the Azure Container Apps team on GitHub, Twitter, and Discord.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets leaked historically in issues]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-leaked-historically-in-issues</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-secret-scanning-now-detects-secrets-leaked-historically-in-issues"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T21:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now detects secrets leaked historically in issues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Improved scaling model for Azure Functions with Target Based Scaling]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-improved-scaling-model-for-azure-functions-with-target-based-scaling</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-improved-scaling-model-for-azure-functions-with-target-based-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling improvement for Service Bus, Event Hubs, Storage Queue, and Cosmos DB is now available for the Azure Functions Consumption and Premium plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Azure Functions V4 programming model for Node.js]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-azure-functions-v4-programming-model-for-nodejs</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-azure-functions-v4-programming-model-for-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a more intuitive and idiomatic experience for JavaScript and TypeScript developers writing Azure Functions apps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Availability:  App Configuration geo-replication]]></title>
        <id>general-availability-app-configuration-georeplication</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/general-availability-app-configuration-georeplication/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Replicate your application configuration data across supported regions to create redundancy, reduce latency, and distribute request load.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps Announces New Pricing Plan and Enhanced Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-announces-new-pricing-plan-and-enhanced/ba-p/3790723</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-announces-new-pricing-plan-and-enhanced/ba-p/3790723"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Microsoft announced the public preview of a new plan and pricing structure for Azure Container Apps (ACA). This structure is designed to adapt compute options to individual apps and microservices components for more flexible microservices solutions. Azure Container Apps now supports a Dedicated plan in addition to the existing serverless Consumption plan.
 
The Dedicated plan guarantees single tenancy and specialized compute options including memory-optimized choices. In addition, the new Dedicated plan runs in the same Azure Container Apps environment as the serverless Consumption plan. This allows apps or microservice components that may have different resource requirements depending on component purpose or development stack to run in the same Azure Container Apps environment.  An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Morton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM with the REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-generate-an-sbom-with-the-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-generate-an-sbom-with-the-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T16:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SBOM with the REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook forwarding in the GitHub CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-webhook-forwarding-in-the-github-cli</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-webhook-forwarding-in-the-github-cli"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T13:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webhook forwarding in the GitHub CLI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning default setup is available for Go]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-code-scanning-default-setup-is-available-for-go</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-12-code-scanning-default-setup-is-available-for-go"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T10:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning default setup is available for Go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost efficiency with Power Platform and Azure APIM]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-apim/ba-p/3793182</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-apim/ba-p/3793182"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T23:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of cloud computing, mobile devices, and the Internet of Things (IoT), APIs have become more important than ever, and their use has increased tremendously in recent years. APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, are the mechanisms that enable different software systems to communicate and interact with each other seamlessly. They allow developers to build flexible, integrated solutions that leverage data and functionality from multiple sources. This, in turn, enables businesses to deliver more personalized, efficient, and innovative services to employees, partners, and customers.
 
With the ability for software systems to communicate with each other comes the need for an efficient platform that can handle the integration of different applications and services. That’s why w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sonjagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost efficiency with Power Platform and Azure API Management]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-api-management/ba-p/3793182</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/boost-efficiency-with-power-platform-and-azure-api-management/ba-p/3793182"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T23:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of cloud computing, mobile devices, and the Internet of Things (IoT), APIs have become more important than ever, and their use has increased tremendously in recent years. APIs, or Application Programming Interfaces, are the mechanisms that enable different software systems to communicate and interact with each other seamlessly. They allow developers to build flexible, integrated solutions that leverage data and functionality from multiple sources. This, in turn, enables businesses to deliver more personalized, efficient, and innovative services to employees, partners, and customers.
 
With the ability for software systems to communicate with each other comes the need for an efficient platform that can handle the integration of different applications and services. That’s why w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sonjagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metadata for active GitHub tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-secret-scanning-now-shows-metadata-for-active-github-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-secret-scanning-now-shows-metadata-for-active-github-tokens"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T21:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metadata for active GitHub tokens]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository archive date in GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-repository-archive-date-in-graphql-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-repository-archive-date-in-graphql-api"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T20:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository archive date in GraphQL API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting on files in a pull request is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-commenting-on-files-in-a-pull-request-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-11-commenting-on-files-in-a-pull-request-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting on files in a pull request is now generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 10, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1399-april-10-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1399-april-10-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T00:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We rolled out an update fixing a bunch of annoyances.  The main theme for this month is improving search quality and we are working on implementing new search sources.
 

In the upcoming months we will be trying to remove as many "limits" in our existing pricing plans and simplifying them as much as possible.
Family plan roll-out has been successful and we are pleased that many families around the world are enjoying benefits of ad-free and safe search for their loved ones. If you have not yet, check out Family plan features.
 


Kagi Search
"Visit Original URL" should be below the other two options #1295 @Browsing6853 
Summarize Page now follows Kagi interface language #1373 @peterdussaud
Summarize Results does not reappear for new queries #1346 @httpjames 
Unexpected behavior on malformed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage caches in your Actions workflows from Web Interface]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-10-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-10-manage-caches-in-your-actions-workflows-from-web-interface"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caching dependencies and other commonly reused files enables developers to speed up their GitHub Actions workflows and make them more efficient. We have now enabled Cache Management from the web interface to enable developers to get more transparency and control over their cache usage within their GitHub repositories. Actions users who use actions/cache can now: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated and customized dashboards for Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automated-and-customized-dashboards-for-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3786891</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automated-and-customized-dashboards-for-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3786891"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T12:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of you have been leveraging Azure Load Testing (ALT) to evaluate how your applications respond to high scale load and get actionable insights to fix performance bottlenecks. If you haven’t started yet, you can get started and run your first load test in less than 10 minutes.
 
Azure Load Testing (ALT) provides a unified dashboard of test statistics, client-side metrics, and server-side metrics so that the performance bottlenecks can be easily identified. While the out of the box dashboard is helpful in most scenarios, you might want the load test results to be available in a tool of your choice –

You have a dashboard to monitor multiple aspects of service reliability and you want to see load test results in that dashboard.
You want to observe the trend of specific metrics across test…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nagarjuna_V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup Multisite in WordPress on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-setup-multisite-in-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3791071</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-setup-multisite-in-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/3791071"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T08:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try WordPress on Azure App Service here:

 
What is WordPress Multisite?
 
WordPress Multisite is a feature of WordPress that enables you to run and manage multiple WordPress websites using the same WordPress installation. You could update multiple websites in a single click by using the parent WordPress dashboard, and even manage individual sites through their individual dashboards. This feature was previously called WordPress Multi-User.
 
For example, a multinational e-commerce store can create multiple country-specific subsites in the same WordPress installation using this feature. The root admin can install plugins and themes required for all the websites at once. They can also assign different admins to each subsite. A lot of our customers use the multisite feature for various scenar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notifications for Team @mentions can now be disabled]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-07-notifications-for-team-mentions-can-now-be-disabled"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team Maintainers may now disable notifications resulting from a team @mention in GitHub issue and pull request comments through an optional configuration in the team settings page. Notifications resulting from PR review requests are unaffected by this setting. Existing issue and PR subscriptions are also unaffected. This team setting will also be exposed via API. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redirect from the non WWW domain to the WWW domain in the Azure WordPress Market Place offering-]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/redirect-from-the-non-www-domain-to-the-www-domain-in-the-azure/ba-p/3790022</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/redirect-from-the-non-www-domain-to-the-www-domain-in-the-azure/ba-p/3790022"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T13:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Navigate to your App Service via the Azure Portal. Under the Development Tools section, select SSH then Go -->.

 
2. Modify the default site config - You would need to make a copy of the existing configuration and place the file inside the /home/site directory by running the below command.
 
 
cp /etc/nginx/conf.d/default.conf /home/site/default
 
 
 

 

Go to https://<app name>.scm.azurewebsites.net/newui/fileManager click on Modify site/default file.


 

in the existing server block update the server name to www domain

 
 
server {

        listen 80;

        ## Your website name goes here.

        server_name www.example.com
 
 
 

In the same default.conf file, you can create a new server block and add the below configurations for non-www to www redirection -

 
 
server {

    listen 80;

    server_name example.com;

    return 301 $scheme://www.example.com$request_uri;

}
 
 
 
// This directive tells Nginx to send any request //for http://example.com to http://www.example.com with HTTP redirect code 301.

Copy the following code snippet to /home/dev/startup.sh.

 
 
cp /home/site/default /etc/nginx/conf.d/default.conf 

/usr/sbin/nginx -s reload
 
 
 

Please restart App Service and verify that the redirect from non www domain to www domain works fine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun_Baliga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running cronjobs in Azure App Service Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/running-cronjobs-in-azure-app-service-linux/ba-p/3789879</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/running-cronjobs-in-azure-app-service-linux/ba-p/3789879"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T08:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To schedule a cronjob on azure app service Linux web application you can follow the steps outlined below,
 

 
Navigate to “SSH” from azure app services portal and click on Go ->
 

 

 
Create a script file in /home with name as start.sh and add the below lines to the script file and save the file.
Command to create a script file - touch /home/start.sh
Open the file using vim editor: vi /home/start.sh and copy the below code
 
# Installing cron 
apt-get update -qq && apt-get install cron -yqq 
# Starting cron 
service cron start 
#cron scheduler 
(crontab -l 2>/dev/null; echo "* * * * * find /home/BackupLogs -type f -size 1k -delete ")|crontab
 
Post that, you can add the created script as a startup command which would install the cron, start the cron and schedule the cron during startup. To add as a startup command, navigate to Azure portal -> Configuration blade -> General settings tab and provide as below,
 
 

 
 
In the above sample code, it checks for all the files with size 1KB in /home/BackupLogs and delete them for every minute.
 
Based on your convenience you can adjust the CRON scheduler time and command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>karthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects – April 6th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-06-github-issues-projects-april-6th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-06-github-issues-projects-april-6th-update"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T18:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects - April 6th update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Crypto News Website in C# using the Microsoft Azure App Service and MongoDB Atlas]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-a-crypto-news-website-in-c-using-the-microsoft-azure/ba-p/3789523</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/building-a-crypto-news-website-in-c-using-the-microsoft-azure/ba-p/3789523"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who said creating a website has to be hard? Writing the code, persisting news, hosting the website. A decade ago this might have been a lot of work. These days, thanks to Microsoft Blazor, Microsoft Azure App Service, and MongoDB Atlas you can get started in minutes. And finish it equally fast!
 
In this tutorial I will walk you through:
 

setting up a new Blazor project,
creating a new page with a simple UI,
creating data in MongoDB Atlas,
showing those news on the website and
making the website available by using Azure App Service to host it.

 
All you need is this tutorial and the following pre-requisites, but if you prefer to just read along for now, check out the GitHub repository for this tutorial where you can find the code and the tutorial.
 
Pre-requisites for this tutorial
 
Be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambitious People Need Each Other]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9540</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/ambitious-people-need-each-other/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ambitious people don’t just need peers. They need mentors. They need people who will encourage them to pursue hard and meaningful projects. 
The post Ambitious People Need Each Other appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use WebP Images on Azure WordPress Managed Offering]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-webp-images-on-azure-wordpress-managed-offering/ba-p/3789326</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-use-webp-images-on-azure-wordpress-managed-offering/ba-p/3789326"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T14:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your WordPress Managed offering, go to webssh of your SCM site -  https://<app name>.scm.azurewebsites.net/webssh/host
Install the GD extension with Webp support using the below command.

apk add --no-cache --virtual .build-deps autoconf pkgconfig gcc g++ gawk make zlib-dev libpng-dev libwebp-dev \
&& docker-php-ext-configure gd --with-webp \
&& docker-php-ext-install gd \
&& apk del .build-deps
Copy the newly installed gd.so file to a persistent file storage. 
mkdir -p /home/dev/extensions
cp /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20200930/gd.so /home/dev/extensions/gd.so
 

Now write a post-startup script to restore the updated copy of gd.so everytime the app starts.

Edit the startup script file in /home/dev directory using the below command: 
vi /home/dev/startup.sh
Then add the following command to the startup.sh file and save it (type :wq to save).
 
cp /home/dev/extensions/gd.so /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20200930/gd.so 
 

Now restart your app from Azure Portal and you can upload a sample .webp image to test the changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun_Baliga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned navigation available in Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-05-redesigned-navigation-available-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-05-redesigned-navigation-available-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T16:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned navigation available in Public Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Cache Retrieval Failures on Azure App Service - Node-Cache Example]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/addressing-cache-retrieval-failures-on-azure-app-service-node/ba-p/3786901</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/addressing-cache-retrieval-failures-on-azure-app-service-node/ba-p/3786901"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T01:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently encountered an issue when attempting to read cache values using the Node-Cache module on an app service running on multiple instances. However, the module worked fine on my local environment, single virtual machine, or single-instance app service.
 
This behavior occurs because Node-Cache and other private cache solutions are designed to store data in the memory of a single process. The private cache works properly when running on a single instance, as all requests are handled by the same process and have access to the same cache.
 

However, in a multi-instance environment like a multi-instance App Service, using a private cache can lead to inconsistent behavior and data inconsistency.
 
For example, you save a value in one cache in an instance. Then, a request tries to read th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yorkzhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding the Triage role and introducing new options for how content is reported]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-expanding-the-triage-role-and-introducing-new-options-for-how-content-is-reported</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-expanding-the-triage-role-and-introducing-new-options-for-how-content-is-reported"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T19:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding the Triage role and introducing new options for how content is reported]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export your sponsorable dependencies and sponsor many in one checkout]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-export-your-sponsorable-dependencies-and-sponsor-many-in-one-checkout</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-export-your-sponsorable-dependencies-and-sponsor-many-in-one-checkout"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Export your sponsorable dependencies and sponsor many in one checkout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling for Demand: Deploying Python Applications Using MongoDB Atlas on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/scaling-for-demand-deploying-python-applications-using-mongodb/ba-p/3786792</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/scaling-for-demand-deploying-python-applications-using-mongodb/ba-p/3786792"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing large amounts of data locally can prove to be a challenge, especially as the amount of saved data grows. Fortunately, there is an efficient solution available. By utilizing the features of Flask, MongoDB Atlas, and Azure App Service, you can build and host powerful web applications that are capable of storing and managing tons of data in a centralized, secure, and scalable manner. Say goodbye to unreliable local files and hello to a scalable solution.
 
This in-depth tutorial will teach you how to build a functional CRUD (Create, Read, Update, and Delete) Flask application that connects to a MongoDB Atlas database, and is hosted on Azure App Service. Using Azure App Service and MongoDB together can be a great way to build and host web applications. Azure App Service makes it easy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>denverbrittain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning adds support for C# 11 / .NET 7]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-code-scanning-adds-support-for-c-11-net-7</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-04-code-scanning-adds-support-for-c-11-net-7"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T08:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning adds support for C# 11 / .NET 7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surrendering to Your Nature]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9525</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/surrendering-to-your-nature/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T19:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mark of maturity is surrendering to the person you actually are instead of the one you wish you were. 
The post Surrendering to Your Nature appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API requests are available via audit log streaming – Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-03-api-requests-are-available-via-audit-log-streaming-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-04-03-api-requests-are-available-via-audit-log-streaming-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T18:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API requests are available via audit log streaming - Public Beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price reduction in Hosting Plans for WordPress on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/price-reduction-in-hosting-plans-for-wordpress-on-azure-app/ba-p/3786290</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/price-reduction-in-hosting-plans-for-wordpress-on-azure-app/ba-p/3786290"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T17:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Database for MySQL – Flexible Server announced a new feature: Autoscale IOPS in October 2022. With this feature enabled, you do not need to pre-provision IOPs. The Flexible server automatically scales IO up and down depending on the workload. You can save on your costs as you do not have to pay for the resources you are not fully using. Read about the announcement here: Announcing Autoscale IOPS (Public Preview) for Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server
 
WordPress on Azure App Service is taking advantage of Autoscale IOPS and Storage auto-grow features of Azure Database for MySQL to provide you with more cost-effective hosting plans. Read more about these features here: Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server service tiers
 
Updated Hosting Plans:
 




Hosting Plan


WebApp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add MIME Types to Nginx - Linux App Service (PHP 8.x blessed image)]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-mime-types-to-nginx-linux-app-service-php-8-x-blessed-image/ba-p/3786096</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/add-mime-types-to-nginx-linux-app-service-php-8-x-blessed-image/ba-p/3786096"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T15:18:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIME types describe the media type of content, either in email, or served by web servers or web applications. They are intended to help provide a hint as to how the content should be processed and displayed.
Examples of MIME types:

text/html for HTML documents.
text/plain for plain text.
text/css for Cascading Style Sheets.
text/javascript for JavaScript files.
text/markdown for Markdown files.
application/octet-stream for binary files where user action is expected.

Server default configurations vary wildly and set different default MIME-type values for files with no defined content type. As new content types are invented or added to web servers, the users may fail to add the new MIME types to their web server's configuration. This is a major source of problems for users of browsers that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shuanand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository topics and team filters for organization-level Dependabot, secret scanning, and code scanning pages]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-repository-topics-and-team-filters-for-organization-level-dependabot-secret-scanning-and-code-scanning-pages"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T00:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now filter by repository topic or team on the organization-level Dependabot, code scanning, and secret scanning pages in security overview. These improvements have shipped to GitHub.com and will be available in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.9. Learn more security overview and send us your feedback Learn more about GitHub Advanced Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2023/04/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2023/04/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weather is starting to get better.
Listening
Gift from the Trees by Mammal Hands

I am still really loving the constellation of bands around
Mammal Hands. They just released
a new album, “Gift from the Trees”, and it’s really excellent.
RETURN by tAKX

Their guitarist, Stephen Mullins, also just released an excellent
album that has more of a Fennesz
direction - guitar-based ambient.
Watching
Of course I watched Succession, and it was good. I also watched
four movies - the best being Nope,
which delivered on all the levels. The rest were more uneven:
The Neon Demon is
a “vibes movie”, Triangle of Sadness
was sort of an overdone, kind of tedious satire, and I disliked
how much I liked This is the End.
It started sometime in the pandemic, but my already-bad taste in movies
has gotten even…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server connector’s V1 actions and triggers will be retired on 31 March 2024 – transition to SQL Server connector’s V2 actions and triggers]]></title>
        <id>sql-server-connector-s-v1-actions-and-triggers-will-be-retired-on-31-march-2024-transition-to-sql-server-connector-s-v2-actio</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/sql-server-connector-s-v1-actions-and-triggers-will-be-retired-on-31-march-2024-transition-to-sql-server-connector-s-v2-actio/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T23:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Server connector’s V1 actions and triggers will be retired on 31 March 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 31, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1371-march-31-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1371-march-31-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T22:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Family Plan
We are happy to announce the launch of Kagi Family Plans!
Read everything about it in our blog post Ad-Free Search for Families: Introducing the Kagi Family Plan.
Universal Summarizer
 

Muriel, our best-in-class model, is now available to API users.
Connect Universal Summarizer to 5,000 other apps with the fresh Zapier integration.
Added support for summarizing PowerPoint files (pptx). 
Added cache param to the API to control how are summaries handled (privacy friendly option). 
Added privacy policy for the Universal Summarizer.
Fix: AI Summarizer doesn't work with Thai #1315 @whs 
Fix: Unable to summarize English Wikipedia #1357 @whs 
Fix: Universal Summarizer fails on mp3 with error message 'No summary available at this moment, please try again later.' #1358 @AC2
 


New
Add…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metrics for custom patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-secret-scanning-now-shows-metrics-for-custom-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-secret-scanning-now-shows-metrics-for-custom-patterns"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T17:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now shows metrics for custom patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice for npm PGP signatures]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-deprecation-notice-for-npm-pgp-signatures</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-31-deprecation-notice-for-npm-pgp-signatures"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T14:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice for npm PGP signatures]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Actually Listen]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9507</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/learning-to-actually-listen/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T14:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been listening the wrong way my entire life — with just my ears. True listening is a totalizing, full-body experience.
The post Learning to Actually Listen appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mar 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/1369-mar-30-2023/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/1369-mar-30-2023/1"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T04:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To everyone waiting for the launch of the Kagi Family plan - we expect it to happen before noon PST on Friday.  Sorry for the delay.
We will be also enabling EUR payments and additional payment methods.
 

Thank you for your patience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository security advisories REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-repository-security-advisories-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-repository-security-advisories-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T20:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository security advisories REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensitivity Isn’t Static]]></title>
        <id>https://perell.com/?post_type=note&amp;p=9501</id>
        <link href="https://perell.com/note/sensitivity-isnt-static/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sensitivity of our senses ebbs and flows. If you’re looking to be more perceptive, start by changing your environment.
The post Sensitivity Isn’t Static appeared first on David Perell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Perell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Organizations with REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-delete-organizations-with-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-delete-organizations-with-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T17:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delete Organizations with REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAMLIdentity GraphQL object now supports `read` scope]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-samlidentity-graphql-object-now-supports-read-scope</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-03-30-samlidentity-graphql-object-now-supports-read-scope"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T14:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAMLIdentity GraphQL object now supports `read` scope]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>