<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2021-07-01T21:12:17.049Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consuming a diet with more fish fats, less vegetable oils can reduce migraine headaches, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630213035.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630213035.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T01:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A diet higher in fatty fish helped frequent migraine sufferers reduce their monthly number of headaches and intensity of pain compared to participants on a diet higher in vegetable-based fats and oils, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep your friends close, cortisol levels low for life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630173629.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630173629.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T21:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interdisciplinary team has determined that older adult women converse more effectively with strangers than their younger counterparts; additionally, communicating with female friends decreases stress hormone levels for women across the lifespan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5-minute breathing workout lowers blood pressure as much as exercise, drugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630135033.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630135033.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T17:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that a breathing exercise known as Inspiratory Muscle Strength Training can reduce blood pressure in weeks, with benefits on par with daily exercise or medication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers look to human 'social sensors' to better predict elections and other trends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115436.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115436.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers can gather highly accurate information about social trends and groups by asking about a person's social circle rather than interrogating their own individual beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eating disorder behaviors alter reward response in brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115345.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630115345.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study found that eating disorder behaviors alter the brain's reward response process and food intake control circuitry, which can reinforce the behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Southern diet - fried foods and sugary drinks - may raise risk of sudden cardiac death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630091407.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210630091407.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T13:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Participants in a large-scale study who more commonly consumed a Southern-style diet - high in added fats, fried foods, processed meats and sugary drinks - had a higher risk of sudden cardiac death than people who had lower adherence to a Southern-style diet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A promising new pathway to treating type 2 diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191737.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629191737.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T23:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers believe the liver may hold the key to new, preventative Type 2 diabetes treatments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success in reversing dementia in mice sets the stage for human clinical trials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629120756.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210629120756.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a new treatment candidate that appears to not only halt neurodegenerative symptoms in mouse models of dementia and Alzheimer's disease, but also reverse the effects of the disorders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers question prevailing Alzheimer's theory with new discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170605.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170605.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts estimate more than 6 million Americans are living with Alzheimer's dementia. But a recent study sheds new light on the disease and a highly debated new drug therapy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GluN3A knockout mouse: Alternative model for Alzheimer's neurodegeneration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170459.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628170459.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T21:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GluN3A-deficient mice display all aspects of Alzheimer's neurodegeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love: How the feeling of power determines happy relationships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628132145.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628132145.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T17:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to have a happy relationship? Make sure both partners feel they can decide on issues that are important to them. Objective power measured by income, for example, doesn't seem to play a big role, according to a new study. Instead, how lovers perceive power dynamics in their relationship is most important for relationship satisfaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists develop simple blood test for early detection of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628124947.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210628124947.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T16:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An international research team has developed a simple but robust blood test from Chinese patient data for early detection and screening of Alzheimer's disease (AD) with an accuracy level of over 96%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having the same nurse for home health visits may prevent rehospitalization for people with dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210625120428.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210625120428.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T16:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People with dementia receiving home health care visits are less likely to be readmitted to the hospital when there is consistency in nursing staff, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early findings of Alzheimer's study in diverse populations now available to researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624200440.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624200440.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A growing trove of data to help scientists understand the biology of Alzheimer's disease among diverse populations within the context of sociocultural, behavioral and environmental factors is now available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find health benefits of Connecticut-grown sugar kelp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624152650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624152650.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have reported significant findings supporting the nutritional benefits of Connecticut-grown sugar kelp. They found brown sugar kelp (Saccharina latissima) inhibits hepatic inflammation and fibrosis in a mouse model of diet-induced non-alcoholic steatohepatitis, a fatty liver disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serving larger portions of veggies may increase young kids' veggie consumption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624135551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624135551.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be difficult to get young kids to eat enough vegetables, but a new study found that simply adding more veggies to their plates resulted in children consuming more vegetables at the meal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potato and rice protein shakes may be a viable vegan alternative to whey protein shakes, research suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114501.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114501.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study found that plant-based protein shakes may be potential viable alternatives to milk-based whey protein shakes, particularly in people with need of careful monitoring of glucose levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting the day off with chocolate could have unexpected benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study of postmenopausal women has found that eating a concentrated amount of chocolate during a narrow window of time in the morning may help the body burn fat and decrease blood sugar levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting the day off with chocolate could have unexpected benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114358.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study of postmenopausal women has found that eating a concentrated amount of chocolate during a narrow window of time in the morning may help the body burn fat and decrease blood sugar levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists may need to rethink which genes control aging, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114334.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114334.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers fed fruit flies antibiotics and monitored the lifetime activity of hundreds of genes that scientists have traditionally thought control aging. To their surprise, the antibiotics not only extended the lives of the flies but also dramatically changed the activity of many of these genes. Their results suggested that only about 30% of the genes traditionally associated with aging set an animal's internal clock while the rest reflect the body's response to bacteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-invasive potential treatment for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114329.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210624114329.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultrasound can overcome some of the detrimental effects of ageing and dementia without the need to cross the blood-brain barrier, researchers have found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melatonin in mice: there's more to this hormone than sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141703.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141703.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have created a mouse model that allows the study of naturally occurring melatonin. Experiments using the new mice showed that natural melatonin was linked to a pre-hibernation state that allows mice to slow down their metabolism and survive when food is scarce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Multi-kingdom dialogue' between internal, external microbiota]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141700.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141700.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have identified an internal communication network in mammals that may regulate tissue repair and inflammation, providing new insights on how diseases such as obesity and inflammatory skin disorders develop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dieting and its effect on the gut microbiome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141657.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141657.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers were able to show for the first time that a very low calorie diet significantly alters the composition of the microbiota present in the human gut. The researchers report that dieting results in an increase of specific bacteria - notably Clostridioides difficile, which is associated with antibiotic-induced diarrhea and colitis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western high-fat diet can cause chronic pain, according to new study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141644.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623141644.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A typical Western high-fat diet can increase the risk of painful disorders common in people with conditions such as diabetes or obesity, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein linked to heart health, disease a potential therapeutic target for dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623095247.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623095247.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have found that high levels of a normal protein associated with reduced heart disease also protect against Alzheimer's-like damage in mice, opening up new approaches to slowing or stopping brain damage and cognitive decline in people with Alzheimer's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An unexpected discovery: Inflammatory proteins may slow cognitive decline in aging adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091307.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091307.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new study researchers report that elevated levels of two chemical mediators of inflammation, known as cytokines, are associated with slower cognitive decline in aging adults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starchy snacks may increase CVD risk; fruits and veggies at certain meals decreases risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091210.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091210.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eating fruits with lunch, vegetables at dinner and a dairy snack in the evening was associated with a reduced risk of early death by cardiovascular disease (CVD) and all-cause mortality, according to a study of U.S. adults. Eating a Western lunch (typically containing a high quantity of refined grains, cheese and cured meat) was associated with an elevated risk of CVD and all-cause mortalities in the same study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recycling of the eye's light sensors is faulty in progressive blindness of older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091145.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091145.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the National Eye Institute reporting that about 11 million older adults in the U.S. endure a condition that leads to progressive blindness, known as age-related macular degeneration, researchers are starting to understand what goes wrong in the disease, in order to develop new therapies to treat it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subconscious changes in movement may predict Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research team found that FMAR was associated with preclinical AD pathology in women, suggesting that FMAR may be a new biomarker for AD before cognitive symptoms begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subconscious changes in movement may predict Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210623091131.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research team found that FMAR was associated with preclinical AD pathology in women, suggesting that FMAR may be a new biomarker for AD before cognitive symptoms begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rap1 controls the body's sugar levels from the brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a mechanism in a small area of the brain that regulates whole-body glucose balance without affecting body weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rap1 controls the body's sugar levels from the brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622162930.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a mechanism in a small area of the brain that regulates whole-body glucose balance without affecting body weight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching from Western diet to a balanced diet may reduce skin, joint inflammation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622161046.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622161046.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T20:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diet rich in sugar and fat leads to disruption in the gut's microbial culture and contributes to inflammatory skin diseases such as psoriasis. Research shows that switching to a more balanced diet restores the gut's health and suppresses inflammation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's true: Stress does turn hair gray (and it's reversible)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622154339.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622154339.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T19:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study offers quantitative evidence linking psychological stress to graying hair in people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personality traits relate to being a morning or evening person]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123338.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123338.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The link between the different hierarchies of personality, sleep patterns and even genetics has now been discovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secretin hormone induces satiation by activating brown fat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new mechanism controlling satiation. According to the recently published study, the hormone secretin induces satiation by activating brown adipose tissue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secretin hormone induces satiation by activating brown fat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123242.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new mechanism controlling satiation. According to the recently published study, the hormone secretin induces satiation by activating brown adipose tissue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running to music combats mental fatigue, study suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123235.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210622123235.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Listening to music while running might be the key to improving people's performance when they feel mentally fatigued a study suggests. The performance of runners who listened to a self-selected playlist after completing a demanding thinking task was at the same level as when they were not mentally fatigued, the research found. The study is the first to investigate the effect of listening to music playlists on endurance running capacity and performance when mentally fatigued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New position statement declares that sleep is essential to health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621174109.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621174109.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:41:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new position statement emphasizes that sleep is a biological necessity, and insufficient sleep and untreated sleep disorders are detrimental for health, well-being, and public safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to pollutants, increased free-radical damage speeds up aging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621160520.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621160520.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T20:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study suggests that unrepaired DNA damage can increase the speed of aging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Managed HSM is generally available]]></title>
        <id>akv-managed-hsm-ga</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/akv-managed-hsm-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Managed HSM (hardware security module) is now generally available. Managed HSM offers a fully managed, highly available, single-tenant, high-throughput, standards-compliant cloud service to safeguard cryptographic keys for your cloud applications, using FIPS 140-2 Level 3 validated HSMs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer catch-up programs need to focus on teens' wellbeing, not just academic progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123730.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123730.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer holiday school catch-up programs to address gaps in knowledge after school closures need to support children who are still struggling due to social isolation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study suggests blood test could guide precision treatment in bladder cancer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123721.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210621123721.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blood test that can detect tiny amounts of circulating cancer DNA may be able to identify risk of cancer recurrence and guide precision treatment in bladder cancer following surgery, according to a clinical study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How childhood exercise could maintain and promote cognitive function in later life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618134038.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618134038.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T17:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who are physically active during childhood have higher cognitive functions in later life. Participants who exercised when they were children did better on cognitive tests regardless of their current age. However, no such relationship was found between task performance and post-childhood exercise -- suggesting that exercise during childhood is particularly important for brain development and long-term cognitive health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tug-of-war receptors for sour taste in fruit flies sheds light on human taste biology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618091654.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210618091654.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sour taste does not have the nearly universal appeal that sweet taste does. Slightly sour foods or drinks such as yogurt and lemon juice are yummy to many, but such highly sour foods as spoiled milk are yucky, even dangerous. Like humans, many other animals, including insects, prefer slightly acidic over very acidic foods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus on emotions is key to improving heart health in people living with obesity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082738.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082738.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People living with obesity who attended a non-judgemental and personalized lifestyle modification program improved their cardiovascular and mental health during just 10 weeks, according to a new study. Participants lost weight and achieved benefits in anxiety and depression and physical measurements including blood pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus on emotions is key to improving heart health in people living with obesity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082738.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082738.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People living with obesity who attended a non-judgemental and personalized lifestyle modification program improved their cardiovascular and mental health during just 10 weeks, according to a new study. Participants lost weight and achieved benefits in anxiety and depression and physical measurements including blood pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stress during pandemic linked to poor sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082718.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210617082718.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study found that stress, anxiety and depression during the first few weeks of the pandemic were associated with less and lower quality sleep. In a survey of more than 900 twins, about half of the respondents reported no change in sleep patterns, but 32.9 percent reported decreased sleep. Another 29.8 percent reported sleeping more. The researchers found that any change in sleep was connected to self-reported mental health issues, though more strongly associated with decreased sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having a strong life purpose eases loneliness of COVID-19 isolation, study finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616154257.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616154257.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why can some people weather the stress of social isolation better than others, and what implications does this have for their health? New research found that people who felt a strong sense of purpose in life were less lonely during the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human infant brains, bodies are active during new sleep stage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616113827.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616113827.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team has found that babies twitch during a sleep stage called quiet sleep, not just during REM sleep. The results may show there's more communication between snoozing infants' brains and motor systems than previously known.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Link found between gut microbes and stroke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616113816.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616113816.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New findings show that the gut microbiome impacts stroke severity and functional impairment following stroke. The results lay the groundwork for potential new interventions to help treat or prevent stroke.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New study finds fresh evidence for our inevitable death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616094141.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616094141.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philosophers, artists and scientists - and probably all the rest of us - have long obsessed over the key to human immortality. We all, no matter our income, culture or religion are bound to die. Even if we escape mortal diseases or accidents, we all face a deadly biological deterioration. While the debate of human longevity has divided the scientific community for centuries, a new study finds fresh evidence for our inevitable death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compounds derived from hops show promise as treatment for common liver disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616094133.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210616094133.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research suggests a pair of compounds originating from hops can help thwart a dangerous buildup of fat in the liver known as hepatic steatosis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New treatment stops progression of Alzheimer's disease in monkey brains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132245.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132245.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new therapy prompts immune defense cells to swallow misshapen proteins, amyloid beta plaques and tau tangles, whose buildup is known to kill nearby brain cells as part of Alzheimer's disease, a new study shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brain cell membranes' lipids may play big role in Alzheimer's progression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132226.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132226.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Links between lipid imbalance and disease have been established, in which lipid changes increase the formation of amyloid plaques, a hallmark of Alzheimer's disease. This imbalance inspired researchers to explore the role of lipids comprising the cellular membranes of brain cells. In Biointerphases, the researchers report on the significant role lipids may play in regulating C99, a protein within the amyloid pathway, and disease progression.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adults who skip morning meal likely to miss out on nutrients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132207.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132207.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adults who skip breakfast are likely to miss out on key nutrients that are most abundant in the foods that make up morning meals, a new study suggests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air pollution exposure during pregnancy may boost babies' obesity risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132201.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132201.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research shows pregnant women exposed to higher levels of air pollution have babies who grow unusually fast in the first months after birth, putting on excess fat that may put them at risk of obesity and related diseases later in life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air pollution exposure during pregnancy may boost babies' obesity risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132201.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132201.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research shows pregnant women exposed to higher levels of air pollution have babies who grow unusually fast in the first months after birth, putting on excess fat that may put them at risk of obesity and related diseases later in life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obesity and hypertension: Researchers discover novel mechanisms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132146.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132146.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have succeeded for the first time in demonstrating the role of hypothalamic astrocytes in obesity-related hypertension. In addition, they showed that the hormone leptin is involved in the increase of blood vessels in the hypothalamus of obese mice, contributing of hypertension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main gland in hormonal system ages due to process that can potentially be slowed down]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132136.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132136.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stem cell biologist have discovered that the pituitary gland in mice ages as the result of an age-related form of chronic inflammation. It may be possible to slow down this process or even partially repair it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthy fat impacted by change in diet and circadian clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132052.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210615132052.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changing your eating habits or altering your circadian clock can impact healthy fat tissue throughout your lifespan, according to a preclinical study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New health benefits of red seaweeds unveiled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614185554.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614185554.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red seaweeds have been prevalent in the diets of Asian communities for thousands of years. Researchers have now shown how these algae confer health benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persistence pays off in the human gut microbiome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614153920.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614153920.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The human gut microbiome is a complex community of trillions of microbes that are constantly interacting with each other and our bodies. It supports our wellbeing, immune system and mental health -- but how is it sustained?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of good taste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614153906.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614153906.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does evolution explain why we can't resist a salty chip? Researchers found that differences between the elemental composition of foods and the elemental needs of animals can explain the development of pleasing tastes like salty, umami and sweet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential new treatment target for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614131220.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614131220.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study not only sheds light on how the APOE4 gene may cause some of the pathologies associated with Alzheimer's disease, but also suggests a new treatment target that might help people who carry the APOE4 gene in early and late stages of the disease. Researchers found that APOE4 is associated with the activation of an inflammatory protein that causes a breakdown in the blood-brain barrier which protects the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new model of Alzheimer's progression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614131215.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614131215.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists explore how protein and signaling pathways change in patients with Alzheimer's disease. Their work creates a new model of disease progression, taking advantage of the heterogeneity that is inherent to human studies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plant-based diet protects from hypertension, preeclampsia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614110811.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614110811.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A plant-based diet appears to afford significant protection to rats bred to become hypertensive on a high-salt diet, scientists report. When the rats become pregnant, the whole grain diet also protects the mothers and their offspring from deadly preeclampsia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How gender norms and job loss affect relationship status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614090606.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614090606.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research shows that, in cultures that value men as breadwinners, their unemployment can affect the long-term success of a romantic relationship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young adults who lost and then restored heart health had lower risk of heart attack, stroke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614090600.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210614090600.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long-term analysis of young adults in Korea found that those with poor heart health had higher rates of cardiovascular disease at a younger age. Young adults with poor cardiovascular health who improved their cardiovascular health over time reduced their chances of heart attack, stroke or heart failure later in life. Those who maintained good cardiovascular health from a young age had the lowest risk of premature cardiovascular disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New super-resolution technique allows for more detailed brain imaging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210613181129.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210613181129.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T22:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new imaging technique has the potential to detect neurological disorders -- such as Alzheimer's disease -- at their earliest stages, enabling physicians to diagnose and treat patients more quickly. Termed super-resolution, the imaging methodology combines position emission tomography (PET) with an external motion tracking device to create highly detailed images of the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitamin D deficiency may increase risk for addiction to opioids and ultraviolet rays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210611174042.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210611174042.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lab animals deficient in vitamin D crave and become dependent on opioids, which is curbed when normal levels of the vitamin are restored. Human health records indicate that people with low vitamin D are more likely to use and misuse opioids. Study results suggest a potential role for vitamin D supplementation in fighting opioid addiction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study identifies how COVID-19 linked to Alzheimer's disease-like cognitive impairment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162405.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162405.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has identified mechanisms by which COVID-19 can lead to Alzheimer's disease-like dementia. The findings indicate an overlap between COVID-19 and brain changes common in Alzheimer's, and may help inform risk management and therapeutic strategies for COVID-19-associated cognitive impairment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget me not: Novel target shows promise in treating Alzheimer's and related dementias]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162350.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162350.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a previously unknown early driver of Alzheimer's disease (AD) and vascular dementia (VaD). They report high levels of cis P-tau, a pathogenic protein, in human AD and VaD brains as well as preclinical disease models. Treatment with an antibody to the toxic protein prevented disease progression and reversed disease symptoms and restored cognitive function in older mice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music listening near bedtime disruptive to sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162348.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610162348.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T20:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people listen to music throughout their day and often near bedtime to wind down. But can that actually cause your sleep to suffer? When a sleep researcher realized he was waking in the middle of the night with a song stuck in his head, he saw an opportunity to study how music -- and particularly stuck songs -- might affect sleep patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Roadmaps' of the brain reveal regions vulnerable to Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610150119.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610150119.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T19:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much like a supply truck crossing the countryside, the misfolded proteins that damage neurons in Alzheimer's disease travel the 'roads' of the brain, sometimes stopping and sometimes re-routing to avoid roadblocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory biomarkers confirm aerobic exercise helps cognitive function in older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610135527.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610135527.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T17:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until now, systemic biomarkers to measure exercise effects on brain function and that link to relevant metabolic responses were lacking. A study shows a memory biomarker, myokine Cathepsin B (CTSB), increased in older adults following a 26-week structured aerobic exercise training. The positive association between CTSB and cognition, and the substantial modulation of lipid metabolites implicated in dementia, support the beneficial effects of exercise training on brain function and brain health in asymptomatic individuals at risk for Alzheimer's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory biomarkers confirm aerobic exercise helps cognitive function in older adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610135527.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610135527.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T17:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until now, systemic biomarkers to measure exercise effects on brain function and that link to relevant metabolic responses were lacking. A study shows a memory biomarker, myokine Cathepsin B (CTSB), increased in older adults following a 26-week structured aerobic exercise training. The positive association between CTSB and cognition, and the substantial modulation of lipid metabolites implicated in dementia, support the beneficial effects of exercise training on brain function and brain health in asymptomatic individuals at risk for Alzheimer's.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Largescale brain epigenetics study provides new insights into dementia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610091050.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210610091050.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T13:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team looked in different regions of the brain, which are affected in Alzheimer's disease before looking for common changes across these cortical regions. They identified 220 sites in the genome, including 84 new genes, which showed different levels of DNA methylation in the cortex in individuals with more severe Alzheimer's disease, which weren't seen in the cerebellum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having trouble falling asleep predicts cognitive impairment in later life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143440.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143440.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study of nearly 2,500 adults found that having trouble falling asleep, as compared to other patterns of insomnia, was the main insomnia symptom that predicted cognitive impairment 14 years later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having trouble falling asleep predicts cognitive impairment in later life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143440.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143440.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study of nearly 2,500 adults found that having trouble falling asleep, as compared to other patterns of insomnia, was the main insomnia symptom that predicted cognitive impairment 14 years later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persistent insomnia symptoms since childhood associated with mood, anxiety disorders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143437.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143437.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 15-year longitudinal study shows that childhood insomnia symptoms that persist into adulthood are strong determinants of mood and anxiety disorders in young adults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women's mental health has higher association with dietary factors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143348.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143348.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women's mental health likely has a higher association with dietary factors than men's, according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women's mental health has higher association with dietary factors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143348.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210609143348.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T18:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women's mental health likely has a higher association with dietary factors than men's, according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source API portal now generally availabile]]></title>
        <id>open-source-api-portal-now-generally-availabile</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/open-source-api-portal-now-generally-availabile/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can create and publish a customized site with API documentation, automatically generated from OpenAPI files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drinking alcohol is linked to reduced chances of pregnancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203716.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203716.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T00:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study of the associations between drinking alcohol and the chances of becoming pregnant suggests that women who want to conceive should avoid heavy drinking. In the second half of menstrual cycle even moderate drinking is linked to reduced chances of pregnancy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study finds novel evidence that dreams reflect multiple memories, anticipate future events]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203711.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203711.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T00:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dreams result from a process that often combines fragments of multiple life experiences and anticipates future events, according to novel evidence from a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study finds novel evidence that dreams reflect multiple memories, anticipate future events]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203711.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608203711.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T00:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dreams result from a process that often combines fragments of multiple life experiences and anticipates future events, according to novel evidence from a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spirituality News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovery of circadian rhythm gene in mice could lead to breakthroughs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608154427.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608154427.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T19:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have identified a novel gene, Per2AS, that controls the sleep/wake cycle in mice. Per2AS appears to be a new type of gene, known as a non-coding gene. Unlike most other genes, Per2AS is not translated from RNA into a subsequent protein, thus making its function unclear until now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence enhances efficacy of sleep disorder treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113257.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113257.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An algorithm based on 20,000 nights of sleep that can improve the diagnosis, treatment and our overall understanding of sleep disorders has been developed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preclinical study suggests new approach to reduce COVID-19 death among the elderly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113237.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113237.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research reveals a possible new approach to preventing death and severe disease in elderly people infected with SARS-CoV-2. Researchers demonstrated in a preclinical study that senolytic drugs significantly reduced mortality upon infection from a beta-coronavirus closely related to SARS-CoV-2 in older mice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weak brain waves may warn of age-related neurodegenerative disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113213.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113213.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weakened electrical signals in the brain may be an early warning sign of age-related neurodegenerative diseases such as Alzheimer's disease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Men with sensory loss are more likely to be obese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113208.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113208.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Men who suffer sensory loss, particularly hearing loss, are more likely to be physically inactive and obese than women, according to a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exercise likely to be best treatment for depression in coronary heart disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113205.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608113205.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study indicates that exercise is probably the most effective short-term treatment for depression in people with coronary heart disease, when compared to antidepressants and psychotherapy or more complex care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People who have trouble sleeping are at a higher risk of dying early - especially diabetics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608092300.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608092300.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People with sleep problems are at an increased risk of dying young, finds a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar overload may be a recipe for long-term problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608092239.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210608092239.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T13:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Children who consume too much sugar could be at greater risk of becoming obese, hyperactive, and cognitively impaired, as adults, according to the results of a new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defying body clock linked to depression and lower wellbeing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607202226.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607202226.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T00:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People whose sleep pattern goes against their natural body clock are more likely to have depression and lower levels of wellbeing, according to a large-scale new study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New drug to halt dementia after multiple head injuries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607110155.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607110155.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An international study has identified a new drug to stop athletes developing dementia after sustaining repeated head injuries in their career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popularity runs in families]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607095739.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607095739.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T13:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To investigate the role genes play in the evolution of social structure, researchers created an experiment they likened to the 1998 film 'The Truman Show.' Genetically identical versions of 20 fruit flies were placed in 98 controlled enclosures, and video cameras recorded their interactions. The study revealed the same clones occupied the same social positions in each enclosure, regardless of living conditions, providing evidence that popularity is heritable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying mathematics takes 'friendship paradox' beyond averages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084636.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084636.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T12:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In network science, the famous 'friendship paradox' describes why your friends are (on average) more popular, richer, and more attractive than you are. Butaslightly more nuanced picture emerges when we apply mathematics to real-world data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Relationships News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers identify a molecule critical to functional brain rejuvenation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084633.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084633.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T12:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has identified a molecule called ten-eleven-translocation 1 (TET1) as a necessary component in the repair of myelin, which protects nerves and facilitates accurate transmission of electrical signals. The discovery could have important implications in treating neurodegenerative diseases and for molecular rejuvenation of aging brains in healthy individuals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple blood test can accurately reveal underlying neurodegeneration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084611.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210607084611.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T12:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study of over 3000 people, has shown for the first time that a single biomarker can accurately indicate the presence of underlying neurodegeneration in people with cognitive issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food scientists aim to make plant-based protein tastier and healthier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210604135425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210604135425.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T17:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As meat-eating continues to increase around the world, food scientists are focusing on ways to create healthier, better-tasting and more sustainable plant-based protein products that mimic meat, fish, milk, cheese and eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is elevated level of lung protein an early predictor for COPD?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603171316.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603171316.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:13:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researcher had previously discovered that the total mucin concentrations in the lungs are associated with COPD disease progression and could be used as diagnostic markers of chronic bronchitis, a hallmark condition for patients with COPD. They now report that one of these mucins, MUC5AC, is more closely and reliably associated with the development of COPD than is its brother, MUC5B.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Studies reveal skull as unexpected source of brain immunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603171058.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603171058.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that the immune cells that protect the brain and spinal cord come primarily from the skull. The finding opens up the possibility of developing therapies to target such cells as a way to prevent or treat brain conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public preview: Identity-based connections in Azure Functions with latest Azure SDK triggers and bindings]]></title>
        <id>public-preview-identitybased-connections-in-azure-functions-with-latest-azure-sdk-triggers-and-bindings</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/public-preview-identitybased-connections-in-azure-functions-with-latest-azure-sdk-triggers-and-bindings/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure functions can now connect using an identity instead of a secret.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secondary infections inflame the brain, worsening cognition in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603083545.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210603083545.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T12:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research into Alzheimer's disease (AD) suggests that secondary infections and new inflammatory events amplify the brain's immune response and affect memory in mice and in humans -- even when these secondary events occur outside the brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Healthy Aging News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Declining fish biodiversity poses risks for human nutrition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602170627.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602170627.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All fish are not created equal, at least when it comes to nutritional benefits. This truth has important implications for how declining fish biodiversity can affect human nutrition, according to a computer modeling study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kids who sleep with their pet still get a good night's rest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602153334.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602153334.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers found that the sleep quality of the surprisingly high number of children who share a bed with their pets is indistinguishable from those who sleep alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gut to brain: Nerve cells detect what we eat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602130330.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602130330.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T17:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nerve cells of the vagus nerve fulfill opposing tasks. The gut and the brain communicate with each other in order to adapt satiety and blood sugar levels during food consumption. The vagus nerve is an important communicator between these two organs. Researchers now took a closer look at the functions of the different nerve cells in the control center of the vagus nerve, and discovered something very surprising: although the nerve cells are located in the same control center, they innervate different regions of the gut and also differentially control satiety and blood sugar levels. This discovery could play an important role in the development of future therapeutic strategies against obesity and diabetes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability: Azure API Management Premium tier price reduction for incremental purchased units]]></title>
        <id>azure-api-management-premium-tier-price-reduction-for-incremental-purchased-units</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/azure-api-management-premium-tier-price-reduction-for-incremental-purchased-units/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T16:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the first purchased unit, a price reduction of 50% will be applied on all subsequent units purchased.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthy diet before, during pregnancy linked to lower complications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091425.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A healthy diet around the time of conception through the second trimester may reduce the risk of several common pregnancy complications, suggests a new study. Expectant women in the study who scored high on any of three measures of healthy eating had lower risks for gestational diabetes, pregnancy-related blood pressure disorders and preterm birth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Prescription' to sit less, move more advised for mildly high blood pressure and cholesterol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091419.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091419.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Physical activity is the optimal first treatment choice for adults with mild to moderately elevated blood pressure and blood cholesterol who otherwise have low heart disease risk. About 21% of adults in the US with mild to moderately raised blood pressure and 28-37% of those with mild to moderate elevated cholesterol levels may be best served by a prescription for lifestyle-only treatment, which includes increasing physical activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fitness News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People who eat a healthy diet including whole fruits may be less likely to develop diabetes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091404.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/06/210602091404.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds people who consume two servings of fruit per day have 36% lower odds of developing type 2 diabetes than those who consume less than half a serving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nutrition Research News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>