<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2024-05-15T14:08:28.774Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The All-Inclusive Update for Everything TLS on App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/the-all-inclusive-update-for-everything-tls-on-app-service/ba-p/4140625</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/the-all-inclusive-update-for-everything-tls-on-app-service/ba-p/4140625"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will provide you with an all-inclusive update around all App Service TLS related features. In the past year, we have announced a couple of updates in this area, and to keep things simple, this article will be broken down to these different areas/features: 

TLS 1.3 Updates 
Min TLS Cipher Suite (Preview) 
End-to-end (E2E) TLS Encryption (Preview) 

 
TLS 1.3 Updates 
As an update to the previous article about the upcoming TLS 1.3 changes on App Service, we have now fully rolled out TLS 1.3 globally. If you require all your inbound requests to be TLS 1.3, you can also set your “Minimum Inbound TLS Version” to be “TLS 1.3” on any client (ie. Portal, CLI, ARM).  
 
Configuring Min TLS Version to TLS 1.3 
Azure Portal 

 
CLI 
 
az webapp config set --min-tls-version "1.3" -g RG-N…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YutangLin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your Container Apps with Key Vault Certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/secure-your-container-apps-with-key-vault-certificates/ba-p/4140337</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/secure-your-container-apps-with-key-vault-certificates/ba-p/4140337"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps has rolled out support for Azure Key Vault certificates on both the individual app and environment levels. This improvement makes it easier than ever for developers to manage authentication and certificates for their applications. This blog post will introduce certificate management in Container Apps and the benefits of storing your credentials in Key Vault. For detailed documentation on this feature, check here.
 
Intro to certificate management
Secure communication across services requires the constant management of information such as secrets, credentials, certificates, and keys. They have to be maintained with regular updates, renewals, and monitoring. Vulnerabilities like pushing a private connection string to the cloud are easy to create but difficult to detect a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JiachenJiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub-hosted runners: Public Beta of Ubuntu 24.04 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-14-github-hosted-runners-public-beta-of-ubuntu-24-04-is-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-14-github-hosted-runners-public-beta-of-ubuntu-24-04-is-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub-hosted runners: Public Beta of Ubuntu 24.04 is now available
The post GitHub-hosted runners: Public Beta of Ubuntu 24.04 is now available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The War On Weeds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-war-on-weeds</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-war-on-weeds"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The War On Weeds appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura J. Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May 14th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/4027-may-14th-2024/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/4027-may-14th-2024/1"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features
GPT-4o integrated in Kagi Assistant
We've benchmarked OpenAI's new flagship model GPT-4o, released yesterday, and its performance on our internal independent tests (Chess puzzles and Pyllms) is impressive. As a result, GPT-4o has now been used across various features in Assistant:

Default model for Research Expert mode and Code assistant



Used for interpreting and working with uploaded files, including images



Available through Chat Assistant

Note: Kagi Assistant is available as open beta for Ultimate plan members
Recipe summarizer
Kagi Universal Summarizer now automatically identifies when you are summarizing a recipe and conveniently displays both the ingredients and the cooking steps #3937 @leopoldarrestrom
You can use Kagi Summarizer as a standalone Web app, through Kagi Search Extension in your browser or directly in search results.




Additional notes for Family / Team account members
When setting up a Family or Team account, you now have the ability to add names for each member. This feature is particularly useful for managing team members who use email aliases #2695 @Alligator


Improvements and bug fixes
Wikipedia card links do not work with smaller browser windows #3469 @yeri
Time in Portugal throws a NaN error #3986 @bleveck
Wikipedia widget does not appear, even though there are relevant Wikipedia articles as search results. #394 @iiv
Sorry, I couldn't summarize these results. #3992 @sjdonadoo
Summarizer layout issue for “Dutch” language #3572 @Nyaa
Clickable Phone Number Results #3884 @kaidea
New assistant icon is off-centred  #3994 @sefidel
Assistant messages can go off the screen #4026 @Zambyte
Research expert AI does not convert sub HTML tags for chemical formulas #3934 @frin 
Wikipedia HTML included in research assistant response #3907 @youngji22
Research assistant returns "We are sorry, this input is not supported. (Invalid Input)" on normal queries #3990 @httpjames]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Semantic Kernel to create a Time Plugin with .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2674</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/using-semantic-kernel-to-create-a-time-plugin-with-net/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plugins are one of the most powerful features of Semantic Kernel and in this demo we show how you can easily use Plugins with the power of Auto Function Calling from AI Models.  
The post Using Semantic Kernel to create a Time Plugin with .NET appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply Easy Auth on Web App under a High-security policy environment]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-apply-easy-auth-on-web-app-under-a-high-security-policy/ba-p/4139404</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-apply-easy-auth-on-web-app-under-a-high-security-policy/ba-p/4139404"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T08:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With increasing emphasis on security issues, enterprises are imposing significant restrictions on internal resources and operations accessible to employees. If your Azure account does not have sufficient AAD (i.e., of Microsoft Entra) permissions, you will be unable to swiftly create easy auth in a web app. This article serves as a simple guide to walk you through the process of setting up easy authentication for your web app.

 
 
Step 1: Create a Web App
You may choose any combination of region/sku/stack/OS, as it does not affect the overall process.

After this step, we will obtain a callback URL for use in the next step, with the following format:
https://<my-web-app-name>.azurewebsites.net/.auth/login/aad/callback
Here is my example.
https://easyauth-myapp.azurewebsites.net/.auth/logi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theringe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What OpenAI did]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/what-openai-did</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/what-openai-did"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new model opens up new possibilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started using Semantic Kernel .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2647</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/how-to-get-started-using-semantic-kernel-net/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
The post How to Get Started using Semantic Kernel .NET appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dependabot-core is now open source with an MIT license]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-13-dependabot-core-is-now-open-source-with-an-mit-license</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-13-dependabot-core-is-now-open-source-with-an-mit-license"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dependabot-core is now open source with an MIT license
The post dependabot-core is now open source with an MIT license appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent app on Azure Container Apps Landing Zone Accelerator]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/intelligent-app-on-azure-container-apps-landing-zone-accelerator/ba-p/4137337</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/intelligent-app-on-azure-container-apps-landing-zone-accelerator/ba-p/4137337"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Apps are on the raise with LLMs capabilities made easier for app integration with Azure OpenAI and Azure Container Apps helps developers focus on building the AI apps faster in a serverless container environment without worrying about container orchestration, server configuration and deployments details.
To fast-track your journey to production with AI applications, it's crucial to implement your solutions adhering to the most effective practices in security, monitoring, networking, and operational excellence.
This blogpost will show you how to leverage Azure Container Apps (ACA) Landing Zone Accelerator (LZA) to deploy the AI apps in a production grade secure baseline.
App Overview
To demonstrate the deployment, Java Azure AI reference template is used that provides a complete end-to-e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aarthimurugan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install intl extension on WordPress on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-install-intl-extension-on-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4138353</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-install-intl-extension-on-wordpress-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4138353"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T08:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1.Run the following code in the App Service SSH -
apk add icu-dev && \
   docker-php-ext-configure intl && \
   docker-php-ext-install intl && \
   docker-php-ext-enable intl
2. Now copy the intl.so & docker-php-ext-intl.ini file to persistent storage located under /home -
mkdir /home/intl-ext
cp /usr/local/etc/php/conf.d/docker-php-ext-intl.ini /home/intl-ext/docker-php-ext-intl.ini
cp /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20220829/intl.so /home/intl-ext/intl.so
3.Insert the following code into the "/home/dev/startup.sh" file - 
apk add icu-dev
cp /home/intl-ext/docker-php-ext-intl.ini /usr/local/etc/php/conf.d/docker-php-ext-intl.ini
cp /home/intl-ext/intl.so /usr/local/lib/php/extensions/no-debug-non-zts-20220829/intl.so
supervisorctl restart php-fpm
4. After completing the previous steps, restart your App Service. Once restarted, navigate to phpinfo.php and verify that the intl extension is successfully installed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun_Baliga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superhuman?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/superhuman</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/superhuman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T11:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean for AI to be better than a human? And how can we tell?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making AI powered .NET apps more consistent and intelligent with Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2627</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/making-ai-powered-net-apps-more-consistent-and-intelligent-with-redis/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T20:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 
The post Making AI powered .NET apps more consistent and intelligent with Redis appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human-Compatible AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/human-compatible-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/human-compatible-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T12:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Human-Compatible AI appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Metrics Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-09-github-copilot-metrics-updates</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-09-github-copilot-metrics-updates"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T17:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Metrics Updates
The post GitHub Copilot Metrics Updates appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to access Azure SQL database with managed identity in PHP in App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-access-azure-sql-database-with-managed-identity-in-php-in/ba-p/4129014</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-access-azure-sql-database-with-managed-identity-in-php-in/ba-p/4129014"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T01:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
After Microsoft ODBC Driver version 17.3.1.1, we will able to use the system-assigned and user-assigned identities (Using Azure Active Directory with the ODBC Driver - ODBC Driver for SQL Server | Microsoft Learn) to access the Azure SQL Server

Microsoft ODBC driver version in Azure Web App for PHP 8.1~ in Linux is after this version. We could run below command to check:

odbcinst -j
cat /etc/odbcinst.ini

The result could see we have both ODBC 17 and ODBC 18 driver. And both version is greater than the 17.3.1.1. So it shall support to use the system-assigned managed identity to access the Azure SQL database

 
Step by Step Setup
Prerequisites:
- Make sure Azure SQL database can use "Active Directory authentication" to login DB since we need the run the database commands to g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe_Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security alerts tool trends on the security overview dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-08-security-alerts-tool-trends-on-the-security-overview-dashboard</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-08-security-alerts-tool-trends-on-the-security-overview-dashboard"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security alerts tool trends on the security overview dashboard
The post Security alerts tool trends on the security overview dashboard appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signing up for GitHub Sponsors just got easier]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-08-signing-up-for-github-sponsors-just-got-easier</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-08-signing-up-for-github-sponsors-just-got-easier"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T18:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signing up for GitHub Sponsors just got easier
The post Signing up for GitHub Sponsors just got easier appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyse browser-side performance with Web Driver Sampler on Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/analyse-browser-side-performance-with-web-driver-sampler-on/ba-p/4134396</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/analyse-browser-side-performance-with-web-driver-sampler-on/ba-p/4134396"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T08:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Performance testing is not always a walk in the park. Quite often, it can be challenging and time-consuming, especially when dealing with complex and dynamic web applications that rely on JavaScript, AJAX, or other browser-side technologies.
For testing browser latencies under heavy load, JMeter has a built-in component called Web Driver Sampler, which allows testers to use Selenium WebDriver to simulate real browser actions and interactions with web elements. Web Driver Sampler can complement the HTTP Request Sampler, which sends HTTP requests to the server, by adding the browser-side perspective and measuring the rendering time, page load time, and user actions. By running JMeter scripts on Azure Load Testing, you can reliably execute your performance tests without worrying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SaloniAgrawal12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic Memory Fit for Java Apps in Azure Container Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automatic-memory-fit-for-java-apps-in-azure-container-apps/ba-p/4134276</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automatic-memory-fit-for-java-apps-in-azure-container-apps/ba-p/4134276"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T06:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Containerization has become the prevailing choice for hosting and managing Java applications, due to its unmatched portability, consistency, and scalability benefits. However, by default, when running a Java app inside containers, the JVM assumes that the OS memory is shared among multiple applications, so it conservatively claims memory for the Java application.
With Azure Container Apps, we can optimize memory allocation by simply dedicating more memory to the Java app, since only one Java application can run inside a container. This feature is called automatic memory fit, which is enabled by default when you deploy from Java source code or artifact.
In this blog we’ll cover the following:

Highlight Java memory management terms and concepts
Discuss how automatic memory fit …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean_Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actions: New region support for Azure private networking]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-07-actions-new-region-support-for-azure-private-networking</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-07-actions-new-region-support-for-azure-private-networking"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actions: New region support for Azure private networking
The post Actions: New region support for Azure private networking appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May 8th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3982-may-8th-2024/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3982-may-8th-2024/1"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates
An update on our T-shirts for the first 20,000 subscribers: they will be ready for delivery in August.
Improvements and bug fixes
Accessibility: Unable to activate buttons in Control Center with Space or Enter/Return keys #3944 @Warner
Bangs broken if used after the query #3419 @strogonoff
Wolfram Alpha answer box doesn't have enough contrast on Dark theme #3967 @sefidel
Show remaining time on title when using timer widget #3445 @sefidel 
Time widget gives an old time result if you search for the exact same query twice #3954 @Iced_Eagle 
‘More Results’ button irrecoverably hides search results #3949 @rmschindler
Can’t delete custom lenses #3947 @sefidel 
‘More Results’ button irrecoverably hides search results #3949 @rmschindler
Click to activate the shield icon #3977 @MatLebrun
Social Icons on wiki widget are not the same size/colors #3382 @ray
Time widget gives an old time result if you search for the exact same query twice #3954 @Iced_Eagle
'AI' icon being everywhere on mobile doesn't look pleasant #3946 @sefidel 
LaTeX equation should be rendered in the side info #3902 @oxlvlnle
The AI icon (that appears when hovering over a search result) is affecting text layout #3953 @stylus
Searching "sibling communication erights" with programming lens does not bring up erights website. #3925 @Bluevertro 
Universal Summarizer should be aligned left/ragged right, not justified #2104 @nbanks
Wrong contents from the universal summarizer #3842 @ene
Font size of long code block gets larger on mobile #3224 @sefidel 
Domain insights cut off on mobile #3895 @Buffalo_Tree
"Continue in Assistant" button shows and doesn't work on Pro plan #3945 @Vapid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Coming Entropy Of Our World Order]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-coming-entropy-of-our-world-order</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-coming-entropy-of-our-world-order"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Coming Entropy Of Our World Order appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parag Khanna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning push protection for file uploads]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-07-secret-scanning-push-protection-for-file-uploads</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-07-secret-scanning-push-protection-for-file-uploads"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning push protection for file uploads
The post Secret scanning push protection for file uploads appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Scanning will stop combining runs from a single upload]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-06-code-scanning-will-stop-combining-runs-from-a-single-upload</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-06-code-scanning-will-stop-combining-runs-from-a-single-upload"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code Scanning will stop combining runs from a single upload
The post Code Scanning will stop combining runs from a single upload appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refresh Expired Keys in Redis using Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-refresh-expired-keys-in-redis-using-azure-functions/ba-p/4131084</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-refresh-expired-keys-in-redis-using-azure-functions/ba-p/4131084"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Redis is an extremely popular in-memory data store that is used as a cache, session store, message broker, and more. One of the features that makes Redis really useful is the ability to set a time-to-live (TTL) value for any key. A key with a TTL value will be automatically deleted from Redis when the TTL expires. This helps reduce memory usage and ensure data freshness.
 
For instance, you might be storing information like inventory or pricing for your e-commerce site in Redis. This is a perfect application for caching in Redis. This type of data will be queried constantly and serving it directly from a database will either slow down your application or make your database implementation very expensive to handle the load! Using a CDN is out of the question because pricing and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kteegarden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage Service Connector to streamline connectivity to backend services on Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/leverage-service-connector-to-streamline-connectivity-to-backend/ba-p/4132416</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/leverage-service-connector-to-streamline-connectivity-to-backend/ba-p/4132416"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T15:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating connections between different compute and backend services on Azure is a common task that all developers have to deal with while implementing a piece of code. There are a lot of considerations one must deal with while planning, deploying and using these connections such as which identity do I use, what network configurations do I implement and where do I storage the connection configuration either in key vault or in App Configuration service to name a few.
Following these practices is important to ensure that as a developer you play your part in not just implementing best practices but also align with azure security baseline and the concept of zero trust.
This is where a service connection can help simplify some of these design and implementation choices for you.
A service connect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saurabhseth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic understanding on Microsoft Entra custom claims provider]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/basic-understanding-on-microsoft-entra-custom-claims-provider/ba-p/4125866</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/basic-understanding-on-microsoft-entra-custom-claims-provider/ba-p/4125866"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T03:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOC

What is it
Architecture
How to use it
References

 
What is it
When a user authenticates to an app (e.g., MS Entra ID application), a custom claims provider can be used to add claims into the token. A custom claims provider is made up of a custom authentication extension that calls an external REST API (e.g., a Function App), to fetch claims from external systems (e.g., a Database). A custom claims provider can be assigned to one or many applications.
 
Claim: Please imagine it as features (or attributes) that belong to the end user. As it may involve sensitive information within the enterprise, the enterprise owner wishes to store this user information in the on-premises environment, while also hoping to retrieve and utilize it through the authentication process.
 
This service is su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theringe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic Scaling: Azure Web Apps Unleash Their Hidden Potential]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automatic-scaling-azure-web-apps-unleash-their-hidden-potential/ba-p/4130820</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/automatic-scaling-azure-web-apps-unleash-their-hidden-potential/ba-p/4130820"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T10:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scale your Azure Web App automatically using Azure App Service Automatic Scaling
 
In this article we will focus on scaling azure web apps and how the new automatic scaling feature of azure app service, which allows it to scale out and in, in response to HTTP web traffic against your web app is a great feature which further enhances cost savings and improves the availability and resiliency of your web application under conditions of load.
We will also try to understand how automatic scaling is different (and at times based on scenarios better) than rule scaling, how to better understand and configure scaling limits and how it impacts scaling of different web applications sharing the same app service plan.
A look at existing options to scale an Azure Web App

Manual scale: This is the simpl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saurabhseth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating API Manifests for Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2601</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/generating-api-manifests-for-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T21:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 
The post Generating API Manifests for Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Kubernetes Service Baseline - The Hard Way]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-kubernetes-service-baseline-the-hard-way/ba-p/4130496</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-kubernetes-service-baseline-the-hard-way/ba-p/4130496"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T12:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Kubernetes Service Baseline - The Hard Way
 
Welcome to "Azure Kubernetes Service - The Hard Way". From this blog, you will learn how to deploy a scalable and resilient Kubernetes cluster on Azure using Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) and a number of adjacent Azure services. You will also learn how to apply best practices from the AKS baseline reference architecture, which provides a recommended starting point for a general purpose AKS cluster infrastructure.
 
The target audience of these instructions is intermediate to advanced Kubernetes users who want to improve their skills and knowledge about AKS and Azure. You will need to have some familiarity with Kubernetes concepts and tools such as pods, services, deployments, and kubectl. You will also need to have an Azure subscription w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibengtsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Clash Of Civilizations Is The Politics Of The End of History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-clash-of-civilizations-is-the-politics-of-the-end-of-history</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-clash-of-civilizations-is-the-politics-of-the-end-of-history"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Clash Of Civilizations <em>Is</em> The Politics Of The End of History appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[GA] Guest Collaborators for enterprise managed users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-ga-guest-collaborators-for-enterprise-managed-users</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-ga-guest-collaborators-for-enterprise-managed-users"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[GA] Guest Collaborators for enterprise managed users
The post [GA] Guest Collaborators for enterprise managed users appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Public Beta] Repository collaborators for Enterprise Managed Users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-public-beta-repository-collaborators-for-enterprise-managed-users</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-public-beta-repository-collaborators-for-enterprise-managed-users"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Public Beta] Repository collaborators for Enterprise Managed Users
The post [Public Beta] Repository collaborators for Enterprise Managed Users appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot pull requests jobs are now available to run on self hosted GitHub Actions runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-dependabot-pull-requests-jobs-are-now-available-to-run-on-self-hosted-actions-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-dependabot-pull-requests-jobs-are-now-available-to-run-on-self-hosted-actions-runners"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot pull requests jobs are now available to run on self hosted Actions runners
The post Dependabot pull requests jobs are now available to run on self hosted GitHub Actions runners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Wrote The Magna Carta, And You Can Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/i-wrote-the-magna-carta-and-you-can-too</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/i-wrote-the-magna-carta-and-you-can-too"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post I Wrote The Magna Carta, And You Can Too appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Mathews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artifact Attestations public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-artifact-attestations-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-artifact-attestations-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artifact Attestations public beta
The post Artifact Attestations public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and updated audit log events for secret scanning non-provider patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-new-and-updated-audit-log-events-for-secret-scanning-non-provider-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-02-new-and-updated-audit-log-events-for-secret-scanning-non-provider-patterns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T16:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New and updated audit log events for secret scanning non-provider patterns
The post New and updated audit log events for secret scanning non-provider patterns appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freeing the chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/freeing-the-chatbot</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/freeing-the-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligence, of a sort, is going to be all around us]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Apps can now use the client ID to fetch installation tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-01-github-apps-can-now-use-the-client-id-to-fetch-installation-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-01-github-apps-can-now-use-the-client-id-to-fetch-installation-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T00:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Apps can now use the client ID to fetch installation tokens
The post GitHub Apps can now use the client ID to fetch installation tokens appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions Newsletter – May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-may-2024/ba-p/4128908</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-may-2024/ba-p/4128908"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T23:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the May 2024 edition of Azure Functions newsletter! We'll share the latest news for Azure Functions here on the Apps on Azure blog.
Azure Functions monthly community live stream
 
Join us for our upcoming live stream on May 02, 2024, at 9:30 AM PST (16:30 UTC). Tune in to hear from Madhura Bharadwaj, Ramya Oruganti, and Thiago Almeida as they discuss the latest releases in Azure Functions, provide insights into HTTP streams support for Node.js, and Functions on Azure Container Apps. Mark your calendars for this informative session!
 



Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
Product News
Following is the list of new Azure Functions features released since February 2024: 
 




AREAS


Since February 2024




Retirements



Support for .NET 6 ends on 12 November 2024
Support for .NET 7 ends on 14 May 2024
Support for the in-process model for .NET apps in Azure Functions ends 10 November 2026
Update to Azure Functions Service Bus extension v5.x by 31 March 2025 for continued support





Triggers and Bindings



GA: Azure SQL Trigger support for Azure Functions





Languages



Public Preview: PowerShell 7.4 support for Azure Functions
GA: Azure Functions Support for Node.js 20
Public Preview: Azure Functions Support for HTTP Streams in Node.js





 
Get notified when we publish future newsletters, subscribe to the Apps on Azure blog. Connect with the Azure Functions team on GitHub and Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nzthiago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for Microsoft Build: Sharpen your skills]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/get-ready-for-microsoft-build-sharpen-your-skills/ba-p/4128754</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/get-ready-for-microsoft-build-sharpen-your-skills/ba-p/4128754"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T21:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Build is nearly here! To get ready for the big event, we're exploring resources that will help you get a head start on key topics by building new skills with the latest tools and technologies. This selection of resources delves into cloud-native development, building intelligent apps with AI, working more productively with GitHub Copilot, and more. Plus, we have other timely news and announcements for developers from around Microsoft. 
 
Training & Assessment
Implement security through a pipeline using Azure DevOpsFind out how to secure your Azure pipelines. Develop key skills, such as configuring secure access to pipeline resources, validating permissions, and managing identity for projects. Work through the Microsoft Learn path and then take the assessment to earn your credenti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mpgraven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audit Log Streaming Health Check is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-01-audit-log-streaming-health-check-is-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-05-01-audit-log-streaming-health-check-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T20:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audit Log Streaming Health Check is Generally Available
The post Audit Log Streaming Health Check is Generally Available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Red Hat OpenShift: Empowering Innovation at Red Hat Summit & AnsibleFest 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-red-hat-openshift-empowering-innovation-at-red-hat-summit/ba-p/4128556</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-red-hat-openshift-empowering-innovation-at-red-hat-summit/ba-p/4128556"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In less than a week, Azure Red Hat OpenShift (ARO) located in Booth 202, will highlight exciting latest updates at the Red Hat Summit & AnsibleFest 2024 in Denver, CO, from May 6-9. At Red Hat Summit, where Microsoft is a platinum sponsor, Azure Red Hat OpenShift, celebrating its 5th anniversary on May 7th, will be showcased alongside Microsoft Red Hat products and services. In this blog, we will explore the significance of Azure Red Hat OpenShift in this esteemed event, provide an overview of what to expect at the summit, and fly over the capabilities.
 
Red Hat Summit 2024
The Red Hat Summit & AnsibleFest 2024 is a convergence of leading minds in open-source technologies, cloud computing, and automation solutions. It serves as a pivotal platform for industry leaders, developers, and IT (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie_Kraintz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Preview: App Insights integration for Python apps on App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/public-preview-app-insights-integration-for-python-apps-on-app/ba-p/4127818</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/public-preview-app-insights-integration-for-python-apps-on-app/ba-p/4127818"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Monitor and App Service teams are happy to share that Application Insights integration with App Services for Python apps is now available for Public Preview. You can now easily monitor your Python apps on App Service without changing your code by leveraging auto-instrumentation that is integrated into the App Services platform.
 
This integration supports App Service deploy as code for Python versions 3.11 and lower. Deploy as container scenarios are not currently supported, but we plan to introduce this capability at a future date. We also plan to support Python 3.12 in the near future.
 
With this feature enabled, the App Service platform will instrument popular Python libraries in your code and automatically channel correlated application-level logs, metrics, and distributed tracing to your Application Insights resource. This will allow you to understand how your Python application is performing and more easily determine the cause of any incidents.
 
You can enable the feature at resource creation or from the App Insights blade after your App Service resource is created. Please review our documentation to learn more.
 
Turn On App Insights during App Service Resource Creation
 
When you create a new Python web application (version 3.11 and lower) using the "Deploy as code" option, you can select "Yes" on the "Enable Application Insights" in the "Monitoring" tab. If you select "Yes", then your non-containerized Python application will pipe data to an Application Insights resource allowing you to automatically monitor your workloads.
 

 
 
Turn On App Insights after App Service Resource Creation
 
Open your App Service application in the portal and go to the App Insights menu item.

Select "Enable" in the toggle under "Application Insights (Preview)"
Select a location for your Application Insights resource (It’s suggested to create the resource in the same region as the Web App.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YutangLin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/05/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/05/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from sunny Brooklyn, where it’s suddenly summer. What’s new?
Over at the Val Town Blog, I wrote about how searching source code is a pretty
hard problem. It was pretty
well-received: I confirmed that yes, it’s a pretty hard problem. We’re really
trying not to write a search engine, but it’s tempting, maybe just
to tinker with Tantivy.

This is a big year for running, so far. My first race of the year is
complete - the Brooklyn Half Marathon. I ran 1:36:21 (7:21/mi pace) –
a time that just squeaks past my previous personal best. Felt pretty good!
My pacing was good until it wasn’t: need to work on endurance past the eleven
mile mark.
I have two 5Ks lined up, but might try running another longer race,
because beating my half marathon PR seems more achievable than
beating my 5K PR, whic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[npm feedback is now available on GitHub Community]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-npm-feedback-is-now-available-on-github-community</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-npm-feedback-is-now-available-on-github-community"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T23:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[npm feedback is now available on GitHub Community
The post npm feedback is now available on GitHub Community appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Licensing page removing “Enterprise Help” section]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-enterprise-licensing-page-removing-enterprise-help-section</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-enterprise-licensing-page-removing-enterprise-help-section"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T22:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Licensing page removing "Enterprise Help" section
The post Enterprise Licensing page removing “Enterprise Help” section appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning supports bypass controls for push protection (public beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-secret-scanning-supports-bypass-controls-for-push-protection-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-secret-scanning-supports-bypass-controls-for-push-protection-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T22:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning supports bypass controls for push protection (public beta)
The post Secret scanning supports bypass controls for push protection (public beta) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: UI Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-github-actions-ui-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-github-actions-ui-improvements"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T17:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: UI Improvements
The post GitHub Actions: UI Improvements appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise – Copilot knows about issues + more April 2024 updates]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-github-copilot-enterprise-copilot-knows-about-issues-more-april-2024-updates</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-github-copilot-enterprise-copilot-knows-about-issues-more-april-2024-updates"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Enterprise - Copilot knows about issues + more April 2024 updates
The post GitHub Copilot Enterprise – Copilot knows about issues + more April 2024 updates appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autoscaling of Microservice Apps on Azure: Leveraging Azure Kubernetes Service, KEDA, and MSSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/autoscaling-of-microservice-apps-on-azure-leveraging-azure/ba-p/4124778</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/autoscaling-of-microservice-apps-on-azure-leveraging-azure/ba-p/4124778"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post aims to walk you through the setup of an autoscaled application on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) with Kubernetes-based Event-Driven Autoscaling (KEDA), activated by Microsoft SQL Server (MSSQL) queries. By following this guide, you will have an autoscaled application in place, facilitating efficient resource utilization and equipping your application to manage fluctuating workloads, thereby enhancing its performance and responsiveness.
Prerequisites:

Azure Account: An active Azure account is required. If you do not have one, you can sign up for a free account on the Azure website.
Kubernetes Familiarity: A basic understanding of Kubernetes concepts, including Deployments, Services, and Persistent Volumes, is essential.
SQL Server Knowledge: Basic knowledge of SQL Server an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hailukassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Build – Community Testimonial Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2586</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/microsoft-build-community-testimonial-videos/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T14:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
The post Microsoft Build – Community Testimonial Videos appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Updates April 30th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-repository-updates-april-30th-2024</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-repository-updates-april-30th-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T14:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository Updates April 30th, 2024
The post Repository Updates April 30th, 2024 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning now allows configuring rulesets to prevent pull requests from being merged (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-code-scanning-now-allows-configuring-rulesets-to-prevent-pull-requests-from-being-merged-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-30-code-scanning-now-allows-configuring-rulesets-to-prevent-pull-requests-from-being-merged-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T14:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code scanning now allows configuring rulesets to prevent pull requests from being merged (beta)
The post Code scanning now allows configuring rulesets to prevent pull requests from being merged (beta) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 30th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3940-april-30th-2024/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3940-april-30th-2024/1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T09:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcements
We are hiring!
As we continue our journey, we're hiring across various teams. Visit our jobs page for more details and reach out via email if you're interested in joining!
Advanced Account Security
On select pages, Kagi will now ask you to confirm with your password or 2FA code (if configured) where sensitive actions or information may be present. This primarily applies to billing-related areas, such as accessing your invoices or switching plans.

This concludes a small arc of changes, with 2FA, QR login, and now these extra security checks. We hope these are working well for you! We'll continue building more supported login methods, and session management tools.
Improvements and bug fixes
Maps - feedback when calculating route between two points #3910 @frin
Infinite scroll w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot multi-directory configuration public beta now available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-29-dependabot-multi-directory-configuration-public-beta-now-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-29-dependabot-multi-directory-configuration-public-beta-now-available"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot multi-directory configuration public beta now available
The post Dependabot multi-directory configuration public beta now available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filters in Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2560</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/filters-in-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T19:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s important to understand how the application behaves and have the ability to override that behavior in runtime based on some conditions. For example, we don’t want to send malicious prompt to LLM, and we don’t want to expose more information than needed to the end users.
The post Filters in Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Link Underline Setting now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-28-link-underline-setting-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-28-link-underline-setting-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T06:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Link Underline Setting now GA
The post Link Underline Setting now GA appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.17.1: AI-powered autofixes for C#, new Ruby queries and more Java models]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-26-codeql-2-17-1-ai-powered-autofixes-for-c-new-ruby-queries-and-more-java-models</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-26-codeql-2-17-1-ai-powered-autofixes-for-c-new-ruby-queries-and-more-java-models"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T15:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.17.1: AI-powered autofixes for C#, new Ruby queries and more Java models
The post CodeQL 2.17.1: AI-powered autofixes for C#, new Ruby queries and more Java models appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fissures That Followed Mandela]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-fissures-that-followed-mandela</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-fissures-that-followed-mandela"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T14:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Fissures That Followed Mandela appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sisonke Msimang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Babelian Tower Of AI Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-babelian-tower-of-ai-alignment</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-babelian-tower-of-ai-alignment"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Babelian Tower Of AI Alignment appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Semantic Kernel Hits 1,000,000 Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2569</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/microsoft-semantic-kernel-hits-1000000-downloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T20:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A million moments of innovation, a million instances of creative coding, a million downloads.  Microsoft Semantic Kernel has proudly reached a significant milestone within the software development community. This achievement is not just a number—it’s a beacon of collective progress and the power of open-source collaboration.
The post Microsoft Semantic Kernel Hits 1,000,000 Downloads appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Chaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Gen Customer Service: Azure's AI-Powered Speech, Translation and Summarization]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/next-gen-customer-service-azure-s-ai-powered-speech-translation/ba-p/4101838</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/next-gen-customer-service-azure-s-ai-powered-speech-translation/ba-p/4101838"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T19:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purpose of this solution is to enable applications to incorporate AI capabilities. In the upcoming demo, I will showcase how to transcribe and speech (Azure AI Speech), translate (Azure AI Translator) and summarize (Azure AI Language) conversations between customers and businesses without significantly modifying your existing apps.
 
This application can be helpful in various scenarios where two parties speak different languages and require simultaneous translation. For instance, it can be employed in call centers where the representative and the customer do not speak the same language, by bank tellers dealing with foreign clients, by doctors communicating with elderly patients who do not speak the native language well, and in other similar situations where both parties need to convers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eladt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise enablement trends for security products (public beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-enterprise-enablement-trends-for-security-products-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-enterprise-enablement-trends-for-security-products-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise enablement trends for security products (public beta)
The post Enterprise enablement trends for security products (public beta) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions – Deployment views across environments (GA)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-github-actions-deployment-views-across-environments-ga</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-github-actions-deployment-views-across-environments-ga"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions - Deployment views across environments (GA)
The post GitHub Actions – Deployment views across environments (GA) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects –  Auto-close issue project workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-github-issues-projects-auto-close-issue-project-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-25-github-issues-projects-auto-close-issue-project-workflow"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T18:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues & Projects –  Auto-close issue project workflow
The post GitHub Issues & Projects –  Auto-close issue project workflow appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Resilience Means Retreat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/climate-resilience-means-retreat</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/climate-resilience-means-retreat"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Climate Resilience Means Retreat appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Stone Jr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing API Manifest Plugins for Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2556</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/introducing-api-manifest-plugins-for-semantic-kernel-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
The post Introducing API Manifest Plugins for Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key announcements for AKS from KubeCon Europe 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/key-announcements-for-aks-from-kubecon-europe-2024/ba-p/4122918</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/key-announcements-for-aks-from-kubecon-europe-2024/ba-p/4122918"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At KubeCon Europe 2024, we showed how Azure and Kubernetes can help you build and deploy intelligent applications. Even if you couldn’t visit us at the Microsoft booth or attend the conference sessions, you can read about all the exciting ways we’re making Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) the best destination for all things cloud-native—including the latest AI and machine learning (ML) applications. With enhancements to security, performance, networking, observability, and more, AKS provides even more platform-as-a-service benefits on top of a smoother onboarding experience for a great end-to-end developer experience.
 
Powering AI, ML, and compute-intensive workloads
Principal PM Lead for AKS Jorge Palma gave the keynote address, where he explored what AI can do for your platform and how to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unit Testing with Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2523</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/unit-testing-with-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T15:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
The post Unit Testing with Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Plans with Semantic Kernel: Implementing the Microsoft Graph Plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2486</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/making-plans-with-semantic-kernel-implementing-the-microsoft-graph-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
The post Making Plans with Semantic Kernel: Implementing the Microsoft Graph Plugin appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Metrics API now available in public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-23-github-copilot-metrics-api-now-available-in-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-23-github-copilot-metrics-api-now-available-in-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T16:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Metrics API now available in public beta
The post GitHub Copilot Metrics API now available in public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Disappearing Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-disappearing-tree</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-disappearing-tree"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T16:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Disappearing Tree appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Astra Lincoln</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot Updates on Actions for GitHub Enterprise Cloud and Free, Pro, and Teams Users]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-22-dependabot-updates-on-actions-for-github-enterprise-cloud-and-free-pro-and-teams-users</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-22-dependabot-updates-on-actions-for-github-enterprise-cloud-and-free-pro-and-teams-users"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T22:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot Updates on Actions for GitHub Enterprise Cloud and Free, Pro, and Teams Users
The post Dependabot Updates on Actions for GitHub Enterprise Cloud and Free, Pro, and Teams Users appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting your IP in the Azure Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/protecting-your-ip-in-the-azure-marketplace/ba-p/4120539</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/protecting-your-ip-in-the-azure-marketplace/ba-p/4120539"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T21:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Marketplace is an online store for Azure customers to discover, evaluate, and purchase a wide array of solutions with integrated billing and easy deployment.  While the Azure Marketplace is used for billing, it does not manage licenses directly. It's essential to integrate your own license management system to  protect your intellectual property (IP) from unauthorized access or misuse. 
 
We are seeing an increase in these types of questions, especially from our AI partners. This article outlines strategies to safeguard your IP effectively when deploying an Azure VM or Azure Container Offer.



 
 
Obfuscate Your Code
Code obfuscation is a technique used to make your source code more difficult to understand and reverse-engineer. By transforming the code into a format that is chal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Falgout</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation through prompting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/innovation-through-prompting</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/innovation-through-prompting"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T11:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratizing educational technology... and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Is Assuming A Pre-War Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-world-is-assuming-a-pre-war-posture</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-world-is-assuming-a-pre-war-posture"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T14:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The World Is Assuming A Pre-War Posture appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push rules public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-push-rules-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-push-rules-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T16:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Push rules public beta
The post Push rules public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Kernel Updates: A Closer Look at Our Redesigned Plugin and Function Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2462</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/python-kernel-updates-a-closer-look-at-our-redesigned-plugin-and-function-integration/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T15:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we approach a stable v1.0 version of the Python Semantic Kernel SDK, we analysed the methods used to add plugins and functions to the kernel. We realised that the variety of available methods might confuse developers. For instance, when should one use import_plugin_from_object() versus import_native_plugin_from_directory()?
The post Python Kernel Updates: A Closer Look at Our Redesigned Plugin and Function Integration appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Mattson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Azure Load Testing on Azure App Service web apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/run-azure-load-testing-on-azure-app-service-web-apps/ba-p/4117175</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/run-azure-load-testing-on-azure-app-service-web-apps/ba-p/4117175"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now create and run load tests directly from App Service web apps in Azure portal. This functionality, powered by Azure Load Testing, enables you to get started with your performance testing journey in a few clicks.
 
Using the Load Testing functionality in App Service web apps you can do the following:

Get started without any knowledge of performance testing tools by configuring your HTTP request details in the Azure portal.
Run tests with up to 100,000 concurrent virtual users and up to 24-hour duration to simulate load testing scenarios like stress testing, spike testing, endurance testing etc.
Automatically gain access to client-side and server-side metrics, which will help in identifying performance bottlenecks.
View the test run history to continuously monitor their web app performance.

 
Navigate to your App Service web app in Azure portal to find the Load Testing feature in the Performance section as shown below.Screenshot of Load Testing feature in Azure App service portal
 
To learn more about this feature and how to use it, check out the documentation. We would love to hear your feedback and suggestions on how to improve it. Please share your thoughts and questions in the comments below or on the feedback forum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita_Nallamothu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-codeql-for-visual-studio-code-documentation-is-now-on-docs-github-com</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-18-codeql-for-visual-studio-code-documentation-is-now-on-docs-github-com"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T09:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com
The post CodeQL for Visual Studio Code documentation is now on docs.github.com appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Space Of Possible Minds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/ai-could-be-a-bridge-toward-diverse-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/ai-could-be-a-bridge-toward-diverse-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T18:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Space Of Possible Minds appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-updates-to-github-importer-and-the-deprecation-of-the-source-import-rest-api-endpoint</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-updates-to-github-importer-and-the-deprecation-of-the-source-import-rest-api-endpoint"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T17:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint
The post Updates to GitHub Importer and the deprecation of the Source Import REST API Endpoint appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in the Reliable Web App Pattern for .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/what-s-new-in-the-reliable-web-app-pattern-for-net/ba-p/4116085</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/what-s-new-in-the-reliable-web-app-pattern-for-net/ba-p/4116085"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest version of The Reliable Web App (RWA) Pattern for .NET enhances its original objective of helping existing .NET web apps transition to Azure by now emphasizing improvements to production infrastructure. These enhancements are a direct response to user feedback, focusing especially on the importance of Infrastructure as Code (IaC) using Bicep best practices and network security. While the update maintains its foundational developer patterns, it also boosts network security for production deployments and streamlines the initial setup process. 
 
In this blog post, we will explain what the reliable web app pattern entails, highlight the new features, and guide you on how to begin using it today. 
 
What is the reliable web app pattern (RWA)? 
The reliable web app pattern is one of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mattsoucoup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-configure-organization-level-codeql-model-packs-for-github-code-scanning</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-17-configure-organization-level-codeql-model-packs-for-github-code-scanning"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning
The post Configure organization-level CodeQL model packs for GitHub code scanning appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock AI Collaboration at Microsoft BUILD 2024 with Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2467</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/unlock-ai-collaboration-at-microsoft-build-2024-with-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T21:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The moment we’ve all been waiting for is nearly here. Microsoft BUILD 2024, happening from May 21 – 23rd, is poised to be a groundbreaking event, especially for our community working at the intersection of AI and application development.
The post Unlock AI Collaboration at Microsoft BUILD 2024 with Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Chaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Importer’s new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-github-enterprise-importers-new-git-source-migrator-improves-reliability-of-large-repo-migrations</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-github-enterprise-importers-new-git-source-migrator-improves-reliability-of-large-repo-migrations"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T20:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Importer's new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations
The post GitHub Enterprise Importer’s new git source migrator improves reliability of large repo migrations appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-secret-scanning-for-historically-existing-secrets-found-in-github-discussions-and-pull-requests</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-secret-scanning-for-historically-existing-secrets-found-in-github-discussions-and-pull-requests"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T19:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests
The post Secret scanning for historically existing secrets found in GitHub discussions and pull requests appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of multi-label larger runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-of-multi-label-larger-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-of-multi-label-larger-runners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T19:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of multi-label larger runners
The post Deprecation of multi-label larger runners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-notice-v3-of-the-artifact-actions</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-04-16-deprecation-notice-v3-of-the-artifact-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T17:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions
The post Deprecation notice: v3 of the artifact actions appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need To Rewild The Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post We Need To Rewild The Internet  appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 20th, 2024 - Introducing QR code sign-in and final sales taxes update]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/3841-april-20th-2024-introducing-qr-code-sign-in-and-final-sales-taxes-update/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/3841-april-20th-2024-introducing-qr-code-sign-in-and-final-sales-taxes-update/1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features and announcements
QR code sign-in
Now you can simply scan a QR code on Kagi's login page with an authenticated device to log into a new device. For more details, visit our help page. #2417 @FrederickZh


Sales tax rollout
Starting this Sunday, April 21st, sales taxes will apply to all subscriptions. We have notified subscribers of this change via email. This marks the completion of the sales tax rollout. For further details, please visit our FAQ page.
Improvements and bug fixes
Add keyboard shortcuts shift-J/K to skip to next domain's results #2465 @Deebster
[Apperance][New UI] Plans do not show their differences anymore #3796 @igak_rekcartgub
Lens settings has a incorrect input label or maybe an incorrect input field? Not sure... #3845 @gunslingerfry
Provide feedback for copying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>