<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2024-08-19T21:08:08.030Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions Newsletter – August 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-august-2024/ba-p/4222747</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-newsletter-august-2024/ba-p/4222747"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the August 2024 edition of Azure Functions newsletter! We'll share the latest news for Azure Functions here on the Apps on Azure blog.
 
Azure Functions monthly community live stream
 
Join us for our upcoming live stream on August 20, 2024, at 8:00 AM PST (15:00 UTC). Tune in to hear from Nikita Nallamothu and Thiago Almeida as they discuss the latest releases in Azure Functions, and cover performance testing and cost optimizing HTTP function apps using Azure Load Testing. Mark your calendars for this informative session!
 



 
Subscribe to the Azure Developers YouTube channel!
 
Product News
Following is the list of new Azure Functions features released since June 2024: 


GA: Support for .NET 8 using the in-process model in Azure Functions
GA: Run Azure Load Testing on Azure Functions
GA: Generally Available: Redis extension for Azure Functions


 
Get notified when we publish future newsletters, subscribe to the Apps on Azure blog. Connect with the Azure Functions team on GitHub and Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nzthiago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notice of upcoming deprecations and breaking changes in GitHub Actions runners]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-notice-of-upcoming-deprecations-and-breaking-changes-in-github-actions-runners</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-notice-of-upcoming-deprecations-and-breaking-changes-in-github-actions-runners"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notice of upcoming deprecations and breaking changes in GitHub Actions runners
The post Notice of upcoming deprecations and breaking changes in GitHub Actions runners appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevention and autofix insights for CodeQL pull request alerts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-prevention-and-autofix-insights-for-codeql-pull-request-alerts</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-prevention-and-autofix-insights-for-codeql-pull-request-alerts"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prevention and autofix insights for CodeQL pull request alerts
The post Prevention and autofix insights for CodeQL pull request alerts appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content Exclusion beta now supports non-Git files]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-content-exclusion-beta-now-supports-non-git-files</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-19-content-exclusion-beta-now-supports-non-git-files"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content Exclusion beta now supports non-Git files
The post Content Exclusion beta now supports non-Git files appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for non-code GitHub surfaces is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-16-secret-scanning-for-non-code-github-surfaces-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-16-secret-scanning-for-non-code-github-surfaces-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T00:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning for non-code GitHub surfaces is now generally available
The post Secret scanning for non-code GitHub surfaces is now generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieve the code security configuration currently applied to a repository via API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-16-retrieve-the-code-security-configuration-currently-applied-to-a-repository-via-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-16-retrieve-the-code-security-configuration-currently-applied-to-a-repository-via-api"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T18:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrieve the code security configuration currently applied to a repository via API
The post Retrieve the code security configuration currently applied to a repository via API appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High contrast theme improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-15-high-contrast-theme-improvements</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-15-high-contrast-theme-improvements"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T16:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High contrast theme improvements
The post High contrast theme improvements appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Knows What Consciousness Is?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/who-knows-what-consciousness-is</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/who-knows-what-consciousness-is"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Who Knows What Consciousness Is? appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Enterprise now helps you fix failed Actions jobs, plus other August updates (public beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-15-copilot-enterprise-now-helps-you-fix-failed-actions-jobs-plus-other-august-updates-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-15-copilot-enterprise-now-helps-you-fix-failed-actions-jobs-plus-other-august-updates-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T15:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Enterprise now helps you fix failed Actions jobs plus other August updates (public beta)
The post Copilot Enterprise now helps you fix failed Actions jobs, plus other August updates (public beta) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code security configurations will replace feature enablement on the organization-level security coverage page on October 15]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-code-security-configurations-will-replace-feature-enablement-on-the-organization-level-security-coverage-page-on-october-15</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-code-security-configurations-will-replace-feature-enablement-on-the-organization-level-security-coverage-page-on-october-15"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code security configurations will replace feature enablement on the organization-level security coverage page on October 15
The post Code security configurations will replace feature enablement on the organization-level security coverage page on October 15 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypass list for secret scanning push protection can include the maintainer role]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-bypass-list-for-secret-scanning-push-protection-can-include-the-maintainer-role</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-bypass-list-for-secret-scanning-push-protection-can-include-the-maintainer-role"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T18:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bypass list for secret scanning push protection can include the maintainer role
The post Bypass list for secret scanning push protection can include the maintainer role appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Autofix for CodeQL code scanning alerts is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-copilot-autofix-for-codeql-code-scanning-alerts-is-now-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-14-copilot-autofix-for-codeql-code-scanning-alerts-is-now-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T16:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Autofix for CodeQL code scanning alerts is now generally available
The post Copilot Autofix for CodeQL code scanning alerts is now generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and Deploy Linux WebJobs on Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/create-and-deploy-linux-webjobs-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4218587</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/create-and-deploy-linux-webjobs-on-azure-app-service/ba-p/4218587"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
WebJobs are a feature of Azure App Service that allows you to run background tasks or scripts in your App Service. They are particularly useful for executing jobs such as scheduled tasks, data processing, or background maintenance tasks. WebJobs can run continuously, on-demand, or on a scheduled basis, and they can be written in various programming languages.
The goal of this blog post is to guide you through the process of setting up and deploying a WebJob on an Azure App Service running Linux. We will walk you through the necessary steps to create and deploy a WebJob, configure its settings, and manage it effectively. By the end of this blog, you will have a working WebJob integrated into your Azure App Service, capable of performing background tasks or processing jobs as ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yash_gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating Workload profile Container App with Front Door and Application Gateway Private Link]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/integrating-workload-profile-container-app-with-front-door-and/ba-p/4217335</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/integrating-workload-profile-container-app-with-front-door-and/ba-p/4217335"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T06:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
For the workload profile container app, private link support is not yet available. This is because the “Private Link Service does not support a load balancer that has an IP-based backend pool, which is used in Consumption + Dedicated environments (Workload Profile)”. Although we have a roadmap to implement this feature (Private link support for Workload Profiles · Azure Container Apps Roadmap), there is currently no ETA.
 
In the meantime, I will guide you on how to integrate a workload profile container app with Azure Front Door using an Application Gateway. The architecture involves using the Application Gateway private link to connect to the Front Door, and placing the Application Gateway in the same VNET as the container app to achieve this integration.

Note: As of August…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe_Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning push protection is supported for content upload REST API endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-secret-scanning-push-protection-is-supported-for-content-upload-rest-api-endpoints</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-secret-scanning-push-protection-is-supported-for-content-upload-rest-api-endpoints"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T19:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning push protection is supported for content upload REST API endpoints
The post Secret scanning push protection is supported for content upload REST API endpoints appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning backfilling existing secrets in GitHub wikis]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-secret-scanning-backfilling-existing-secrets-in-github-wikis</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-secret-scanning-backfilling-existing-secrets-in-github-wikis"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T18:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning backfilling existing secrets in GitHub wikis
The post Secret scanning backfilling existing secrets in GitHub wikis appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign-up for the GitHub Copilot Extensions waitlist]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-13-sign-up-for-the-github-copilot-extensions-waitlist"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T16:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to open our waitlist for all GitHub Copilot users to start using Copilot Extensions! Join the Copilot Extensions waitlist. With extensions, you can extend the capabilities…
The post Sign-up for the GitHub Copilot Extensions waitlist appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making ‘Food Out Of Thin Air’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/making-food-out-of-thin-air</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/making-food-out-of-thin-air"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T16:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Making ‘Food Out Of Thin Air’ appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Maughan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's move away from API keys!]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/let-s-move-away-from-api-keys/ba-p/4217697</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/let-s-move-away-from-api-keys/ba-p/4217697"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T12:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API keys management
This is the first part in a series of security practices on Azure
 
You want enterprise-grade security but don't know where to start. You've heard terms like Entra ID and Managed identity or maybe even Service principal but where do you go from here? Let's start here with this series on security.



35% of all exposed API keys are still active - 35% of exposed API keys still active, posing major security risks - Help Net Security


That's a pretty scary statement, that means services are being misused most likely, data is actively being stolen and so on. 

Let's try to understand why the concept of API keys is a problematic one and how we can move away from it.

What's the problem with using API keys?
API keys feel great to use right, you get your key, you talk to the A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris_Noring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous HTTP APIs with Azure Container Apps jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/asynchronous-http-apis-with-azure-container-apps-jobs/ba-p/4217431</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/asynchronous-http-apis-with-azure-container-apps-jobs/ba-p/4217431"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T08:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building HTTP APIs, it can be tempting to synchronously run long-running tasks in a request handler. This approach can lead to slow responses, timeouts, and resource exhaustion. If a request times out or a connection is dropped, the client won't know if the operation completed or not. For CPU-bound tasks, this approach can also bog down the server, making it unresponsive to other requests.
 
In this post, we'll look at how to build an asynchronous HTTP API with Azure Container Apps. We'll create a simple API that implements the Asynchronous Request-Reply pattern: with the API hosted in a container app and the asynchronous processing done in a job. This approach provides a much more robust and scalable solution for long-running tasks.
 
Long-running API requests in Azure Container Apps…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnthonyChu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark Testing puts you on the path to peak API Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/benchmark-testing-puts-you-on-the-path-to-peak-api-performance/ba-p/4216776</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/benchmark-testing-puts-you-on-the-path-to-peak-api-performance/ba-p/4216776"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark performance testing involves measuring the performance characteristics of an application or system under normal or expected conditions. It's a recommended practice in any case, but it's a critical consideration for your APIs since your consumers will depend on consistent performance for their client applications.
 
Incorporating benchmark testing of your Microsoft Azure API Management services into your software delivery process provides several important benefits:
 

It establishes performance baseline as a known, quantifiable starting point against which future results can be compared.
It identifies performance regressions so that you can pinpoint changes or integrations that may be causing performance degradation or hindering scalability — in effect helping you to identify whi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JonLester</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced Repo Insights Views]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-12-auto-draft</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-12-enhanced-repo-insights-views"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T19:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Enhanced Repo Insights Views We’re thrilled to introduce improvments to Repo insights! With this update, you’ll find significant enhancements to two of our repository insights views—Contributors and Code Frequency.…
The post Enhanced Repo Insights Views appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change blindness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/change-blindness</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/change-blindness"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T03:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[21 months later]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Metrics API Organization Team Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-09-copilot-metrics-api-organization-team-metrics</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-09-copilot-metrics-api-organization-team-metrics"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T19:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Metrics API Organization Team Metrics
The post Copilot Metrics API Organization Team Metrics appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics for push protection bypass requests are included in the secret scanning metrics page]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-08-metrics-for-push-protection-bypass-requests-are-included-in-the-secret-scanning-metrics-page</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-08-metrics-for-push-protection-bypass-requests-are-included-in-the-secret-scanning-metrics-page"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T23:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics for push protection bypass requests are included in the secret scanning metrics page
The post Metrics for push protection bypass requests are included in the secret scanning metrics page appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Team Metrics Now Available on the Copilot Metrics API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-08-enterprise-team-metrics-now-available-on-the-copilot-metrics-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-08-enterprise-team-metrics-now-available-on-the-copilot-metrics-api"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T16:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Team Metrics Now Available on the Copilot Metrics API
The post Enterprise Team Metrics Now Available on the Copilot Metrics API appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Silicon Valley’s Grand Ambitions To Control Our Planet’s Thermostat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/inside-silicon-valleys-grand-ambitions-to-control-our-planets-thermostat</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/inside-silicon-valleys-grand-ambitions-to-control-our-planets-thermostat"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T16:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Inside Silicon Valley’s Grand Ambitions To Control Our Planet’s Thermostat appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Robert Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your Generative AI APIs with Azure API Management and Azure Open AI]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/manage-your-generative-ai-apis-with-azure-api-management-and/ba-p/4214178</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/manage-your-generative-ai-apis-with-azure-api-management-and/ba-p/4214178"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is for you who have started with Generative AI APIs and you’re looking to take those APIs into production. At high-level, there are things to consider like load balancing error management and cost management. We’ll mention those in this article and guide you to an Azure Sample where you can get started deploying an enterprise-ready solution. 
 
Scenario: you want to take your generative AI to production. 
So, you’re starting to use Azure Open AI, you like what you see, and you see how you can add this AI functionality to several of the apps in your company.  
However, you have a big operation with many customers and many different apps and enterprise grade requirements on security and you know you must tackle all that before you can adopt generative AI to your business.  
 
Problems w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris_Noring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super fast creating react app with Microsoft Entra on Azure Web app]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/super-fast-creating-react-app-with-microsoft-entra-on-azure-web/ba-p/4213815</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/super-fast-creating-react-app-with-microsoft-entra-on-azure-web/ba-p/4213815"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOCStepsReferences
 
Steps:

Create an App registration in Microsoft Entra.


 
 
 

After creation, note down the Application (client) ID and Directory (tenant) ID, which will be used later.


 
 

Create a Linux web app in Azure Portal and use Node.js.


 
 

After creation, note down the App Name, which will be used later.


 
 
 

Download the sample code in your development environment:

 
git clone https://github.com/Azure-Samples/ms-identity-docs-code-javascript.git
 
 
 

You can use VS Code to open the react-spa subfolder.

 
 
 

Edit src/authConfig.js and make the corresponding modifications:




clientId
Specify the Application (client) ID obtained in step 2


authority
Fill in the Directory (tenant) ID obtained in step 2 in the specified format. (https://login.microsoftonline.com/<TENANT_ID>)


redirectUri
Fill in the App Name obtained in step 4 in the specified format. (https://<APP_NAME>.azurewebsites.net/.auth/login/aad/callback)




 
 
 

Run the following command to install the relevant packages:

 
npm install
 
 

Run the following command to compile the project. After execution, a build subfolder will be created.

 
npm run build
 
 

Create or modify build/.deployment with the following content:

 
[config]
SCM_DO_BUILD_DURING_DEPLOYMENT=false
 

 
 
 

Publish your project, specifying the build subfolder during the publishing process.




 
 

After publishing, go back to the App registration in Microsoft Entra, find Authentication, create a Platform, specify Single-Page Application, and fill in the value of authority from Step 7.


 
 
 

Go back to the project, navigate to Configuration, and specify the Startup Command as follows:

 
pm2 serve /home/site/wwwroot --no-daemon --spa
 

 
 
 

After restarting the web app, you can visit your webpage using a browser.




 
 
 
References:
Quickstart: Sign in to a SPA & call an API - React - Microsoft identity platform | Microsoft Learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theringe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.14 Release Candidate is available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-07-the-github-enterprise-server-3-14-release-candidate-is-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-07-the-github-enterprise-server-3-14-release-candidate-is-available"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T23:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.14 Release Candidate is available
The post The GitHub Enterprise Server 3.14 Release Candidate is available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Mobile, July Update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-07-whats-new-in-mobile-july-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-07-whats-new-in-mobile-july-update"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T20:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's New in Mobile, July Update
The post What’s New in Mobile, July Update appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Security and Control: Bring Your Own NSG to Microsoft Azure Red Hat OpenShift Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enhancing-security-and-control-bring-your-own-nsg-to-microsoft/ba-p/4212157</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/enhancing-security-and-control-bring-your-own-nsg-to-microsoft/ba-p/4212157"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure Red Hat OpenShift (ARO) has taken a significant step forward in empowering organizations with greater control over their cluster security. The "bring your own" Network Security Group (NSG) feature offers a flexible approach to managing network security for ARO clusters. Let us explore this feature and see how it can benefit your organization.
 
What is an NSG?
Network Security Groups (NSGs) are crucial for maintaining robust security and efficient traffic management within cloud environments. They provide essential control over network traffic by defining rules that determine which IP addresses, ports, and protocols are allowed or denied, thereby safeguarding resources from unauthorized access and cyber threats. By segmenting security policies according to specific network …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie_Kraintz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revised release plan for Copilot subscription-based network routing]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-revised-release-plan-for-copilot-subscription-based-network-routing</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-revised-release-plan-for-copilot-subscription-based-network-routing"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revised release plan for Copilot subscription-based network routing
The post Revised release plan for Copilot subscription-based network routing appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App lock via Face ID or biometrics]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-app-lock-via-face-id-or-biometrics</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-app-lock-via-face-id-or-biometrics"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[App lock via Face ID or biometrics
The post App lock via Face ID or biometrics appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSV exports for security alerts on the organization-level security overview dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-csv-exports-for-security-alerts-on-the-organization-level-security-overview-dashboard</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-csv-exports-for-security-alerts-on-the-organization-level-security-overview-dashboard"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T21:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSV exports for security alerts on the organization-level security overview dashboard
The post CSV exports for security alerts on the organization-level security overview dashboard appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest Blog: Microsoft MVP Developed Course on Understanding Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3072</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-microsoft-mvp-developed-course-on-understanding-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re featuring an AI Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) who’s been developing content on Semantic Kernel. We wanted to highlight Jamie Maguire’s work and detail the multi-part blog below. Here’s the link to his course: New Course: Understanding Semantic Kernel – Jamie Maguire
Jamie has broken the Semantic Kernel content he’s developed for an Understanding Semantic Kernel course into 7 parts.
The post Guest Blog: Microsoft MVP Developed Course on Understanding Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Battle Over Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/the-battle-over-institutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/the-battle-over-institutions"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Battle Over Institutions appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Featured Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-featured-sponsors</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-featured-sponsors"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T17:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Featured Sponsors
The post Featured Sponsors appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning alerts for non-provider patterns and passwords are retrievable with the REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-secret-scanning-alerts-for-non-provider-patterns-and-passwords-are-retrievable-with-the-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-06-secret-scanning-alerts-for-non-provider-patterns-and-passwords-are-retrievable-with-the-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T15:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning alerts for non-provider patterns and passwords are retrievable with the REST API
The post Secret scanning alerts for non-provider patterns and passwords are retrievable with the REST API appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing lower pricing for Azure App Service Premium P0v3 to help build and modernize AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-lower-pricing-for-azure-app-service-premium-p0v3-to/ba-p/4207811</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-lower-pricing-for-azure-app-service-premium-p0v3-to/ba-p/4207811"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App Service team is excited to announce that the entry-level Premium plan known as P0v3 is now available at a significantly lower price, making it even more convenient and affordable to get started in your AI apps journey using your favorite platform-as-a-service. There is no change in price of other Azure App Service Premium plans. 
 
How much can you save with Premium v3?
Premium v3 is the latest generation of Azure App Service that offers high performance, high scalability, and high reliability as a multi-tenant managed service. Unlike previous generation plans such as Premium v2 or Standard, Premium v3 plans include commitment-based savings over one and three years that significantly lower the monthly bills, while delivering more powerful compute resources. Azure savings plans an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayunk_Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name Reservation on Azure Container Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/name-reservation-on-azure-container-registry/ba-p/4208389</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/name-reservation-on-azure-container-registry/ba-p/4208389"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T22:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's changing?
Starting August 1st, Azure Container Registry (ACR) will update its behavior regarding the deletion and re-creation of registries. ACR will prevent the reuse of a subdomain name, e.g. abc123.azurecr.io, for a period after the resource is deleted. This updated behavior enhances security and prevents subdomain takeovers by automatically reserving registry names during the creation of the ACR resource, without requiring any additional action or configuration from customers. 
 
Once a resource name is reserved, it remains reserved from the moment of creation and throughout an extended period following the deletion of the resource (referred to as a cooldown period). During this cooldown period, subscriptions not associated with the original Azure AD tenant that created the reso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving GitHub Copilot Completions in VS Code for C++ Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-improving-github-copilot-completions-in-vs-code-for-c-developers</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-improving-github-copilot-completions-in-vs-code-for-c-developers"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T23:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improving GitHub Copilot Completions in VS Code for C++ Developers
The post Improving GitHub Copilot Completions in VS Code for C++ Developers appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing enterprise multi-agent support in Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3100</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/introducing-agents-in-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “agent” has become a popular term within the industry. There have many different definitions, but at their core, they consist of a system prompt (i.e., a persona), plugins, and an ability to automatically reason and create plans to address user goals.
The post Introducing enterprise multi-agent support in Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Rickman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Managed User accounts now require email verification]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-enterprise-managed-user-accounts-now-require-email-verification</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-enterprise-managed-user-accounts-now-require-email-verification"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T20:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Managed User accounts now require email verification
The post Enterprise Managed User accounts now require email verification appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing metered billing for GitHub Enterprise and GitHub Advanced Security]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-introducing-metered-billing-for-github-enterprise-and-github-advanced-security</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-introducing-metered-billing-for-github-enterprise-and-github-advanced-security"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing metered billing for GitHub Enterprise and GitHub Advanced Security
The post Introducing metered billing for GitHub Enterprise and GitHub Advanced Security appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Noema Issue V: Threshold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/introducing-noema-issue-v-threshold</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/introducing-noema-issue-v-threshold"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T16:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Introducing Noema Issue V: Threshold appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Consumption Tax (JCT) on your GitHub Account]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-japanese-consumption-tax-jct-on-your-github-account</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-08-01-japanese-consumption-tax-jct-on-your-github-account"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Consumption Tax (JCT) on your GitHub Account
The post Japanese Consumption Tax (JCT) on your GitHub Account appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On speaking to AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-speaking-to-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/on-speaking-to-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T11:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice changes a lot of things]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Related issues  for Function App Synctriggers]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/network-related-issues-for-function-app-synctriggers/ba-p/4205866</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/network-related-issues-for-function-app-synctriggers/ba-p/4205866"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T06:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous blog: Simple Self-Troubleshooting Steps for Function App Not Seeing Triggers, I've mentioned a simple self-check method for Synctriggers. However, more and more enterprises are leaning towards using more secure network architectures. Due to the involvement of many different components, it is easy for minor configuration issues to cause the entire app to be unusable. Therefore, in this article, I will delve into more detailed content, specifically discussing NSG, UDR, DNS, and Storage Account.
 
TOC
NSG rules
UDR and Firewall
DNS
Storage Account
 
NSG rules
Please refer to this network architecture diagram first. Most enterprises want the Function App to run in a completely private network environment, hence this setup.

 
 
For outbound traffic, since the Function App is set…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theringe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/08/01/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/08/01/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I skipped Recently last month. This one’s even more
of a grab-bag than usual!
The <video> element and browser abstractions
I was reading Iván Sánchez Ortega’s thoughts on maps4html
(at the time of writing, his website is down, so that’s an archive.org
link). The post is about a theoretical HTML element that embeds
a map on a webpage - something that Iván is skeptical of and I am as well.
But this section really got me thinking:
The user experience for video back in the day, both for the user
(“I have to download what and install it where?”) and the web
developer (user agent sniffing plus an <object> inside
an <embed> with a MJPG fallback in the form of a <img>)
was quite abismal (sic). A <video> element back then made sense.
So let’s fast-forward ten years, and see what <video> has
really …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ai-for-developers/ba-p/4206684</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ai-for-developers/ba-p/4206684"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T22:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jumpstart your journey with AI. This month, we’re exploring resources to help developers to do more with AI.  Use AI to be more productive and write better code, faster; add AI to your applications to create more intelligent apps; and build customized copilot experiences for your users.
 
Live event: .NET Conf - Focus on AIJoin a free livestreaming event to learn how to add AI to your .NET apps. .NET Conf: Focus on AI is happening August 20. Watch demos, learn about the latest advancements, and see real-world examples of AI in .NET apps.
 
OpenAI GPT-4o mini is available in Azure AIOpenAI recently released GPT-4o mini, its fastest and most cost-efficient small model. GPT-4o mini is available on Azure AI, and you can try it at no cost in the Azure OpenAI Studio Playground. Get details.
 
In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mpgraven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete discussions when blocking their author from your organization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-delete-discussions-when-blocking-their-author-from-your-organization</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-delete-discussions-when-blocking-their-author-from-your-organization"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T19:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delete discussions when blocking their author from your organization
The post Delete discussions when blocking their author from your organization appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot network requests are now routed based on subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-copilot-network-requests-are-now-routed-based-on-subscription</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-copilot-network-requests-are-now-routed-based-on-subscription"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot network requests are now routed based on subscription
The post Copilot network requests are now routed based on subscription appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat and pull request summaries are now powered by GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-github-copilot-chat-and-pull-request-summaries-are-now-powered-by-gpt-4o</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-github-copilot-chat-and-pull-request-summaries-are-now-powered-by-gpt-4o"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Chat and pull request summaries are now powered by GPT-4o
The post GitHub Copilot Chat and pull request summaries are now powered by GPT-4o appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repository updates July 31st 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-repository-updates-july-31st-2024</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-31-repository-updates-july-31st-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T15:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repository updates July 31st 2024
The post Repository updates July 31st 2024 appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector Image Search using Azure OpenAI & AI Search: A Technical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/vector-image-search-using-azure-openai-amp-ai-search-a-technical/ba-p/4205393</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/vector-image-search-using-azure-openai-amp-ai-search-a-technical/ba-p/4205393"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Repository: azure-ai-vision-search
 
Introduction
Vector image search uses AI to revolutionize how we find and retrieve images. This article explains how to combine Azure OpenAI and Azure AI Search for an efficient solution. We'll cover setup, deployment, and usage to guide AI developers and engineers. We'll focus on the search and vectorize methods in the function_app.py Python file, crucial for integrating Azure's AI services for vector image searches. This technology is ideal for applications like e-commerce and digital asset management.
 
We dive into the core functionalities of the Azure AI Search service, focusing on the search and vectorize methods in the function_app.py python file. These methods are pivotal in integrating Azure's AI services to perform vector image searches…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eladt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s coming next? Summer / Fall roadmap for Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3138</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/whats-coming-next-summer-fall-roadmap-for-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T19:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like yesterday when we went live with v1.0+ of all our SDKs (Python, Java, and C#) at Microsoft Build. Since then, the Semantic Kernel team has been hard at work making Semantic Kernel even better. Now that we’ve made some progress,
The post What’s coming next? Summer / Fall roadmap for Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Bolanos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporary PayPal authorization holds on metered products]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-temporary-paypal-authorization-holds-on-metered-products</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-temporary-paypal-authorization-holds-on-metered-products"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T16:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temporary PayPal authorization holds on metered products
The post Temporary PayPal authorization holds on metered products appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run workflows set as workflow_dispatch manually]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-run-workflows-set-as-workflow_dispatch-manually</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-run-workflows-set-as-workflow_dispatch-manually"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Run workflows set as workflow_dispatch manually
The post Run workflows set as workflow_dispatch manually appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask sophisticated questions about diverse GitHub primitives on GitHub Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-ask-sophisticated-questions-about-diverse-github-primitives-on-github-mobile</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-30-ask-sophisticated-questions-about-diverse-github-primitives-on-github-mobile"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ask sophisticated questions about diverse GitHub primitives on GitHub Mobile
The post Ask sophisticated questions about diverse GitHub primitives on GitHub Mobile appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Oil That Makes LA Boil]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/its-oil-that-makes-la-boil</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/its-oil-that-makes-la-boil"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post It’s Oil That Makes LA Boil appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support for Azure.AI.OpenAI and OpenAI v2 is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3103</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/support-for-azure-ai-openai-and-openai-v2-is-coming/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T08:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announced the official OpenAI library for .NET at the Build 2024 conference. This new SDK ensures that .NET developers have parity with other programming language libraries when accessing Azure OpenAI models. This means the new SDK will be able to support the latest OpenAI features and models as soon as they come out,
The post Support for Azure.AI.OpenAI and OpenAI v2 is coming appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse engineering a day’s worth of websites]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2024/07/30/reverse-engineer-a-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2024/07/30/reverse-engineer-a-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some light reverse-engineering of websites has been
a source of entertainment and knowledge for me. I’ll poke around
in the Chrome DevTools and figure out the basics of
how popular websites work.
Sure, it’s common to compress JavaScript
and other resources, and the HTML source of webpages no longer
give many hints for technology – long gone are the days of
having a <meta name=generator tag that revealed your tech stack.
But it’s pretty easy to suss out the major tech involved and
reading obfuscated source isn’t too bad. The more you practice
the easier it is to notice the patterns.
Here’s some of what I look at in a day, with some quick reverse-engineering
applied. It’s interesting to get a sample of these applications,
the ones that I use on a daily basis.
The websites
Fastmail: custom fr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily deploy .NET apps to Azure Container Apps with default configuration for data protection]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/easily-deploy-net-apps-to-azure-container-apps-with-default/ba-p/4204285</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/easily-deploy-net-apps-to-azure-container-apps-with-default/ba-p/4204285"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Container Apps and .NET team have made it easier than ever to deploy your .NET application by supporting automatic configuration for data protection. This support is currently available as an opt-in feature in the Container Apps API version 2024-02-02-preview.
 
This blog post will discuss the feature and what it enables, how to determine if your application is correctly configured, and how to enable configuration for data protection across a variety of .NET versions.
 
What is data protection?
 
Many ASP.NET Core apps rely on a feature called data protection, which is a cryptographic API to protect data using methods like key management and rotation. By default, it requires additional configuration in both Azure and in application code to function correctly when hosted in Contai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JiachenJiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Navigation Improvements for Hovercards]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-29-keyboard-navigation-improvements-for-hovercards</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-29-keyboard-navigation-improvements-for-hovercards"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Navigation Improvements for Hovercards
The post Keyboard Navigation Improvements for Hovercards appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically submit your Maven transitive dependencies to the dependency graph]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-29-automatically-submit-your-maven-transitive-dependencies-to-the-dependency-graph</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-29-automatically-submit-your-maven-transitive-dependencies-to-the-dependency-graph"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T15:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically submit your Maven transitive dependencies to the dependency graph
The post Automatically submit your Maven transitive dependencies to the dependency graph appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.18.1: Kotlin & Swift mobile support is generally available, TypeScript 5.5 support, C# build-mode: none public beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-codeql-2-18-1-kotlin-swift-mobile-support-is-generally-available-typescript-5-5-support-c-build-mode-none-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-codeql-2-18-1-kotlin-swift-mobile-support-is-generally-available-typescript-5-5-support-c-build-mode-none-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T19:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeQL 2.18.1: Kotlin & Swift mobile support is generally available, TypeScript 5.5 support, C# `build-mode: none` public beta
The post CodeQL 2.18.1: Kotlin & Swift mobile support is generally available, TypeScript 5.5 support, C# build-mode: none public beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Enterprise Mixed Licensing beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-copilot-enterprise-mixed-licensing-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-copilot-enterprise-mixed-licensing-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T19:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Enterprise Mixed Licensing beta
The post Copilot Enterprise Mixed Licensing beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation on package name when submitting a new GitHub security advisory (GHSA)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-validation-on-package-name-when-submitting-a-new-github-security-advisory-ghsa</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-26-validation-on-package-name-when-submitting-a-new-github-security-advisory-ghsa"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T17:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Validation on package name when submitting a new GitHub security advisory (GHSA)
The post Validation on package name when submitting a new GitHub security advisory (GHSA) appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Are Equal To The Spirit You Understand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/you-are-equal-to-the-spirit-you-understand</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/you-are-equal-to-the-spirit-you-understand"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T16:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post You Are Equal To The Spirit You Understand appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Gardels</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Usage Metrics is generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-actions-usage-metrics-is-generally-available</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-actions-usage-metrics-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T22:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actions Usage Metrics is generally available
The post Actions Usage Metrics is generally available appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of enum field “detached” from the “get repositories associated with a code security configuration” endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-deprecation-of-enum-field-detached-from-the-get-repositories-associated-with-a-code-security-configuration-endpoint</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-deprecation-of-enum-field-detached-from-the-get-repositories-associated-with-a-code-security-configuration-endpoint"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of enum field "detached" from the "get repositories associated with a code security configuration" endpoint
The post Deprecation of enum field “detached” from the “get repositories associated with a code security configuration” endpoint appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Private Mirrors App – Public Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-github-private-mirrors-app-public-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-25-github-private-mirrors-app-public-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T18:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Private Mirrors App - Public Beta
The post GitHub Private Mirrors App – Public Beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Boundaries Of Consciousness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noemamag.com/exploring-the-boundaries-of-consciousness</id>
        <link href="https://www.noemamag.com/exploring-the-boundaries-of-consciousness"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Exploring The Boundaries Of Consciousness appeared first on NOEMA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Bayne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Semantic Kernel for Java 1.2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2994</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/announcing-semantic-kernel-for-java-1-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Java AI developers!
The post Announcing Semantic Kernel for Java 1.2.0 appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Keeler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 30th, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kagifeedback.org/d/4498-july-30th-2024/1</id>
        <link href="https://kagifeedback.org/d/4498-july-30th-2024/1"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kagi LLM Benchmarking Project
Introducing the Kagi LLM Benchmarking Project, which evaluates major large language models (LLMs) on their reasoning, coding, and instruction following capabilities on an unpolluted benchmark relevant to using LLMs in the context of search.

Improvements and bug fixes
Fixes to session synchronization between devices
Fixed a performance regression on initial search page load
Adjust the redirect for "no results found" when searching with Lenses #4471 @snuser
Comboboxes' search bar is overlapped by provided options below #4472 @snuser
!gi redirection broken from image result pages #4486 @tuesday
Non ascii characters breaks from image search #4434 @etra0
Image search filters not working #4424 @-mbs-
Ask questions about the page issue is still not resolved #4519 @ntt 
Search control popup is trapped inside when word definition box is present #4482 @sefidel 
Should be able to click on a Map item and see more about it #4055 @jducoeur 
Some of the text for the widgets are not translatable #4183 @Grooty 
When using upload feature it no longer responds to follow up questions #4447 @cakeboss
Upgraded Mistal Small to Mistral Nemo model in Assistant chat mode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Activity in the release-notes tag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot text completion for pull request descriptions beta]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-24-copilot-text-completion-for-pull-request-descriptions-beta</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-24-copilot-text-completion-for-pull-request-descriptions-beta"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot text completion for pull request descriptions beta
The post Copilot text completion for pull request descriptions beta appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customer Case Study: SimCorp’s AI Journey with Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=2918</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-simcorps-ai-journey-with-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T15:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to feature the SimCorp team on the Semantic Kernel blog today. The SimCorp team will discuss their AI journey and how they’ve integrated Semantic Kernel to build out their AI solutions. Let’s dive into the details from the SimCorp team!
The post Customer Case Study: SimCorp’s AI Journey with Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Lagerkrans-Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning with Semantic Kernel using Automatic Function Calling]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3011</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/planning-with-semantic-kernel-using-automatic-function-calling/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T19:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone!
The post Planning with Semantic Kernel using Automatic Function Calling appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmytro Struk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Planners in Semantic Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/?p=3032</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/the-future-of-planners-in-semantic-kernel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the very earlier days of Semantic Kernel, we have shipped experimental “planners” that use prompts to generate multi-step plans. This was extremely powerful because it allowed developers to use LLMs (which were created to merely generate text) to begin automating business processes.
The post The future of Planners in Semantic Kernel appeared first on Semantic Kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Bolanos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable secret scanning for non-provider patterns on repositories with the REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-23-enable-secret-scanning-for-non-provider-patterns-on-repositories-with-the-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-23-enable-secret-scanning-for-non-provider-patterns-on-repositories-with-the-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enable secret scanning for non-provider patterns on repositories with the REST API
The post Enable secret scanning for non-provider patterns on repositories with the REST API appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of API endpoint to enable or disable a security feature for an organization]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-22-deprecation-of-api-endpoint-to-enable-or-disable-a-security-feature-for-an-organization</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2024-07-22-deprecation-of-api-endpoint-to-enable-or-disable-a-security-feature-for-an-organization"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deprecation of API endpoint to enable or disable a security feature for an organization
The post Deprecation of API endpoint to enable or disable a security feature for an organization appeared first on The GitHub Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting Impossible Futures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/confronting-impossible-futures</id>
        <link href="https://www.oneusefulthing.org/p/confronting-impossible-futures"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T11:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We shouldn't be certain about what is next, but we should plan for it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Mollick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect Azure SQL Server via User Assigned Managed Identity under Django]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/connect-azure-sql-server-via-user-assigned-managed-identity/ba-p/4197460</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/connect-azure-sql-server-via-user-assigned-managed-identity/ba-p/4197460"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T05:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOC
Why we use it
Architecture
How to use it
References
 
Why we use it
This tutorial will introduce how to integrate Microsoft Entra with Azure SQL Server to avoid using fixed usernames and passwords. By utilizing user-assigned managed identities as a programmatic bridge, it becomes easier for Azure-related PaaS services (such as Function App or App Services) to communicate with the database without storing connection information in plain text.
 
Architecture

I will introduce each service or component and their configurations in subsequent chapters according to the order of A-D:
A: The company's account administrator needs to create or designate a user as the database administrator. This role can only be assigned to one person within the database and is responsible for basic configuratio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theringe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>