<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS following feeds | Christopher Lopes</title>
    <updated>2023-01-08T21:06:01.679Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://rss.christopherlopes.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions 2022 recap and 2023 sneak peek]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-2022-recap-and-2023-sneak-peek/ba-p/3710636</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-2022-recap-and-2023-sneak-peek/ba-p/3710636"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T20:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firstly wish you all a very happy new year. I sincerely hope that this year brings you much success. As I was doing a perspective of last year of the value that we added for Azure Functions customers - although we shipped 100’s of small improvements - I wanted to share with all of you a recap of all the major releases and provide a sneak peek on what we are working on in this year.
 
Language Versions Support: This year we continued on making sure that our customers have access to the latest language versions for various languages as soon as we can. We believe we have the most comprehensive latest support across all the major languages among all the major cloud serverless vendors. These include support for .NET 7, Python 3.10, NodeJS 18, Java 17, PowerShell 7.2 across all the SKU’s that Az…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anirudh Garg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating NGINX default configurations on Azure App services Managed WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/updating-nginx-default-configurations-on-azure-app-services/ba-p/3710146</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/updating-nginx-default-configurations-on-azure-app-services/ba-p/3710146"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T05:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure App services Managed WordPress is a new service offering provided by Microsoft Azure to host WordPress websites. It runs on a Linux machine and the technology on which this Managed WordPress site runs is PHP and the web server it uses is NGINX.
 

 
 
In this blog post, you will understand on how you can modify the default configurations of NGINX on Managed WordPress site on Azure app services.
 
On that note, let's quickly deep dive into the technical aspects of modifying the default configurations on Azure app service Managed WordPress website.
 
Now, let us quickly navigate to the Azure portal --> App service (Managed WordPress) --> click on SSH blade, this would take you to the WebSSH console.

This would open an SSH session for you as below and you can navigate to the path /etc/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>karthi2210</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning emits audit log events for custom pattern push protection enablement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-05-secret-scanning-emits-audit-log-events-for-custom-pattern-push-protection-enablement</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-05-secret-scanning-emits-audit-log-events-for-custom-pattern-push-protection-enablement"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T23:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning emits audit log events for custom pattern push protection enablement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues – January 5th update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-05-github-issues-january-5th-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-05-github-issues-january-5th-update"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T18:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues - January 5th update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Registry: the first cloud registry to support the OCI Specifications 1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-registry-the-first-cloud-registry-to-support-the/ba-p/3708998</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-registry-the-first-cloud-registry-to-support-the/ba-p/3708998"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T05:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Registry (ACR) now has support for the OCI v1.1-RC Specifications. The update continues the journey of standardizing OCI Distribution-based registries to store, discover and distribute all types of artifacts, including adding references to existing images and other OCI artifacts.
 
It started 4 years ago when ACR added support for Helm Chart distribution using the existing registry services users have already configured for their secure environments. We knew Helm adoption would require support across all registries which initiated the OCI Artifacts and ORAS projects.
 
As supply chain initiatives drove the need for distributing detached signatures for container images and signed Software Bill of Materials (SBOM), reference types were needed to add information to the registr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FeynmanZhou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning can now push protect enterprise-level custom patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-04-secret-scanning-can-now-push-protect-enterprise-level-custom-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2023-01-04-secret-scanning-can-now-push-protect-enterprise-level-custom-patterns"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T17:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning can now push protect enterprise-level custom patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reduce the deployment time using the file compression technique in Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-reduce-the-deployment-time-using-the-file-compression/ba-p/3708095</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-reduce-the-deployment-time-using-the-file-compression/ba-p/3708095"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T13:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uncompressed file uploads are slower than uploading the compressed file to the artifact when using the GitHub Workflow.
 
The time taken for a sample Node application to Azure App Service was 50mins to an hour for completing the deployment, that was triggered using GitHub Action Workflow.
The screenshot below shows the total duration for the task to complete using the default GitHub Action workflow:

 
To help mitigate the problem for reducing the deployment time significantly I have added the following steps in the GitHub Action workflow. Please note as I am using the ubuntu-latest OS to run the GitHub Action so there might be different method for file compression when using a different OS.
 
Build Stage:
- name: Zip artifact to upload
   run: zip -r ${{ env.ZIP_PACKAGE_NAME }} ${{ env.AZ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sarkarsa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulating desired throughput with Azure Load Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simulating-desired-throughput-with-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3707149</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/simulating-desired-throughput-with-azure-load-testing/ba-p/3707149"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T11:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most common way to load test applications is to simulate a specific number of virtual users. But what if you want to test the system to make sure it can handle a desired number of requests per second (RPS) ? For example, you may want to load test a payment gateway service for the number of transactions that can be processed every second. RPS or throughput is a crucial metric that reveals fundamental information about the tested system. Every system has a critical point in terms of throughput. Once the system reaches the critical point, it might keep the throughput around the same level, but the response times go up  or the requests get throttled.
In this article you’ll learn how to:

Create and run a load test for a desired RPS by using Azure Load Testing and the JMeter Throughput Shap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita_Nallamothu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2023/01/03/recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2023/01/03/recently.html"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 2023! I wrote my “2022 in review” in my paper journal and
will write about some retrospectives on how the business and such
have gone, but for now, let’s keep this traditional, a good old-fashioned
Recently.
Reading
This month’s theme, looking back on it, was feminism, and so I read
Bad Sex, which was
on quite a few best-of-2022 lists. It was fine, but mostly whetted
my appetite for the books that it referenced. The
Right to Sex on
the other hand, was a perfect sort of thought-provoking thesis that
explored a bunch of surprising topics with a lot of intellectual
power.
I’ve been experimenting with switching from my usual setup -
Feedbin for RSS and Instapaper
for read-it-later, in favor of Readwise Reader,
which does both, and more. Readwise feels flashy and has an
expansive feature …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite books of 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://macwright.com/2022/12/27/books.html</id>
        <link href="https://macwright.com/2022/12/27/books.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I read 22 books, which is about the average for the last few years. The
ratio of fiction to non-fiction was skewed toward non-fiction. I think overall
I read fewer amazing books than last year, when I finished 20, but also fewer
duds - though there certainly were some duds. Next year as always, I want to read more
and I’ll probably dive back into fiction. You can find the whole list and
reviews in the /reading section. Here are the hits.
The Invention of Brownstone Brooklyn by Suleiman Osman
My review, on IndieBound
This was the best book I read this year. It tells the story of the modern era of Brooklyn - that of real estate appreciation, displacement, redevelopment and preservation, NIMBYs and Robert Moses. Osman knits together history in a way that’s compelling but doesn’t ove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom MacWright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Functions OpenAPI Extension Update]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-openapi-extension-update/ba-p/3702128</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-functions-openapi-extension-update/ba-p/3702128"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the last update of v1.4.0, this Azure Functions OpenAPI extension has a lot of improvements. Here in this post, let's discuss what improvements have been made.
Update – v1.5.0
.NET 7 support for the isolated worker extension
According to the Azure Functions roadmap, Azure Functions isolated worker model has started supporting .NET 7. Therefore, this OpenAPI extension also starts supporting .NET 7 with the isolated worker model. The migration step is as easy as changing the target framework. Update your .csproj file and find the <TargetFramework> node, and change it from netcoreapp3.1 (.NET Core 3.1), net5.0 (.NET 5) or net6.0 (.NET 6), to net7.0 (.NET 7).
 
<Project Sdk="Microsoft.NET.Sdk">

  <PropertyGroup>
    <TargetFramework>net7.0</TargetFramework>
    <AzureFunctionsVersion>v4…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinyoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues – December 22nd update]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-22-github-issues-december-22nd-update</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-22-github-issues-december-22nd-update"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T17:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Issues - December 22nd update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GA: App Insights integration for .NET apps on App Service Linux and On by Default for .NET and Java]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ga-app-insights-integration-for-net-apps-on-app-service-linux/ba-p/3701444</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/ga-app-insights-integration-for-net-apps-on-app-service-linux/ba-p/3701444"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Azure Monitor and App Service teams are happy to share that Application Insights integration with App Services for .NET apps running on Linux is now generally available. You can now easily monitor your .NET applications on App Service Linux without changing your code by leveraging auto-instrumentation that is integrated into the App Services platform. With this feature enabled, the App Service platform will configure and attach a .NET application insights agent to your application runtime. This will allow application-level logs, metrics, and traces to flow into your Application Insights resource allowing you to understand how your .NET Linux application is performing and more easily determine the cause of any incidents. 
 
In addition to being generally available, this feature and the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YutangL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code security enablement settings on the list organization repositories REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-20-code-security-enablement-settings-on-the-list-organization-repositories-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-20-code-security-enablement-settings-on-the-list-organization-repositories-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T18:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code security enablement settings on the list organization repositories REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the stable release of Spring Cloud Azure 4.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-the-stable-release-of-spring-cloud-azure-4-5-0/ba-p/3700823</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/announcing-the-stable-release-of-spring-cloud-azure-4-5-0/ba-p/3700823"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T02:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're pleased to announce that Spring Cloud Azure version 4.5.0 has been released and is available from Maven Central. This release is compatible with:
 

Spring Boot versions:

2.5.0 through 2.5.14
2.6.0 through 2.6.14
2.7.0 through 2.7.6


Spring Cloud versions:

2020.0.3 through 2020.0.6
2021.0.0 through 2021.0.5



 
NOTE: Spring Boot 2.5.x (x > 14), 2.6.y (y > 14), and 2.7.z (z > 6) should be supported, but they weren't tested with this release.Spring Cloud 2020.0.x (x > 6) and 2021.0.y (y > 5) should be supported, but they weren't tested with this release.
 
 The 4.5.0 release focused on improving support for passwordless connections. This release is our first stable version to support passwordless connections to Azure Database for MySQL and Azure Database for PostgreSQL. For a compl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jimmyfang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access the Audit Log REST API using scoped tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-access-the-audit-log-rest-api-using-scoped-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-access-the-audit-log-rest-api-using-scoped-tokens"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T23:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the Audit Log REST API using scoped tokens]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflecting on Azure App Service’s innovations and triumphs in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/reflecting-on-azure-app-service-s-innovations-and-triumphs-in/ba-p/3664399</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/reflecting-on-azure-app-service-s-innovations-and-triumphs-in/ba-p/3664399"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T22:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, many organizations emerged from the crisis-response mode of the past few years with renewed focus on application innovation and investing for growth. Azure delivered several new experiences to improve the speed, flexibility, and cost of your app modernization projects across the spectrum of languages, frameworks, and budgets. According to Gartner, 90 percent of enterprise applications will still be in use by 2025. Azure App Service is the leading platform to support your enterprise modernization journey with a lot of innovations in store for the new year. But first, let’s take the time to celebrate and appreciate the exciting announcements from the year that was.  
 

 
 




New features and capabilities




Day zero support for .NET 7 and introducing Go on App Service 
Building …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayunk Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Weixin now partners with GitHub to notify users if their credentials are exposed in a public repository]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-tencent-wechat-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-tencent-weixin-now-partners-with-github"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T20:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent WeChat is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent WeChat is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-tencent-wechat-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-19-tencent-wechat-is-now-a-github-secret-scanning-partner"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T20:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent WeChat is now a GitHub secret scanning partner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning alerts link to providers’ docs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-16-secret-scanning-alerts-link-to-providers-docs</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-16-secret-scanning-alerts-link-to-providers-docs"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T21:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning alerts link to providers' docs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: SBOMs now attached to hosted runner image releases for Ubuntu & Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-16-github-actions-sboms-now-attached-to-hosted-runner-image-releases-for-ubuntu-windows</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-16-github-actions-sboms-now-attached-to-hosted-runner-image-releases-for-ubuntu-windows"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions: SBOMs now attached to hosted runner image releases for Ubuntu & Windows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now push protects custom patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-15-secret-scanning-now-push-protects-custom-patterns</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-15-secret-scanning-now-push-protects-custom-patterns"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning now push protects custom patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning is now available for free on public repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-15-secret-scanning-is-now-available-for-free-on-public-repositories</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-15-secret-scanning-is-now-available-for-free-on-public-repositories"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secret scanning is now available for free on public repositories]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress on Azure App Service - Top features you must know about]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/wordpress-on-azure-app-service-top-features-you-must-know-about/ba-p/3697873</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/wordpress-on-azure-app-service-top-features-you-must-know-about/ba-p/3697873"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T08:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, WordPress on Azure App Service is built on top of Azure App Service and takes advantage of all the advanced features in Azure App Service to build, deploy, and manage your WordPress applications. But that is not all; WordPress on Azure App Service makes use of other Azure Products like MySQL Flexible server, Azure CDN, Azure BLOB storage, Azure VNET, and Azure Front Door to give you the best WordPress experience. In addition to using these Azure Products, the WordPress on Azure App Service team at Microsoft makes sure that you get the latest versions of all underlying technology.
 
In this article, we will go through the top features of WordPress on Azure App Service and know why you should choose this offering for your next WordPress project!
 

Azure App Service

Az…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abhishekreddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing The Forrester Wave™: Security Analytics Platforms, Q4 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.forrester.com/?p=202821</id>
        <link href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/announcing-the-forrester-wave-security-analytics-platforms-q4-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T19:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The security analytics platform market is moving faster than it has in years, as demonstrated by these Wave results. Though Splunk still has a tight grip on the segment, competitors are finding opportunities to loosen its hold by addressing continued dissatisfaction with outdated pricing models. Hyperscalers like Microsoft are establishing themselves as top competitors through […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allie Mellen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Container Apps on Azure Arc enabled Kubernetes – Run your container apps anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-on-azure-arc-enabled-kubernetes-run-your/ba-p/3684148</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/azure-container-apps-on-azure-arc-enabled-kubernetes-run-your/ba-p/3684148"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing the Technical Preview of the ability to run Azure Container Apps on Azure Arc enabled Kubernetes Clusters, targeting AKS and AKS-HCI.
Azure Container Apps enables developers to rapidly build and deploy microservices and containerized applications.  Developers can leverage the highly optimized developer productivity capabilities of Azure Container Apps without dealing with the complexity of Kubernetes, while Operators are able to provide developers with a highly productive platform but retain the ultimate control of the underlying Kubernetes cluster(s).
Common uses of Azure Container Apps include:

Deploying API endpoints
Hosting background processing applications
Handling event-driven processing
Running microservices

Run your container apps anywhere with Azure Arc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>apwestgarth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dormant Users Report for Enterprise Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-14-dormant-users-report-for-enterprise-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-14-dormant-users-report-for-enterprise-accounts"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dormant Users Report for Enterprise Accounts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generally Available: Azure Functions support for Java 17]]></title>
        <id>generally-available-azure-functions-support-for-java-17</id>
        <link href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/generally-available-azure-functions-support-for-java-17/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T17:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use the latest LTS version of Java with Azure Functions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azure service updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions – Sharing actions and reusable workflows from private repositories is now GA]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-14-github-actions-sharing-actions-and-reusable-workflows-from-private-repositories-is-now-ga</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-14-github-actions-sharing-actions-and-reusable-workflows-from-private-repositories-is-now-ga"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T10:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions - Sharing actions and reusable workflows from private repositories is now GA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable secret scanning with the enterprise-level REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-enable-secret-scanning-with-the-enterprise-level-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-enable-secret-scanning-with-the-enterprise-level-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T21:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enable secret scanning with the enterprise-level REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unarchive a repository via the REST API]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-unarchive-a-repository-via-the-rest-api</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-unarchive-a-repository-via-the-rest-api"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T20:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unarchive a repository via the REST API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot hardens support for private registries]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-dependabot-hardens-support-for-private-registries</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-13-dependabot-hardens-support-for-private-registries"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T20:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot hardens support for private registries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Operation Results API to check the progress of deployment slots swap operation in App Service]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-operation-results-api-to-check-the-progress-of-deployment/ba-p/3641831</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/using-operation-results-api-to-check-the-progress-of-deployment/ba-p/3641831"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T07:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently there is no standard REST API to monitor swap operation, apart from using the activity logs. 
 
Web Apps - Swap Slot Slot - REST API (Azure App Service) | Microsoft Docs
 
However, we have recently found the following way to monitor the Swap operation and the same API is being used by Azure portal as well to update the Swap status and it's comparatively fast. Please refer to the steps below:
 

First call the POST Slot-Swap API & it will trigger the swap operation as shown below:

https://management.azure.com/subscriptions/{SubscriptionID}/resourceGroups/{resourceGroupName}/providers/Microsoft.Web/sites/{name}/slots/{slot}/slotsswap?api-version=2022-03-01
 
 

 
2. The above API will have location parameter in Response Headers with Operation Results API call which can be used to continuously poll in a loop until the Response is 200 (Swap completed) or (failure status code in case of swap failure)
 
GET: https://management.azure.com/subscriptions/{SubscriptionID}/resourceGroups/{resourceGroupName}/providers/Microsoft.Web/sites/{name}/slots/{slot}/operationresults/915677b6-ea92-44c9-865b-95cfc693d5bb?api-version=2018-11-01
 
Polling: Swap in accepted/in-progress state:
 

 
Polling: Swap completed:
 

 
Thanks to @DeependraChaudhary for sharing the approach.
If you have any questions or feedback, please add a comment below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shuanand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigate Azure Spring Apps Networking Issue with the new Connect feature]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/investigate-azure-spring-apps-networking-issue-with-the-new/ba-p/3693455</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/investigate-azure-spring-apps-networking-issue-with-the-new/ba-p/3693455"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T05:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In A Simple Network Connection Test Tool for Azure Spring Cloud we demonstrated a way to build a very simple App for DNS resolve and TCP ping tests in Azure Spring Apps.
 
Azure Spring Apps published a new Connect Feature that allows you access the shell environment inside your application instances to do advanced troubleshooting.
 
This blog aimed to describe how to directly access the shell environment inside your application instances to investigate common networking issues.
 
Step 1: Connect to an app instance for troubleshooting 
Step 2: Investigate Azure Spring Apps Networking Issue in the Console 
Step 1: Connect to an app instance for troubleshooting
Reference Doc: Connect to an app instance for troubleshooting
1. Before connecting to an app instance, you must be granted the role A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hanli_Ren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rename repositories while transferring them]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-12-rename-repositories-while-transferring-them</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2022-12-12-rename-repositories-while-transferring-them"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T18:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rename repositories while transferring them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Duck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental illness plays havoc with the mind as well as the heart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503201650.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T00:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to pay more attention to the physical impacts of mental illness. It could not only be messing with your mind, but also your heart, say scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute sleep loss may alter the way we see others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/05/220503102900.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows that young adults when sleep-deprived evaluate angry faces as less trustworthy and healthy-looking. Furthermore, neutral and fearful faces appear less attractive following sleep loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Molecular basis of deep sleep pinpointed, suggests avenues for novel treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429145059.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists pinpoint the molecular epicenter of deep-sleep regulation. The findings, based on research in mice, identify a gene that makes a protein that regulates delta waves -- electrical signals between neurons that occur during the deepest phases of relaxation and are a hallmark of restorative sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sleep molecule discovered: 'It shows just how complex the machinery of sleep is']]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220429144940.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers presents a new study demonstrating that a small molecule in brain cells affects the level of hypocretin, which is responsible for making us feel awake during the day and tired at night. People with a genetic variation of this molecule have a higher risk of suffering from daytime sleepiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours of sleep is optimal in middle and old age, say researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220428125425.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T16:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven hours is the ideal amount of sleep for people in their middle age and upwards, with too little or too much little sleep associated with poorer cognitive performance and mental health, say researchers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risky driving behaviors increase as common sleep disorder worsens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420170509.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up to half of older adults may have sleep apnea, a condition in which breathing and sleep are briefly interrupted many times a night. A new study shows that this chronic tiredness can have serious implications for road safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia delivered over the internet shown to be highly effective in Black women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420113004.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T15:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black women are disproportionately affected by poor sleep, which is associated with increased risk of adverse outcomes such as cardiovascular disease, depression and worse quality of life. The gold standard treatment for insomnia is cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I), which specifically targets the individual's problematic sleep behaviors and beliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drug reduced frequency of breathing pauses in sleep apnea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220414165551.htm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study has paved the way for the first drug treatment for sleep apnea. Compared to before receiving the treatment, breathing pauses decreased with on average more than 20 per hour for patients given the drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Insomnia News -- ScienceDaily</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>